<?xml version="1.0"  ?>

	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" ><channel><title>CiTR -- Radio Freethinkers</title><description></description><itunes:summary></itunes:summary><itunes:author>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Radio freethinker is a radio show promoting skepticism, critical thinking and science. We examine popular extraordinary claims and subject them to our critical analysis. These claims may fall into the category of religion, alternative medicine, conspiracy</itunes:subtitle><itunes:owner> <itunes:name>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:name><itunes:email>technicalservices@citr.ca</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="http://www.citr.ca/podcast_photos/radiofreethinkers.jpg"/><itunes:link rel="image" type="video/jpeg" href="http://www.citr.ca/podcast_photos/radiofreethinkers.jpg">CiTR -- Radio Freethinkers</itunes:link><image><link>http://www.citr.ca</link><url>http://www.citr.ca/podcast_photos/radiofreethinkers.jpg</url><title>CiTR -- Radio Freethinkers</title></image><link>http://www.citr.ca</link><generator> podcast mate 2000</generator><item><title>RFT - Ep 274  Mental Health Edition 18-Nov-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 15:04:00 -0800</pubDate><description>RFT - Ep 274  Mental Health Edition

This week a special show with guest Matt Harvey.

We take look at the way popular media portrays and stigmatized mental illnessthe disconnect between the reality of mental illness and the fictional account we all assume it true.

Matt shares a very personal and inspirational story of being stricken with Bi-Polar Disorder, learning to live with and finding that it can be both a source of strength but a lens to help one realize how very lucky we arenot sure what I mean by that, listen and find out.


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 274 -  Mental illness...How the media distorts it, who we should view it and yes, there is someone who cares</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141118-150400-to-20141118-160400.mp3" length="57320948" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141118-150400-to-20141118-160400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - Ep 273 - Electric Element Edition 11-Nov-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 15:03:35 -0800</pubDate><description>RFT - Ep 273 - Electric Element Edition
This week rant is about which poppy should you wear this remembrance day...white, red or both...

In Five new things

We talk about:
- What IS electricity
- The duality of electrons
- DNA in blood cells
- What is your blood made of
- And how are all the elements of the universe made

We also close some web wisdom...a debate about the colour of your poppy...how you skin heals itself and how we are the cosmos's way to know itself

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 273 -  Which poppy to wear, what is electricity,DNA and blood, are we star stuff and a debate over white and red poppies.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141111-150335-to-20141111-160600.mp3" length="59716613" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141111-150335-to-20141111-160600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - Ep 272 - Left in Toronto Edition 04-Nov-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 15:05:26 -0800</pubDate><description>RFT - Ep 272 - Left in Toronto Edition

This week a web wisdom bonanzaplanned obsolescence, not all conspiracies are falseDoctors conflict of interest, the end of everything, UN climate change report and what happened to Olivia Chow in Toronto

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 272 -  planned obsolescence, not all conspiracies are falseDoctors conflict of interest, the end of everything, UN climate change report and what happened to Olivia Chow in Toronto</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141104-150526-to-20141104-160720.mp3" length="59178266" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141104-150526-to-20141104-160720.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - Ep 271 - Halloween Edition 28-Oct-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 15:06:00 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT - Ep 271 - Halloween Edition

This week are ghost possible? What is the origin of witches?

We also discuss the commercialization of Halloween that has turned into an almost 8 billion dollar industry south of the boarder.

But we start the show with a blast from the past as we do a recasting of our very first Halloween special...where we discuss the origins of Halloween...the real world origins of vampires and werewolves and how dangerous is taking candy from strangers?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinkers - Ep 271 - Origins of Halloween, real Vampires and Warwolves, Are ghost possible, witches thought time and the economics of Halloween</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141028-150600-to-20141028-160600.mp3" length="57357227" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141028-150600-to-20141028-160600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - Ep 270 - Islamophobia Edition 21-Oct-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 15:06:17 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Islamophobia Edition
&lt;Note: about 55 min, i quote Reza Aslan and used a sound filter to differentiate his words/voice from mine...it seems the filter i used is so much of a distraction. my apologizes.

This week we are joined by host emeritus Ethan Clow.

In the light of a recent dust up between Ben Affleck and Sam Harris/Bill Maherabout whether criticism of Islam equals islamaphobiawhether liberals should stop being hypocritical about social ills perpetrated by Muslims

Well, we take a skeptical look at whether or not Islam is the most violent or worst mass religion everor at least currentlyis it true that any criticism of Islam equated to islamaphobiaare liberals NOT criticizing Muslims for social ills like womens rights?

Lastly, we take direct aim at Sam Harris and just what is his problem</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinkers - Ep 270 - Is Islam as bad as Sam Harris claims? And is Sam Harris as bad as Ben Affleck claims?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141021-150617-to-20141021-160640.mp3" length="57724604" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141021-150617-to-20141021-160640.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - 5 New Things Edition 07-Oct-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - 5 New Things Edition

This week a new segment5 new things you might not know..

What is a planet? Until 2006, that term has no offical meaning. When it did, we went from 9 to 8 planets.

Life-like killers  There is a things that technically are not life but are life-like and  kill millions of people each yearwhat are they?

What happened to 10 DAYS in 1582? In what could be one of the greatest conspiracies of the all timeslearn how the Catholic Church made 10 days disappear from history

Leaping time why do we have lead years and what the hell is a leap second? The choice humanity faces between real and apparent time

Where is the end of the solar system? Voyager 1 has left the solar system at lest 3 timesand it has yet to reach the real edge of our system.

Also, ISIS reduxa path that will not end well

and some web wisdom about

Leap years
Leap seconds
What do vitamins do again
Zombie Prionslife that is not alive?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 269 - What is a planet, Life-like killers, 10 DAYS in 1582, Leaping time, end of the solar system, ISIS redux and web wisdom</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141007-150000-to-20141007-160000.mp3" length="57335960" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141007-150000-to-20141007-160000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Ig Nobel 2014 Edition 31-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 15:35:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Ig Nobel 2014 Edition

This week a look at some of the Ig Nobel Awards...
  - neuroscience prize: Seeing Jesus in toast
  - mental health: Is it mentally hazardous to own a cat
  - physics: Frictional Coefficient under Banana Skin
  - biology: Dogs are sensitive the Earth's magnetic field
  - nutrition:Infant feces used to make sausages...no, really.
  -  aesthetic: Arts affect on pain...they use lasers!

And some web wisdom....
  - Pareidolia - Why we see things not really there
  - Taxoplasmosis - Is you cat dangerous to your health
  - Magnetoception - 'Seeing' magnetic waves

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 268 humorous science that makes a point, pareidolia, taxoplasmosis, and magnetoception</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140930-153500-to-20140930-163600.mp3" length="58316327" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140930-153500-to-20140930-163600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - ISIS Edition 16-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - ISIS Edition 

This week -

We postpone our rant to remind everyone that the Ebola epidemic is not only continuing in Africa but gaining momentum. We share a little web wisdom from about the scale and urgency for the world to react.

Also, we take an extended look at ISIS or the Islamic State...who are they, how have they gain such success...should be be afraid or worried about them. We also discuss the very real dangers present by the US reaction to ISIS...will we have a repeat of 9/11 where the cure is worse than the disease?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 267 - Ebola epidemic is still going on and getting worse and an extended look at ISIS and the US reaction.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140916-150000-to-20140916-160000.mp3" length="57337211" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140916-150000-to-20140916-160000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Teachers Strike Edition 09-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Teachers Strike Edition

This week -

A rant about the Teachers strikewho is right? We take a skeptical is not balanced look at the issues that precipitated and prolongs the educational unrest.

Also Don rambles about how a hundred years ago the FIRST mechanized unit of the British Army was the Canadian Automobile Machine Gun Brigadealso, how on this day in 1941 Dennis Richie was bornthe creator of the C programming language, perhaps the most profound moment in the history of computingalso, how in 1752 11 days were literately wiped off the calendar

And also have some web wisdom about the evolution of the Gregorian Calendarthe role of Horses in World War One..Tim Mitchins The Storm and a sample of Last Week Tonight with John Oliver about some sexting Geckos</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 266 - a Strike and why it's happeing, 100 years ago cool stuff happened, web wisdom about the lost 11 days, Heros who were horses, Tim Mitchin's the Storm and lastly a sample of John Oliver and sexy Geckos</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140909-150000-to-20140909-160000.mp3" length="57331373" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140909-150000-to-20140909-160000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Shark-umantary Edition 02-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Shark-umantary Edition

A rant about mandatory surcharges for criminalsand how it harms victims of crime. A classic example of Harpers bait-and-switchsidestepping federal responsibility for the well being and health care of victims of crime and shifting it criminals who are unable to pay for these social servicewhich should be part of the social safety net.

Also, with Shark Week gone, we take a look at the decline of science documentaries as they try to compete with Big Bang Theory and Big Brotheralso the mockumentaries the Discovery Channel peddles and how it has turned into tabloid scient-ish network

And we take a look at a number of science facts that are actually fictionlike we only use 10% of our brainsour nails grow after death and lightning never strikes twice.

We end the show with some web wisdom about the growing dangers of drug resistance bugs thanks to our over use and misuse of antibiotics..

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 265 - Harper victimizes victims of crime, Sharks and the Discovery Channel's psuedo-mentries, and facts you thought you new but are wrong.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140902-150000-to-20140902-160100.mp3" length="58293392" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140902-150000-to-20140902-160100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - The Something Completely Different Edition 26-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - The Something Completely Different Edition

This show is a bit of an experiment in stylemore rifting, less scripting and things you need to know

This week -

There has been much talk about privilege and implicit oppressionnotably via race, gender and sexuality. Panti Bliss gave a great talk about this when she was taken to court for calling someone homophobicas it turned out, she as a gay man cannotwell, you should listen, it is very enlightening

Also, an interview from Democracy Now with Vijay Prashad on Rise of Islamist Militias &amp; Bloody Legacy of 2011 U.S. Intervention. Something you are not likely to hear on corporate media

And we close the show with some wisdom of Noam Chomsky about reform, revolution, a democratic workplace and utopinamism

AS an Easter egg somewhere in the show is Symphony of Sciences latesta tribute to Robin WilliamsSeize the Day.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 264 - Implicit self-directed bias with Panti Bliss, Libya civil was, Syria and ISIS and what corporate media is not reporting and Chomsky on reform and revolution</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140826-150000-to-20140826-160100.mp3" length="58291724" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140826-150000-to-20140826-160100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - The Goodbye Robin Williams Edition 19-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 15:09:58 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - The Goodbye Robin Williams Edition

This week whine is a Ebola redux editionstop talking about a miracle cure and start putting doctors on the ground.

When is too much tolerance of intolerance too much? We talk about how a group of Hindu fundamentalist managed to so what every Nazi wish they could doand they did it with the magic power of RELIGION.

What is the Hitler test and how can it help us know when we should and should not tolerate intolerance

Traffic safety and the possible crime of driving while brown

A man who left a mark on my life and many of my friendsthe passing of Robin Williams has made us all sad at the tragedy of it allthis week half the show is a tribute to the genius that was RobinCarpe DiemRIP.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 263 - Ebola and the magic serum, CBSA and how intolerance banished women for terminal 3, pulled over from driving while brown and a wake for Robin Williams...</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140819-150958-to-20140819-160240.mp3" length="50367056" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140819-150958-to-20140819-160240.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - The Ebola Virus Bias Edition Edition 12-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - The Ebola Virus Bias Edition Edition

This week whine is about the Ebola Virusmore to the point how what was a page 3 story when it only killed Africans became front page material once a white american gets infected.

In the shadow of the all the hype and hysteria, this week we look at the outbreak why its worse than previous and why we really really should not be that worried..

Joining me this week is host emeritus and sometimes historian Ethan Clow as we discuss Harpers latest attack on democracy as the CRA is ramping up unnecessary and unprecedented audits of charities that are critical of the Harper Regime.

Ethan and I discuss the issue and how it has put a chill on non-profits across the nation as well as how this can dramatically undermined the democratic process as we seem one more step closer to a Harper-ocracy.

Finally a look at cognitive biaseswhat are they, how they effect us and what can be done. This may explain why every decision you made has been right, why you by more food on a hungry stomach and why you think people are idiots for not knowing what you know.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 262 - How Ebola made the front page, Is Harper using the CRA to crack down on inconvenient NGOs? and Cognitive Biases and why we make such bad choices</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140812-150000-to-20140812-160000.mp3" length="57335960" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140812-150000-to-20140812-160000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Canada Goes To War Edition 05-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 15:01:45 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Canada Goes To War Edition

This week an extended look at how the Great War affected Canada. 

Joining me this week is host emeritus and sometimes historian Ethan Clow.

We talk about the defining battles for Canada, their role in the bigger picture of the war.

We discuss the darker side of the war when Canada interned thousand of &quot;enemy agents&quot; and forced tens of thousand to register...

We note how racism has changed between the two world wars, by pointing out that the vast majority of interned were actually people of Ukrainian descent.

We cover perhaps the most defining issue in Canadian history the conscription crisis of 1917 and how questionable politics pushed this bill through parliament.

We also reflect how the war placed Canada as an independent nation on the world stage.

To close the show, some web wisdom about the Conscription Crisis of 1917.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 261 - Canada declaires war, Canada's military record, the War and home, Canada's identity, Independence from UK and the Conscription Crisis.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140805-150145-to-20140805-160136.mp3" length="57214196" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140805-150145-to-20140805-160136.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - Classic - Best of 250s 29-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 15:01:41 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT - Classic - Best of 250s

Facebook big experiment editing you friends feedwhy are we not more angry?

Justin and the PopeJustin Trudeau exercises dictatorial powers to deny an anti-abortion candidate from running as a liberal, he then get threatened with excommunication for his pro-choice viewsso, we are left wondering is religious people should be banned from public office?

The dirty dozen and misreporting toxic food

A look at the new prostitution bill...Protection of Communities and Exploited Persons Act. A bill that is more oppressive than the one just struck down and ironically named for it is a bill to exploit sex workers for political gains.

GMOs and you  After tens of thousands of years of modifying organisms, what does GMO mean now? And the most counter-intuitive argument for GMO labeling.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Best of the 250s - Facebook censors, Justin and the Pope, the Dirty Dozen, New Prostitution law and GMOs and you</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140729-150141-to-20140729-160335.mp3" length="59058170" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140729-150141-to-20140729-160335.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker - Science Word Abuse Edition 22-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 15:02:56 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker - Science Word Abuse Edition

This week science words that we misuse in everyday conversations,

Web wisdomfacts about evolution you may have forgotten

WWI  Lest we Forgetthe dominoes that lead to the start of world war one.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 260 - Scientific words we always seem misuse, facts on evolution and what were the events that started WWI</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140722-150256-to-20140722-160534.mp3" length="59803349" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140722-150256-to-20140722-160534.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Gaza's Burning Edition 15-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 15:03:13 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Gaza's Burning Edition

Because of the myopia of main stream media, this week episode will provide alternative views about the crisis in the Gaza strip from the alternative media

This week's whine - Gaza and the biased reporting by the main stream media

Web wisdom...Israeli Propaganda and the Politics of Revenge against Gaza -  interview with Ali Abunimah and Max Blumenthal discuss how the Israeli government manipulated the public into accepting an escalated military operation against Gaza after the murder of three Israeli teenagers - July 11, 2014

Web wisdom...&quot;Israel Targets Civilians, the Casualties Speak Volumes&quot;: Intl Protection Urged for Besieged Gaza - interview with Palestinian attorney Diana Buttu, who has served as a legal adviser to the Palestinians in negotiations with Israel and to Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas

Web wisdom...A Ground Invasion of Gaza Will Achieve Nothing But More Bloodshed - interview with Haaretz columnist Gideon Levy says the people of Gaza are victims of Israeli domestic politics and treated like hostages by Hamas -   July 14/2014 Real News Network

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFt - Ep 259 - Balance reporting on the Gaza Strip - Special information edition</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140715-150313-to-20140715-160331.mp3" length="57524444" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140715-150313-to-20140715-160331.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Who Shot the Archduke Edition 08-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 15:01:16 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Who Shot the Archduke Edition

Facebook big experiment editing you friends feedwhy are we not more angry?

Snowden one year laterwhat have we learned and what have we done about it?

And Legal anachronismsimmorality still a crime and crime comic still illegal

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 258 - Facebook edits feed, Snowden one year later, the shot that started WW1 and Crime Comics and Immoral homes</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140708-150116-to-20140708-160208.mp3" length="58035269" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140708-150116-to-20140708-160208.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Sex Sells Redux Edition 01-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 15:07:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Sex Sells Redux Edition
&lt;note: repodded due to incorrect start time&gt;
This week's whine - Iraq and global rights...of the UN's Right to Protect ushered in the idea of Global Citizen's with universal rights and how Syria and now Iraq exemplifies who horrible we have cocked it up in it's implementation.

A look at the new prostitution bill...Protection of Communities and Exploited Persons Act. A bill that is more oppressive than the one just struck down and ironically named for it is a bill to exploit sex workers for political gains.

A case for the justification of brothels...should brothels and sex work in general be legalized and regulated or is prostitution innately harmful? We scour the globe to find evidence as to what is the better social policy.

Lastly, some web wisdom - How Class Works...what class is all about and applies that understanding to the foreclosure crisis of 2007--2011.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 257 - Iraq and global rights, New protitution law, should brothel be legalized and how class works</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140701-150700-to-20140701-160800.mp3" length="58314659" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140701-150700-to-20140701-160800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Sex Sells Redux Edition 24-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Sex Sells Redux Edition

This week's whine - Iraq and global rights...of the UN's Right to Protect ushered in the idea of Global Citizen's with universal rights and how Syria and now Iraq exemplifies who horrible we have cocked it up in it's implementation.

A look at the new prostitution bill...Protection of Communities and Exploited Persons Act. A bill that is more oppressive than the one just struck down and ironically named for it is a bill to exploit sex workers for political gains.

A case for the justification of brothels...should brothels and sex work in general be legalized and regulated or is prostitution innately harmful? We scour the globe to find evidence as to what is the better social policy.

Lastly, some web wisdom - How Class Works...what class is all about and applies that understanding to the foreclosure crisis of 2007--2011.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 257 - Iraq and global rights, New protitution law, should brothel be legalized and how class works</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140624-150000-to-20140624-160000.mp3" length="57469817" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140624-150000-to-20140624-160000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - What Good is the News Edition 17-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 15:05:43 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - What Good is the News Edition

This week more web wisdom...

A 2008 interview with the very nationalist Mel Hurtig about his book &quot;Truths about Canada&quot;...about how Canada has changed, very much for the worse, in the last twenty years. As a result of these profound (often hidden) changes, we are no longer the people we think we are.
Mel states that he wrote the book because we cant do anything to fix the direction were drifting in unless we recognize it  and recognize The Truth About Canada.
Now this book was published in 2008  and he makes some predictions about Canadanow, 8 years on, it is surprising how these predictions fared.

also,

Alain de Botton asks: What is it that were really looking for when we watch or read the news  and is it doing us any good?

Listen as de Botton turns his philosophical lens on The News, to examines the peculiar position it holds in our lives  and offers counsel on the precautions we should take before venturing anywhere near it and the noise it generates.

Lastly, how many of you have gone out and spent too much money to watch X-Men: days of future past?
I bet a number of you wish you were mutants with special powerswell it may surprise you that many of you ARE mutants and that power may have help your kind rule the world.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 256 - Truths about Canada, the value of news and I bet youre a mutant</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140617-150543-to-20140617-160724.mp3" length="58838828" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140617-150543-to-20140617-160724.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Dirty Dozen Edition 10-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 15:05:35 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Dirty Dozen Edition

This weeks whine - The dirty dozen and misreporting toxic food

Blinded by Science - Mice gotta run, The Beast asteroid and DNA expands

Prairie Correspondent - Reflections on the phrase &quot;thank god&quot;

Web Wisdom - Ted-ED - How to choose your news - Damon Brown

And D-Day...meaning to Canada and the context of controversy

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 255 - apples most &quot;toxic&quot; , mice gotta run, The Beast asteroid and DNA expands, pondering the phrase thank god, how to choose your news and  D-Day remembrance and furry</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140610-150535-to-20140610-160452.mp3" length="56540324" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140610-150535-to-20140610-160452.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Dark Origins Edition 03-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Dark Origins Edition

This week a whine about Evidence Based Medicine and a childs capacity to consent, 

Our Prairie Correspondent Talks Language, Bias and Politics,

a Bright Side Segment on a New Prize to Save the World and 

a shyte just got interesting segment on Dark Origins of Fairy-tales and Nursery Rhymes.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 253 - Evidence Based Medicine, childs capacity to consent, Language, Bias and Politics, a New Prize to Save the World and  Dark Origins of Fairy-tales and Nursery Rhymes.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140603-150000-to-20140603-160000.mp3" length="57178751" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140603-150000-to-20140603-160000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - No Bananas Edition 27-May-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - No Bananas Edition 

This week
-	Too big to jailthere seems to be two legal system, one for you and me and one for corporations (and the rich). We get put into jail, they get a fine and have go back to doing what they do. 
-	Fair Election Lawjust days away for become the law of the land, we look and what was change and what we lost.
-	Media consolidationCanada has the highest levels of media concentration in the world, we also have the most vertically integrated media in the world. We look at how this harms society and what we can do the fix it!
-	Justin and the PopeJustin Trudeau exercises dictatorial powers to deny an anti-abortion candidate from running as a liberal, he then get threatened with excommunication for his pro-choice viewsso, we are left wondering is religious people should be banned from public office?
-	Yes, We have no more bananasIt is likely that with a decade our beloved proof of god, the Cavendish banana will be on the verge of extinctionhow did it happen and what can be done about it? Plus, why doesnt banana pudding taste like bananas?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 254 - too big to jail, Neighbors and the world, Fair Election Law, Media consolidation, Justin and the Pope and Yes, We have no more bananas</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140527-150000-to-20140527-160130.mp3" length="58616984" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140527-150000-to-20140527-160130.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - Classic - Best of 240s take 2 20-May-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 15:02:02 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT - Classic - Best of 240s take 2
Due to technical difficulties, the podcast was cut short, so this week is a rebroadcast of the show in it's entirety. 

This time a rewind on Killing the CBC plus a bonus update to the story.

Also, what is it to be a Canadian?

and a debunking of Astrology plus a bonus clip of Carl Sagan on astrology.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Best of the 240sT2 - Killing the CBC, MacIntyre speaks out, what's a Canadian and debunking astrology</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140520-150202-to-20140520-160029.mp3" length="55873958" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140520-150202-to-20140520-160029.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - Classic - Best of 240s 13-May-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 15:15:00 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT - Classic - Best of 240s

NOTE: due to technical issues, this episode is 15 minutes short. The complete show can be heard here:

http://www.radiofreethinker.ca/podcasts/RFT-BestOfThe240s.mp3

This time a rewind on Killing the CBC plus a bonus update to the story.

Also, what is it to be a Canadian?

and a debunking of Astrology plus a bonus clip of Carl Sagan on astrology.</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Best of the 240s - Killing the CBC, MacIntyre speaks out, what's a Canadian and debunking astrology</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140513-151500-to-20140513-155931.mp3" length="42572909" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140513-151500-to-20140513-155931.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - The GMO and You Edition 06-May-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 15:01:30 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - The GMO and You Edition

This week: 
A special report from the Prairies on poverty  How kicking out a homeless man from a grocery store reflects on the deficiencies of our society.

Non-english signs  Recent debate about a Chinese only sign in Richmond leads to thought about what multiculturalism ultimately means.

Temporary foreign workers  A 40yr old program gone off the rails under Harpers watchhow did it happen?

Chernobyl at 28  28yrs later, life has not only survived at Chernobyl but is flourishing.

GMOs and you  After tens of thousands of years of modifying organisms, what does GMO mean now? And the most counter-intuitive argument for GMO labeling.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFt - Ep 252 - a special report from the Prairies on poverty, Non-english signs, temporary foreign workers, Chernobyl at 28 and GMOs and you</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140506-150130-to-20140506-160130.mp3" length="57358061" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140506-150130-to-20140506-160130.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - The Sector Edition 29-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 15:03:57 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - The Sector Edition

This week: NGOs, non-profits and charitieswhat are they and what are they good for? We also have our irregular regular Ethan Clow talk about his new venture The Sector.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 251 - NGO, Non-Profits and Charities: What are they and what are they good for, plus Ethan's new venture, The Sector</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140429-150357-to-20140429-160523.mp3" length="58730825" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140429-150357-to-20140429-160523.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Landmark 250th Edition 22-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 15:01:12 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Landmark 250th Edition

This weeks whine is about the Senates push back on the Fair Elections act...weak tea. As well as the mystifying comments of Senator Frum accusing Elections Canada of a conflict of interest.

Celebrating our 250th episode we have a visit for past host Chloe, Daniel and Rob...we as read a message from Jenna.

And as a special treat we are rebroadcasting the very first episode of Radio Free Thinker...how the show has evolved.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 248 - Push back on Fair Elections act, visits for past host and a recast of the very first RFT</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140422-150112-to-20140422-160320.mp3" length="59399693" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140422-150112-to-20140422-160320.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Killing the CBC Edition 15-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 15:01:31 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Killing the CBC Edition

This weeks whine: Killing the CBC, how the Harper government is yet again trying to destroy another crown jewel of Canada.

Seriously the Unfair Elections Act is Important: How did Poilievre become Minister for Democratic Reform, how the the act craft and again...how it can destroy democracy in Canada - The Harper fix is in!

Climate Change...even more certainty and dire warnings, again - The IPCC released it latest report on the state of the worlds climate and we're serious screwed!

and, 
Society Is Doomed: NASA funded study shows the not only do civilizations collapse, it happens regularly and is inevitable...but there is an upside.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 248 - Killing the CBC, UnFair Elections act...it's important!, IPCC climate change report, and Society Is Doomed: NASA</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140415-150131-to-20140415-160443.mp3" length="60422177" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140415-150131-to-20140415-160443.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Special - The Shock Doctrine 08-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 15:03:24 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Special - The Shock Doctrine

As part of our Wisdom from the Web series, this week we present an interview Naomi Klein gave at the launch of her book Shock Doctrine. In this interview she discusses the books theme that the neoliberal free market policies have risen to prominence in some countries because of a deliberate strategy of certain leaders to exploit crises by pushing through controversial, exploitative policies while citizens were too busy emotionally and physically reeling from disasters or upheavals to create an effective resistance. 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Special - The Shock Doctrine - Disaster Capitalism</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140408-150324-to-20140408-160324.mp3" length="57404765" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140408-150324-to-20140408-160324.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Canada Post Bank Edition 01-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 15:03:46 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Canada Post Bank Edition

The Whine of the Week - the ominous omnibus budget bill: what's wrong with presenting a bloated bill, how it subverts democracy and why its not an accident.

With much discussion about the woes of Canada Post's immanent demise and the need to cut service, we take a look at the validity of this prophecy of doom and how resurrecting the Canada Post Bank would shore up the crown corp and provide a valued social service.

And we review the global condemnation of the Fair Elections Act as an open letter from Canadian academics is joined by one from the worlds academics.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 248 - ominous omnibus budget bill, Canada Post myths and a Canada Post Bank, the world sends an open letter on elections.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140401-150346-to-20140401-160212.mp3" length="55857695" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140401-150346-to-20140401-160212.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT Classics - Skepticism 01 Edition - 25-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 14:59:52 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT Classics - Out take on skepticism Edition
Some of the best from our first season:

Ahead of the Curve - A warning about Conspiracy Theory with Jesse Ventura
Science and Skepticism
Interview with Jennifer Kaban discussing Science and Media
Interview with Justin Trottier, then national director of Center For Inquiry, discussing skeptical tribalism and free speech.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT Classics - Skepticism 01 - Conspiracy Theory with Jesse Ventura, Science and Skepticism, Science and Media and skeptical tribalism and free speech.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140325-145952-to-20140325-160037.mp3" length="58053617" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140325-145952-to-20140325-160037.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Crimean War 2014 Edition 18-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 15:01:39 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Crimean War 2014 Edition

Don puts in on the record that he missing Malysian plan was stolen...

This weeks harangue restated the argument against the anti-vax rhetoric and makes a case for the criminalization of such speech.

We take another look the growing tension in the Ukraine as well as point out the similarities between the revolution in Kiev to that in Crimea. As well as making parallels to Putin's claims to the Crimea and Hitler's to the Sudetenland. 

And more wisdom from the web as we share 3 CGP Grey's talks about the problems with voting.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 247 - Anti-Vax-ers should be jailed, Crimean War or political farce, and A look at the problems with voting</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140318-150139-to-20140318-160119.mp3" length="57037388" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140318-150139-to-20140318-160119.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - Crimean War 2014 Edition 18-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2014 15:01:39 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - Crimean War 2014 Edition

Don puts in on the record that he missing Malysian plan was stolen...

This weeks harangue restated the argument against the anti-vax rhetoric and makes a case for the criminalization of such speech.

We take another look the growing tension in the Ukraine as well as point out the similarities between the revolution in Kiev to that in Crimea. As well as making parallels to Putin's claims to the Crimea and Hitler's to the Sudetenland. 

And more wisdom from the web as we share 3 CGP Grey's talks about the problems with voting.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 247 - Anti-Vax-ers should be jailed, Crimean War or political farce, and A look at the problems with voting</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140318-150139-to-20140318-160119.mp3" length="57037388" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140318-150139-to-20140318-160119.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinkers - BitCoin Edition 11-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers - BitCoin Edition

Don's harangue about journalist's and speaking fees. Journalist the fourth estate are a fundamental pillar of a democracy. Journalist are afforded special privileges and protections. That is all compromised when they become journo-celebrities. 

An in-depth look at Bitcoin...what is it, how do you mine them, how are they used and how can they be stolen. With emphasis on the MtGox event where almost a billion dollars was stolen...making it the 2nd biggest bank job in history.

Wisdom from the Web - RSA animation, &quot;Crisis with Capitalism&quot;

And another internet get, What is critical thinking?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 246 - Jounalism and speeking fees, Bitcoins or what's up with MtGox?, Crisis with Capitalism and What is critical thinking?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140311-150000-to-20140311-160038.mp3" length="57941027" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140311-150000-to-20140311-160038.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thihkers - Fantasy Fundrive Edition 04-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 14:58:52 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thihkers - Fantasy Fundrive Edition

This weeks show
We take a look at the Crisis in Crimea, when and how did the latest crisis start, why did Russia invade, Whats the history of the region, is Putin recreating the old Soviet Union, or is just a deluded neo-tsarist?

We discuss fiction and how that plays out in the skeptical community.

And we critique Bill Nyes creation debate and will this finally but an end to skeptics debating fringe ideas?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 245 - Whats up in the Ukraine, skepticism and fiction, Creation debate or debacle, and its pledge drivetime.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140304-145852-to-20140304-160407.mp3" length="62365397" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140304-145852-to-20140304-160407.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 244 - Free Trade Edition - 25-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 15:00:54 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 244 - Free Trade Edition

Dons harangue is about Terrorist, capital T and what we learned from the Sochi Olympics

On the 25th Anniversary of CAFTA and 20th for NAFTA, we take a look at free trade and what to be looking at with the pending Trans Pacific Partnership.

As skeptics, we are often accused of being closed minded by peddlers of pseudoscience, alt-med, and believers in supernatural. To help explain why this an inverted position, we have a guest clip from QualiSoup, who does a good takedown on why proponents of Woo are really the closed minded.

We close the show with another guest clip from SciShow which talks about the topic of taboo scienceare there areas or topics that should be out-of-bounds for science?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 244 - What we have learned abour terrorism at Sachi, After 25 years of free trade was it worth it and what about that TPP, Will the real open mind stand up, Are there topics science should not study?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140225-150054-to-20140225-160028.mp3" length="56942729" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140225-150054-to-20140225-160028.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 243 - Canadian Citizenship Edition - 18-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 15:01:20 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 243 - Canadian Citizenship Edition

A rant about what a budget should be, a look at Americas first settlers, a segment of A head of the Curve warning about bad science, a look at how we became Canadian Citizens and in honour of the Olympics a classic RFT segment about doping in sports.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 243 - What wrong with the budget, who were the first First People, bias science warning, Canadian Citizenship and Classic RFT: doping in sports</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140218-150120-to-20140218-160247.mp3" length="58747088" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140218-150120-to-20140218-160247.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 242 - Whats Your Sign Edition - 11-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 15:01:22 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 242 - Whats Your Sign Edition

This week an extended look at Bill C-23 the Fair Elections Act and how it can destroy fair elections in the future.

We also take a quick look at Astrology as MacMillan Space Center hosts a Valentines event that is NOT science.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 242 - Why we should be afraid of the Fair Elections Act and a look at Astrology at Valantines</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140211-150122-to-20140211-160122.mp3" length="57321365" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140211-150122-to-20140211-160122.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 241 - Debating God Edition - 04-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 15:01:26 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 241 - Debating God Edition

Dons Rant's turned into a primer and tutorial about how to debate a charismatic christian apologist.

Having listened to a debate between an Atheist and an Apologist on the topic &quot;Is it rational to believe in god&quot;. However quickly the Apologist changed the question to &quot;What is a rational belief&quot; and then it became &quot;Can a rational person believe in god?&quot;

So, this weeks show is what are the arguments for and against god, but more importantly how do you debate rhetoric instead of facts.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 241 - How to debate a charismatic christian apologist...rhetoric over logic</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140204-150126-to-20140204-160233.mp3" length="58426415" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140204-150126-to-20140204-160233.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT - RFT - Classics - Best of the 230s - 21-Jan-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 15:05:06 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker - Classics - Best of the 230s

Dons Rant's about Harper's redefinition of Antisemitism and his twisted logic of criticizing 'apparent' moral relativism but stating moral acts must be judged relatively...you cannot condemn Israeli actions with weigh them compared to Arab/Palestinian actions.

Also from the vaults, my extended interview with Dale McGowan, author of &quot;Atheism for Dummies&quot; and executive director of Foundation Beyond Belief. We discuss that others think of atheism, the history of disbelief and the culture of atheism.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Best of the 230s - Harper's speach to the Knesset, and interview with the author of Atheism for Dummies</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140121-150506-to-20140121-160247.mp3" length="55183823" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140121-150506-to-20140121-160247.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 240 - Polar Vortex Edition - 14-Jan-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 15:01:01 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 240 - Polar Vortex Edition

Dons Rant's about the cold snap, what is a polar vortex and why this is NOT proof the climate change is bogus.

Ina new segment Moral Dilemma's, we discuss the sad case of a pregnant woman who suffered a aneurysm and is now brain dead. Now there is a legal fight between the spouse who wants to honour his dead wife's wish to not be kept alive via extraordinary means and the hospital that is legally bound to keep her on life support as long as she is pregnant. 

Which is deadlier nuclear power or fossil fuel? We first examine Fukushima 1000 days later. We compare Fukushima to Chernobyl...which was worse? and finally which is actually a greater danger to the global health - nuclear power or fossil fuel.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 240 - Climate change and the polar vortex, dilemma of a brain dead pregnant woman, Fukushima 1000 days on, Fukushima Vs. Chernobyl and which is deadlier nuclear power or fossil fuels?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140114-150101-to-20140114-160144.mp3" length="57964379" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140114-150101-to-20140114-160144.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 239 - Pope Francis Gambit Edition - 07-Jan-2014</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 15:02:14 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 239 - Pope Francis Gambit Edition

Dons Rant is all about the closure of almost all of the DFOs libraries. The contents of the libraries were either given away or tossed in the trash. Scientist complain that the government did not live up to its promise to digitize the libraries contents and that this is just another front Harper has opened on his war on science.

We also discuss the charm offensive of Time Person of the Year, Pope Francis. Does this pope spark real change or is it just a new ploy dreamt up by former Fox News reporter now head of the Vatican public relations. Is there a real Pope Frankie who has masterminded the smoke and mirrors that is Pope Francis while Pope Frankie continues the condemnation of church doctrine? Does the actions match the rhetoric? Atheist should be very afraid of this pope, the easy battles with the cartoon caricature Pope Benedict presented are gone; the church has launched a new offensive. Are we up to the challenge?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 239 - Book burning in the wake of DFO library closure and a does the Pope's word match his action...will the real pope please stand up.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140107-150214-to-20140107-160312.mp3" length="58282967" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140107-150214-to-20140107-160312.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 237 - World Federalist Movement Edition  - 17-Dec-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 15:03:27 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 237 - World Federalist Movement Edition

Don's Rant is about Affluenza, Povertiitus and how growing inequality is creating two separate legal standards. How our own Minister of Industry, can not so image what its like to help others, that he finds the idea that AS a minister and servant of the people that he may have to help those in need...when he say &quot;&quot;, he laughed as thought the idea preposterous.

We talk to Vivian Davidson from the World Federalist Movement and how they plan to transform global governance...hint - one world government + UN &quot;army&quot; + social egalitarian ethos = utopia. 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 237 - Affluenza, Povertiitus, and inequality of justice as well as what is the World Federalist Movement?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131217-150327-to-20131217-160230.mp3" length="56397710" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131217-150327-to-20131217-160230.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 236 - Pentecostal History Maker Edition  - 10-Dec-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 15:03:08 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 236 - Pentecostal History Maker Edition

Randolf Richardson returns as one of our irregular regulars. 

Don's Rant is about the impact of Nelson Mandela, how he may be the greatest person for generations and how he turned hate to love, and as he put it &quot;The oppressed and the oppressor alike are robbed of their humanity...my mission, to liberate the oppressed and the oppressor both.&quot;.

We talk to Sam Fenn and Gordon Katic who created the documentary History Maker 2013...a Pentecostal event for teenagers. We discuss the history of the church, how these events fit into the future of the church, its impact on the kids. List to find out what Sam confession is and why he may be uncomfortable. 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 236 - Mandela Mania and the documantary on History Maker 2013, what it was, who made it and what can be learned</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131210-150308-to-20131210-160304.mp3" length="57200435" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131210-150308-to-20131210-160304.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 235 - Pseudo-scientist Take-down Edition - 03-Dec-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 15:03:15 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 235 - Pseudo-scientist Take-down Edition

Randolf Richardson returns as one of our irregular regulars. 

Don's Rant is about the Harper Governments silence about the the how the American Home Land Security seem have complete access to Canadian private medical records. Is this a sign of weakness, incompetence, arrogance or is the Harper Government breaking the law by willingly sharing this information.

We discuss an exchange between Jerry Coyne and Deepak Chopra at The New Republic. Coyne does a great take-down of Pseudo-scientist paranoia, a irrelevant rebuttal by Deepak and Coynes take-down of Deepak's rebuttal. 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT- Ep 235 - Is the Harper government breaking the law by sharing private medical information with the NSA? and a great tit-er-tat between Jerry Coyne and Deepak Chopra about paranoid pseudo-scientist</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131203-150315-to-20131203-160118.mp3" length="55401080" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131203-150315-to-20131203-160118.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 234 - Doctor Who Edition - 26-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 14:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 234 - Doctor Who Edition

Host emeritus Ethan Clow returns for a look at Doctor Who, and what lessons we can learn from both the Doctor and his enemies. 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 234 - a look at Doctor Who, and what lessons we can learn from both the Doctor and his enemies</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131126-145900-to-20131126-155850.mp3" length="57116201" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131126-145900-to-20131126-155850.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 233 - Privatized Edition -  19-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 15:01:24 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 233 - Privatized Edition

Host emeritus Daniel Gipps returns for an extended look at public vs private corporations - what is public ownership? What wrong with private corporation?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 233 - An extended look at public vs private corporations - what is public ownership? What wrong with private corporation?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131119-150124-to-20131119-155800.mp3" length="54062927" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131119-150124-to-20131119-155800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 232 - The Poppy Wars Edition - 12-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 15:04:15 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 232 - The Poppy Wars Edition

Rob Ford has been big in the news, but when should private lives be left private for public figures?

Every Remembrance Day a battle occurs between the Red and the White poppy. Where did they come from, why are they both important and how to understand those who refuse to wear a red poppy.

We take a look at they hypocrisy of the Harper government attitude towards veterans. They are quick to exploit them for political points but when a vet needs help, there actively.

The role of bullying in professional sports. When Jonathan Martin exposed bullying in football, other players blamed and condemned the victim. 

The USA looses voting rights at UNESCO after 2 years of not paying its dues because UNESCO has the audacity to ignore Israel demands and accepted Palestine as a state member. UNESCO lose 1/4 of its funding in this petty move by the USA.

Also an classic interview with Tony Sabrato on the conspiratory mind.

And we end the show with a few classics from Symphony of Science.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 232 - Rob Ford and the privacy of public people, White vs Red Poppies, Harper's hypocrisy to Vets,</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131112-150415-to-20131112-160300.mp3" length="56160854" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131112-150415-to-20131112-160300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 231 - 1984 Edition - 05-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 15:03:52 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 231 - 1984 Edition

Don's Rant is about Harper's quote from the Conservative convention &quot;I couldn't care less&quot; and the pending disaster as the RCMP are called in to investigate wrong doing at the PMO's office over Duffy's cheque.

Also,the full lecture Don gave at Skepticamp Vancouver 2013 - &quot;1984 - NSA, Snowden and Spying: A Skeptic Look at the Surveillance State&quot;.

Also an classic interview with Phil Plait of Bad Astronomy fame.

And we end the show with a few classics from Symphony of Science.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 231 - Harper &quot;couldn't care less&quot;, A Skeptic Look at the Surveillance State, and a classic interview with Phil Plait</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131105-150352-to-20131105-160254.mp3" length="56431904" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131105-150352-to-20131105-160254.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 230 - Dummies Edition - 29-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 15:04:53 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 230 - Dummies Edition

Don's Rant is about how the continuing revelations from Snowden is showing how the US and Canada are spying allies. Also how much state spying is being done for corporate benefit. Lastly, how this spying is causing a race to the bottom of unethical spying

Also an extended interview with Dale McGowan, author of &quot;Atheism for Dummies&quot; and executive director of Foundation Beyond Belief. We discuss that others think of atheism, the history of disbelief and the culture of atheism.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 230 - A rant about the race to the bottom in 'ethical' spying and an interview with the author of Atheism for Dummies</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131029-150453-to-20131029-160235.mp3" length="55161305" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131029-150453-to-20131029-160235.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 229 - Skeptic Music Edition - 22-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 229 - Skeptic Music Edition

Don's Rant is about how thanks to the Senate scandal, nomination shenanigans in BrandonSouris and an thrown speak which didn't mention accountability...the Conservatives are risking looking there political base in the same way the PC's did in the 90s.

Also more evidence the Pope may be a closet Atheist when he claims that the church is plagued by &quot;ideology&quot; minded Christians who have, as he put it &quot;lost the faith&quot;.

Research is in on the Zamboni treatment for MS, and it looks like it does nothing...making the rash actions of Zamboni to treat people before his claims could be proven makes he a dangerous quack!

Also we take a relaxed moment and enjoy some skeptical music largely thanks to Symphony of Science.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 229 - Rant about Conservatives losing their base, more of the Pope as closeted atheist, Zamboni treat found failing and much skeptic music</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131022-150000-to-20131022-160000.mp3" length="57355142" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131022-150000-to-20131022-160000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 225 - Economic Science Edition - 15-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 15:04:34 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 225 - Economic Science Edition

Don's Rant is about Quebec Charter Of ValuesAnti immigrant policy implement for political gain, with luck it will backfire.

This week returning to the show, host emeritus Daniel Gipps. We discuss whether economics is or is not a science. What qualifies as science? Is it possible for economics to have a hard science foundation? And what lessons can be learned from Stalinist Russia and Nazi Germany?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 225 - Quebec Charter Of Values and economics - science or fiction?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131015-150434-to-20131015-160138.mp3" length="55418594" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131015-150434-to-20131015-160138.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 228 - Debating Islam Edition - 08-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 15:01:30 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 228 - Debating Islam Edition

Don's Rant about how political micro-targeting has turned citizens into a commodity to be bought like we would chips. Politicians are not longer listening to the electorate about what government should be/do but instead are marketing their parties like you would a car. It's telling people to BY Harper (for example) and not 'we hear you and will do you bidding'.

Also, How to debate a Muslim and not be a racist. We live in culture that has equate Islam with terrorism...a religious faith with a racist identity. This has happened because popular media promotes this view.

We provide a primer on the origins of Islam, its beliefs, it's sects and the rise of the Islamic Empire.
We also follow the major arguments for faith and debunk them.

Special thanks to Randolf Richardson from Atheist Frontier from joining in on the show.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 228 - Microtargetting is runing democracy and a primer on Islam plus how to debunk the Muslim arguments</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131008-150130-to-20131008-160142.mp3" length="57549464" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131008-150130-to-20131008-160142.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 227 - Mega Vitamins Edition - 01-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 15:03:30 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 227 - Mega Vitamins Edition

Don's Rant is about the death of Canadian technology giant Black Berry and how the icons of Canada are disappearing. 

Mega vitamins may not only be a waste of money but a strong cause of cancer and heart deceases.

Should we boycott the Sochi Olympics? What are the alternative?

And we have a chat with host emeritus Ethan Clow about GTA-V, how TV villains are now the guys we root for and moving to mars.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 227 - Death of Canadian Tech Giants and the myth of Mega Dosing</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131001-150330-to-20131001-160253.mp3" length="56628311" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131001-150330-to-20131001-160253.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 226 - Free Thinkers Club Edition - 24-Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2013 15:08:19 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 226 - Free Thinkers Club Edition

&lt;apologizes for the poor quality of this show, a better version is available on our website&gt;

Don's Rant about Pope Francis...based on recent comments, could the pope be a closeted atheist? Or maybe the first communist pope? 

We also have an interview with Pratyush Dhawan and Darren Bell from the UBC Free Thinkers Club. We discuss atheism, skepticism, humanism, and just what is &quot;free thinking&quot;.

We also discuss 'natural spiritualism', humanity becoming an inter-stellar species, and the moral landscape.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 226 - Rant: is the pope a closet athiest? and a discussion with the Prez and VP of UBC Free Thinkers Club</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130924-150819-to-20130924-160458.mp3" length="54149246" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130924-150819-to-20130924-160458.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 224 - Carl Saga Association Edition - 10-Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 15:02:39 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 224 - Carl Saga Association Edition

We start with Don's Rant about Frosh Chant...HOW could any one think the &quot;no-consent&quot; was legal...let along appropriate. It leaves you just gobsmacked. 

We also have an interview with Jason Fernando from the Carl Sagan Association for the Communication of Science. Who is Carl Sagan, why an Association and just how do the plan to communicate about science and more specifically to science community.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 224 - Rant about Frosh Chant and Jason Fernando from the Carl Sagan Association for the Communication of Science.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130910-150239-to-20130910-160239.mp3" length="57210443" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130910-150239-to-20130910-160239.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 223 - Atheist Identity Edition - 03-Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 15:04:22 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 223 - Atheist Identity Edition

We start with Don's Rant about Syria, Chemical weapons, crimes against humanity, The UN's Responsibility to Protect, Russia intransigence, and how the US's history has come to haunt the world. 

We also have an intensive discussion about is there an atheist identity, what does that mean and should we embrace it or run for the hills. Also, are Atheist moral and how does an Atheist parent frame teaching ethics to their children?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep 223 - An extended discussion with Randolph Richardson from Atheist Frontier about 'the atheist identity;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130903-150422-to-20130903-160210.mp3" length="55249292" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130903-150422-to-20130903-160210.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 222 - Thats Funny Edition - 27-Aug-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 15:33:11 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 222 - Thats Funny Edition

This week an extended interview with local funny man Hamoon Efdis. We talk about the health effects of laughter, the origins of humour, the first recorded jokes and how Jokes have evolved over time. Are there words that should never be used, even in a joke? Are there topics that are out of bounds for comics? What is offensive? What is obscene? How are these the same/different and what role does it play in comedy?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep.222 - Exit interview with local funny man, Hamoon Efdis.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130827-153311-to-20130827-163249.mp3" length="56901029" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130827-153311-to-20130827-163249.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 221 - Leaving Skepticism Edition - 13-Aug-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 15:31:28 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 221 - Leaving Skepticism Edition

This week
Radio Free Thinker 2.0, an hour long exit interview with host emeritus Ethan Clow about how he started into skepticism and why he is leaving it.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep.221 - Exit interview with host emeritus Ethan Clow</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130813-153128-to-20130813-163128.mp3" length="57358061" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130813-153128-to-20130813-163128.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT- Best of the 200s - 30-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT- Best of the 200s

This week:

Library and Archives of Canada are ask to swear loyalty to the government of Canada and not to Canada itself
With the recent arrival of Pandas to Toronto, we discuss pandas, panda politics and what did Harper do to change China's mind.
Suing for information - how Canada's Information Commissioner is pushing back on Harper's muzzling of our government , and
The Parliamentary Budget Office and why its important for democracy.

A pure version is available on our website: 
http://radiofreethinker.com/listen-now/


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT- Best of the 200s - Loyalty oaths for Librarians, Panda Politics, UN-Access to information, and PBO for democracy</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130730-153000-to-20130730-163344.mp3" length="60911318" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130730-153000-to-20130730-163344.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 220 - UK Porn Ban  Edition - 23-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 15:30:23 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 220 - UK Porn Ban  Edition

This week
- Cosmos rebirth - Sagan's classic show has a reboot
- Norse Myth fact check - Orwell as seen in Viking mythology
- Who murdered Mars? - a look at explanations that don't make sense, and
- The UK to ban Pornright! - Britain put forward a plan to filter out all porn traffic.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep.220 - Cosmos rebirth, Norse Myth fact check, Who murdered Mars?, and the UK to ban Pornright!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130723-153023-to-20130723-162908.mp3" length="56183789" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130723-153023-to-20130723-162908.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 219 - Not So Ancient Wisdom  Edition - 16-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 15:30:10 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT - Ep.219 - Not So Ancient Wisdom  Edition

This week
- TRex is bad ass again -We delve into the debate, was TRex predator or scavenger, 
- The View anti-vax fail - The View hires anti-promoter Jenny McCarthy, &lt;due to technical issues, this segment is unavailable&gt;
- Atheist types - Just what kind of atheist are you?,
And
- Not so ancient wisdom - Just how ancient are those ancient wisdoms?.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep.219 - TRex is bad ass again, The View anti-vax fail, Athiest types and Not so ancient wisdom</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130716-153010-to-20130716-163036.mp3" length="57818429" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130716-153010-to-20130716-163036.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 218 - Bench Clearing Edition - 09-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2013 15:29:25 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 218 - Bench Clearing Edition

This week
- We discuss Bill C-266 - An Act to establish Pope John Paul II Day in Canada, 
- Don talks about &quot;Irished Water&quot; - Should the state medicate the entire population to reduce depression and suicide?, 
- We talk about the science of the Saints - academic myth busting of Mother Teresa,
And
- Ethan tackles the questions: Does hockey need violence? Could we remove it? Do we want to?.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT - Ep.218 - Pope Day, Irished water, science of saints and does hockey need violence?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130709-152925-to-20130709-163058.mp3" length="58818812" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130709-152925-to-20130709-163058.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 217 - Post Canada Day Edition - 02-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 15:30:10 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 217 - Post Canada Day Edition

This week we why the mythology around our flags maple leaf, 
We talk about how politically driven drug laws are censoring science, 
Atheist erect the first of many 'town hall' monuments to atheism...much to the protest of the godly,
And
We exam a trio of food stories that show the wide range of reporting and how one story will become the seed for others.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT Ep.217 - Myths of the Maple leaf, Schedule 1 drugs, Atheist monument and Food reporting - ugly, good and sarcastic</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130702-153010-to-20130702-163149.mp3" length="58938491" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130702-153010-to-20130702-163149.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 216 - Goodbye Gandolfini Edition - 25-Jun-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 15:32:17 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 216 - Goodbye Gandolfini Edition

This week we discuss the global memorials to the death of James Gandolfini. 
Dolphin Woo - the bad science behind Dolphin Assisted Treatment, 
Anti science left - we review a few of the bad anti-science news stories from the left - GMO food, Nuclear Power, Energy risks,
Museum fail - UK museum hints 4000 yr old spirits are moving statues around,
And
We do fun flashback and look at the pre-internet conspiracy about the 'alleged' death of Paul McCartney of the Beatles back in 1966.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 216 - Gandolfini's death, Dolphin Woo, Anti-science lefties, Museum fail and Is McCartney dead?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130625-153217-to-20130625-163012.mp3" length="55362299" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130625-153217-to-20130625-163012.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 215 - Bad Big Data Edition - 18-Jun-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 15:31:21 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 215 - Bad Big Data Edition

This week we discuss the latest blunder by CFI Transnational as Rebecca Watson, Greta Christina, and other leading women skeptics cut their ties to CFI-T,
Ethan explains that CFI Canada has not ties/connections (beyond a shared name) with CFI Transnational,
And
Don takes an extended look at the dark sides of big data and what you need to know and why its important to everyone.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 215 - CFI female troubles, CFI Canada is NOT CFI Transnational and the dark side of big data</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130618-153121-to-20130618-163104.mp3" length="57085760" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130618-153121-to-20130618-163104.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 214 - The Good of Big Data Edition - 11-Jun-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 15:30:49 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 214 - The Good of Big Data Edition

This week historical precedent for the Red Wedding on Game of Thrones,
New research shows a global divide on the acceptance of homosexuality,
We reports on a study that shows atheist gain solus from science in times of stress and existential anxiety,
And
We look at the good Big Data has brought into our lives,

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 214 - the red wedding, gay around the world, faith in science and the good of big data</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130611-153049-to-20130611-163158.mp3" length="58458524" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130611-153049-to-20130611-163158.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 213 - Drone Strike Edition - 04-Jun-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 15:30:26 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 213 - Drone Strike Edition

This week Micheal Douglas blames oral sex for his cancer...was he right?
Humanist report - In praise of Morgentaler
We reports on the use of super-computers to discover HIV's protein secrets,
And
We look at drones or semi-autonomous aerial military vehicles,

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 213 - Oral sex and cancer, Humanist Report- obit for Morgentaler, Super-computing HIV, and Drone war  Good or bad?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130604-153026-to-20130604-163139.mp3" length="58523576" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130604-153026-to-20130604-163139.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 212 - Election Fraud Edition - 28-May-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 15:29:58 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 212 - Election Fraud Edition

This week A look at Volkswagen - Hitlers one good thing?
We look at early evidence the ending fluoridation in Calgary is leading to a rise in tooth decay.
We reports on Ottawa's Health boards decision to expel the un-vaccinated,
We tackles some of fallacies of the anti-GMO movement, and discuss better reasons to hate Monsanto,
And
In the light of a courts ruling confirming election fraud in the Robocall scandal, Don explores the ruling and the role of the Conservative party in this and other scandals threatening democracy.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 212 - Anti-floride rot, Anti-Vaxers expelled, Anti-GMO exposed and Anti-Democratic Fruad</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130528-152958-to-20130528-163044.mp3" length="58070714" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130528-152958-to-20130528-163044.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 211 - Election Autopsy Edition - 21-May-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 15:30:28 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 211 - Election Autopsy Edition

This week a salute to Chris Hadfield for showing astronauts can be great PR agents for science and space, A look at the past election and how the pollsters and pundits could get it so wrong, Senate Shenanigans - can you fire a senator and you'll hate your self for not going to Imagine No Religion 3 - Ethan give a review of what happened.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 211 - Hadfield promotes space science, post-election autopsy, can you fire a senator? and a review of Imagine No Religion 3</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130521-153028-to-20130521-162746.mp3" length="54793511" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130521-153028-to-20130521-162746.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 210 - Election Issues Edition - 07-May-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 15:30:53 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 210 - Election Issues Edition

This week Quitting skepticism, Super languages, and The big Election Issues

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 210 - Quitting skepticism, Super languages, and The big Election Issues</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130507-153053-to-20130507-163142.mp3" length="58141187" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130507-153053-to-20130507-163142.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 209 - BC Beliefs Edition - 30-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 15:30:16 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 209 - BC Beliefs Edition
This week 

- Anti-fluoridation conspiracist attack Portland

- Does a state-religion actually promote atheism?

- The Humanist Report - Ian talks about the results of the Humanist Association poll about BC's beliefs

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 209 - Rubber ducking fluoridation, state religion and atheism and The Humanist Report - Polling BC's Beliefs</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130430-153016-to-20130430-163144.mp3" length="58763768" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130430-153016-to-20130430-163144.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 208 - Boston Bomb Edition - 23-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 15:31:31 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 208 - Boston Bomb Edition

This week 

- We discuss MP Reid's weird but compelling attack against blasphemy laws.

- Do you need to be a skeptic to be an atheist? Are all atheist skeptics? Don argues to be a 'good' skeptic you will be a atheist and if your a 'good' atheist you need to be a skeptic.

- In the aftermath of the Boston Marathon Bombing, a number of issues came to mind - what separates crime from terrorism, Is WMD meaningless now, power-creep and comparing today's word to that of 20 years ago.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 208 - Reid and religion, The Scottish Atheist, and Issues of the Boston Bombing</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130423-153131-to-20130423-163003.mp3" length="55953188" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130423-153131-to-20130423-163003.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 207  Digital Rights Edition - 16-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 15:30:10 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 207  Digital Rights Edition

This week 

- We talk about a spectacularly bizarre and time disturbing  poll from the USA showing, for example, how many people voted Obama believe he WAS the Antichrist.

- Canada's first Parliamentary Budget Officer has recently stepped down. It is likely that his office will be &quot;wound down&quot; because it proved to be too embarrassing for the Harper Government. We discuss what it did, why it did it and  why you should care.

- EA used Digital Rights Management (DRM) to ensure no one pirated its new SimCity game resulting in a horrible PR disaster. HBO felt proud that Game of Thrones was the most pirated TV show in history. We discuss the issue of DRM

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 207  Crazy Polling, PBO and you, and Digital Media Rights and wrongs</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130416-153010-to-20130416-162857.mp3" length="56215898" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130416-153010-to-20130416-162857.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 206  Election Quiz Edition - 09-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 15:29:37 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 206  Election Quiz Edition

This week 

- We talk about the passing of progressive, skeptic and complicated &quot;unbeliever catholic&quot; Roger Ebert.

- In the them of Harper's war on science and democracy, we discuss Canada's Information Commissioner efforts to investigate how the Access To Information Law is being abused and ignored by this government including suing the DOD over a 1100 day 'extension' for a report by law that should be produced in 30 days..

- The Humanist Report - Ian joins Don to talk about Atheist churches, the upcoming BC election and a quiz distributed by the BC Humanist Association to pin down the views of the candidates.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 206  Goodbye Roger, Suing for information and The Humanist Report - Election Quiz</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130409-152937-to-20130409-163143.mp3" length="59348819" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130409-152937-to-20130409-163143.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 205  Nuking Korea Edition - 02-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 15:30:31 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 205  Nuking Korea Edition

This week we discover the real Gates of Hell...who'd a thunk it was in...listen to find out where.
Salon posts a hatched job to equate Dawkins with radical Islamaphobist...listen to see how you separate the genuine from the dishonest criticisms.
Ethan explores the really real origins of Easter...kinda and
With all the talk in the news about the pending nuclear war in Korea, Don takes a factual look at the peninsula's history, North Korea and what really could happen.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 205  Gates of Hell, Dawkins islamiphobic?, the real origin of Easter and an assessment of war in the Koreas</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130402-153031-to-20130402-163212.mp3" length="58970600" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130402-153031-to-20130402-163212.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 204  Panda Politics Edition - 26-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 15:30:02 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 204  Panda Politics Edition

This week we discover the Pope Frankie may be like the old pope and complicit in 'hiding' pedophilic priest, A creationist is offering $10,000 for anyone who can disprove Young Earth Literal Creationism, Library and Archives of Canada are ask to swear loyalty to the government of Canada and not to Canada itself, and with the recent arrival of Pandas to Toronto, we discuss pandas, panda politics and what did Harper do to change China's mind.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 204  New Pope old pedo problems, $10000 creationist challenge,Silence of the Librarians, and Pandas Politics</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130326-153002-to-20130326-163121.mp3" length="58619903" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130326-153002-to-20130326-163121.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 203  Who Killed JC Edition - 19-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 15:29:28 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 203  Who Killed JC Edition

This week we discuss who killed Julius Caesar and what does &quot;ides&quot; mean in the Ides of March, new research shows that active criminals use theology to enable/excuse/validate their criminal activities, Pope Francis has old baggage and an impossible job, and we talk about how atheists and non-believers deserve explicit designation in the UN (and else where) declaration of freedom.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 203  The ides of March, Faith and crime, New pope old problems and Atheist vs religious freedom</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130319-152928-to-20130319-162954.mp3" length="57773393" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130319-152928-to-20130319-162954.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 202  Stompin' Tom Edition - 12-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 15:34:46 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 202  Stompin' Tom Edition

This week we pay tribute to a great Canadian Stompin' Tom Connors, Don makes his case why Vaccine Awareness Network (VAN) or the Anti-Vax-ers should be censored, Ethan reviews his media encounters regarding the Anti-Vax-ers, and we talk about the new phenomena of Atheist Churches.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 202  Goodbye Stompin' Tom, censoring Anti-Vax-ers, Media coverage of Anti-Vax-ers, and Atheist Churches</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130312-153446-to-20130312-162920.mp3" length="52177670" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130312-153446-to-20130312-162920.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Fundrive Special Broadcast on 05-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate><description></description><itunes:subtitle>Donate to CiTR and help support our show!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130305-153000-to-20130305-163000.mp3" length="57336794" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130305-153000-to-20130305-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 201  Magdalene Laundry Edition - 26-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 15:30:24 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 201  Magdalene Laundry Edition

This week we discuss the Oscars, praise and criticism of Seth MacFarlane, the movie Argo rewriting history, Catholic silence on the Magdalene Laundry scandal and we reply to some listener feedback on free-will clarification.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 201  a review of the Oscars, the skeptic side of Family Guy, Argo fiction,  Magdalene Laundry, and Freewill clarification</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130226-153024-to-20130226-163141.mp3" length="58587794" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130226-153024-to-20130226-163141.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 200  The Fecken 200th Edition - 19-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 15:31:56 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 200  The Fecken 200th Edition

This week we discuss the space attack on Russia by an unknown meteor, Italian authorizes seize part of the Vatican bank as part of a money laundering investigation, Canada's new Office for Religious Freedom leave out atheists and we reply to some listener feedback on gun control.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 200  Meteor shakes Russia, Vatican Bank Money Laundering, No freedom for atheist, and Gun Control feedback</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130219-153156-to-20130219-163140.mp3" length="57100772" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130219-153156-to-20130219-163140.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 199  Non-Secular Liberal Edition - 12-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 15:32:14 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 199  Non-Secular Liberal Edition

This week we discuss the possible risks of a close flyby of asteroid 2012DA14 - the first apocalypse story of 2013, a win for science based medicine as Ottawa cancer charity drops anti-vax-er Jenny McCarthy from event, CIDA has given half a million dollars to an anti-gay charity to do work in Uganda, The  Pope quiets, why? and the sad story of BC Premier Christy Clark view of the bible and faith in politics..

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 199  First Apocalypse 2013, Cancer charity win McCarthy loss, CIDA supports anti-gay charity, The Pope quits, and Christy Clark and the state of BC secular state</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130212-153214-to-20130212-163117.mp3" length="56447750" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130212-153214-to-20130212-163117.mp3</guid></item><item><title>RFT Classics - Best of the 180s - Sketpicly focused Edition - 05-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2013 15:31:32 -0800</pubDate><description>RFT Classics - Best of the 180s - Sketpicly focused Edition 

Its a best of Radio Free Thinker show. Today we revisit some of the best bits from past shows.

This episode: Cellular Memory - the skeptical bubble - are we preaching to the 'chour' and missing the 'less' informed?; We take a moment and try to define what the terms used in the 'skeptic' community mean so that people engaging (at least RFT) will have a common understanding of what we are talking about and What up with the skeptical movement? - Should we continue to attempt to educate the ignorant (both senses of the term) or cut them a drift as lost causes

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT Classics - Best of the 180s - The Skeptic Bubble, The -isms of SKepticism and Skepticism moving forward</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130205-153132-to-20130205-163136.mp3" length="57422279" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130205-153132-to-20130205-163136.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 198  Cost of Casinos Edition - 29-Jan-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 15:31:34 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 198  Cost of Casinos Edition

This week we discuss the turmoil in Mali and what is has to do with Canada, did someone record the sounds of Big Foot, Canada RePoopUlator, and what are the costs and benefits of casinos.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 198  Mali malady, Shriek of the Big Foot, The RePoopUlator, and the cost of casinos</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130129-153134-to-20130129-163204.mp3" length="57833858" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130129-153134-to-20130129-163204.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 197  Lancing Armstrong Edition - 22-Jan-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 15:30:53 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 197  Lancing Armstrong Edition

This week we discuss the genisis of a new conspiracy theory - the Sandy Hook Truthers, De-extinction - a Neanderthalian indecent proposal, Was the earth hit by a gamaray burst 1300 years ago?, the Doh! Of Doha and Lance Armstrong and professional doping

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 197  Sandy Hook Truthers, De-extinction, Earth Bursts a Gamaray, the Doh! Of Doha and Lance Armstrong and professional doping</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130122-153053-to-20130122-163050.mp3" length="57309689" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130122-153053-to-20130122-163050.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 196  Goodbye Arron Edition - 15-Jan-2013</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 15:32:24 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 196  goodbye Arron Edition

This week we discuss the possible role the element lead to decreased violence, Calgary's Flaming Flu controversy, Eulogy for Aaron Swartz, and Sam Harris shots himself...again.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 196  Lead violence, Calgary's Flaming Flu controversy, Eulogy for Aaron Swartz, and Sam Harris shots himself...again</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130115-153224-to-20130115-162735.mp3" length="52766891" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130115-153224-to-20130115-162735.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 193  Solemnized Edition - 11-Dec-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 193  Solemnized Edition

This week the Real Noahs Ark, Repressive blasphemy law, Beyond Secularism in Chilliwack, and an interview with CFI Indiana about the right to solemnize weddings.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 193  the Real Noahs Ark, Repressive blasphemy law, Beyond Secularism in Chilliwack, and seculare solemnized weddings</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121211-153000-to-20121211-162640.mp3" length="54165509" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121211-153000-to-20121211-162640.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 192  Certified Organic Edition - 04-Dec-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 15:31:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 192  Certified Organic Edition

This week we discuss how climate change is threatening another culinary staple - the truffle, Ethan give a historians review of the movie Lincoln, Germany makes zoophilia illegal, and A look at the law and what makes organic food Organic.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 192  End of Truffles, Lincoln movie review, Zoophilia, and What makes organic Organic?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121204-153100-to-20121204-162952.mp3" length="56294711" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121204-153100-to-20121204-162952.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 191  Chicken Soup Edition - 27-Nov-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 15:32:57 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 191  Chicken Soup Edition

This week we discuss plans the USA had to nuke the moon, an update of the effort to stop bible distribution at schools, climate change threatens the end of shellfish, and the mythology of Chicken soup.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 191  Nuking the moon, Gideon Bible update, the end of shellfish and the mythology of Chicken soup</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121127-153257-to-20121127-162858.mp3" length="53565029" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121127-153257-to-20121127-162858.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 190  Killer Energy Shot Edition - 20-Nov-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 15:30:20 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 190  Killer Energy Shot Edition

This week we discuss women's issues in the secular movement, Ireland's 'pro-life' laws kill, rogue planet found, and killer energy drinks - is caffeine toxic?.

Special Bonus: Stephanie Van Dyk, UBC's FreeThinker Club president, sits in as a guest Thinker.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 190  women and the secular, 'pro-life' kills, rogue planet, and killer energy drinks</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121120-153020-to-20121120-162849.mp3" length="55925666" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121120-153020-to-20121120-162849.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker - Ep. 189 - End of Coffee Edition of Radio Free  Thinker - 13-Nov-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 15:31:19 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker - Ep. 189 - End of Coffee Edition of Radio Free 
Thinker

This week we discuss the extinction of coffee, Elephant talk, Tyson find Kryton, autism and the flu and doctor's reaction to the mandatory flu vaccine.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker - Ep. 189 - extinction of coffee, Elephant talk, Tyson find Kryton, autism and the flu and doctor's reaction to the mandatory flu vaccine.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121113-153119-to-20121113-163105.mp3" length="57134549" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121113-153119-to-20121113-163105.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 188  Talking Elaphant Edition - 06-Nov-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 15:28:51 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 188  Talking Elaphant Edition

This week we discuss how much fun we had at SkeptiCamp Fall 2012, the 100 interstellar space ship project, the controversy over the anthropocene, and the legal status of security guards.

We missed the talking elephant segment, but hope to include it on the next show.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 188  Skepticamp 2012, 100 yr spaceship, the Anthropocene, and the Rent-a-cop dilemma</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121106-152851-to-20121106-162903.mp3" length="57549464" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121106-152851-to-20121106-162903.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 187  Zombie Free Will Edition - 30-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 15:32:34 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 187  Zombie Free Will Edition

This week we discuss Gideons in your school, Atheist solemnize marriage, More ramifications from dropping long form census, Vaccine recall, Scary music, Zombie Planet...NOT!, and The illusion of Free Will and Sam Harris.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 187  Gideons in your school, Atheist solemnize marriage, More census change ramifications, Vaccine recall, Scary music, Zombie Planet, and Sam Harris on Free Will</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121030-153234-to-20121030-163240.mp3" length="57460643" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121030-153234-to-20121030-163240.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 186  Cellular Memory Edition - 23-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 186  Cellular Memory Edition

This week we discuss bad-art thieves, goodbye Paul Kurtz, scientist convicted for earthquake, and cellular memory - the skeptical bubble.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT-Ep186bad-art thieves, goodbye Paul Kurtz, scientist convicted for earthquake, and cellular memory - the skeptical bubble</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121023-153000-to-20121023-163007.mp3" length="57439376" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121023-153000-to-20121023-163007.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 185  Dino's are dead forever Edition 16-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2012 15:31:14 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 185  Dino's are dead forever Edition

This week we discuss signs of evidence based legislation, dishonest scientific papers, why jurassic park is impossible, unhealthy myths about Medicare, and Are we losing the anti-vax war..

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>RFT Ep 185  Suicide fallout, dishonest science papers, mission jurassic impossible, unhealthy Medicare myths, and the Anti-vax war</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121016-153114-to-20121016-162547.mp3" length="52105112" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121016-153114-to-20121016-162547.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 184  Free Speech Hypocrisy Edition  09-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 15:32:20 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 184  Free Speech Hypocrisy Edition

This week government budget cutting comes home to roost as Canada food safety agencies fail to adequately protect our beef supply . Stats Canada is released information showing its future reports may reflect inaccuracies due to low rates of reporting from rural, minority and disadvantages communities as result of switching the census from mandatory to voluntary. Ethan takes us on a hypothetical look that potential controversy over religious accommodation in Quebec when one councillor was accused of anti-Semitism for daring to suggest city council work on the night of Yom Kippur. We discuss an article in published on Slate.com which took a binary look at the recent uproar over a YouTube video, Don promotes a more nuanced response for making a distinction between hate and free speech.  New research vindicates flu vaccines that had been liked to increased rates of narcolepsy in Scandinavia. Based on work done in China, it seems narcolepsy is linked with the flu and not the flu vaccine  correlation vs causation, and our review of the 2012 Ig Nobel prizes.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 184  Poor data from voluntary census, Funding cuts and beef recall, the almost Montreal Yom Kippur controversy, Hate vs Free speech  hypocrisy in action?, Narcolepsy cause -  the Flu or the vaccine, and Our review of this year</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121009-153220-to-20121009-162937.mp3" length="54771410" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121009-153220-to-20121009-162937.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 183  Islamic Bomb Edition  25-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 15:33:50 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 183  Islamic Bomb Edition

This week parents prayed as their son does from extremely painful appendicitis and only get put on probation, Is Iran really building a nuclear bomb?, Pew study shows religious tolerance declining as governments turn to legislating god, and history and myths around the Black Death.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 183 Prayed to death, Iran and the Bomb, Religious intolerance on the rise, and The Black Death.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120925-153350-to-20120925-163008.mp3" length="53826071" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120925-153350-to-20120925-163008.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 182  Innocence of YouTube Edition - 18-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 15:29:37 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 182  Innocence of YouTube Edition 

This week The Innocents of Muslims controversy takes an odd twist, Framing Blasphemy in Pakistan  religion or petty retribution?, The Lesula monkey is welcome to the family, Parking Richard the 3rd -  Real discover or more pseudo-hype, Recast of the bad investment of Fare-gates, and Fare-gates impact..

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 182  Innocence and Islam, Lesula Monkey, A lot for Richard the 3rd, recast of Fare-Gate folly and Impact of Fare-Gate</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120918-152937-to-20120918-163430.mp3" length="62018453" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120918-152937-to-20120918-163430.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 181 - Science Strikes Back Edition 11-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 15:43:18 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 181 - Science Strikes Back Edition

This week Canada Cuts Diplomatic Ties to Iran, Organic Shmorganic, Korean Science strikes back, and Interview with Desiree Schell from Sceptically Speaking.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 181 - Cutting off Iran, Organic fail, Korean Win and Desiree Schell</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120911-154318-to-20120911-163800.mp3" length="52304855" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120911-154318-to-20120911-163800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 180 - Skeptical Waves Edition 04-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 15:31:45 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 180 - Skeptical Waves Edition

This week we have we discuss the passing of Neil Armstrong, we discuss a article claims a causal link between climate change and particular weather events, Don helps clear the rhetorical air by providing some common definition of the 'ism's and What up with A+ and the skeptical movement? Is Skepticism facing a schism? Is A+ exclusionary or divisive?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 180 - Goodbye to Armstrong, Causality and Climate Change, Defining the -isms and What up with A+ and the skeptical movement?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120904-153145-to-20120904-163609.mp3" length="61568927" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120904-153145-to-20120904-163609.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers - Best of the 170s - 28-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers - Best of the 170s

Its a best of Radio Free Thinker show. Today we revisit some of the best bits from past shows.

This episode: Fear-mongers exaggerate the risks of radiation in our food; Are all atheist good skeptics? We discover 5 who seem to fail and Alternative Medicine aint just for people - we explore homeopathy and other quack medicine inflicted on our pets

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers - Best of the 170s - Nuclear Fish invade West Coast, 5 Awful Atheist, and Who's quacking Fido</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120828-153119-to-20120828-163050.mp3" length="56893940" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120828-153119-to-20120828-163050.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 179 - Bad Science Watch Edition  21-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 15:32:16 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 179  Bad Science Watch Edition

This week we have we discuss what is political asylum, an egg-travagant myth about cake mixes, the on-again off-again sex affair with Neanderthals and interview with Bad Science Watch executive director Jamie Williams

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 179  Political Asylum, Egg-travant cake mix myth, the on-again off-again sex affair with Neanderthals and interview with BC Humanist executive director Ian Bushfield</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120821-153216-to-20120821-163245.mp3" length="60392570" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120821-153216-to-20120821-163245.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Humanist Agenda Edition - 14-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 15:30:37 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Humanist Agenda Edition

This week we have an extend interview with BC Humanist Association executive director Ian Bushfield. We discuss what is humanism, religion and Christi Clark, a secular charter, the US election and much much more....

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Extended interview with BC Humanist executive director Ian Bushfield</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120814-153037-to-20120814-162956.mp3" length="56725472" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120814-153037-to-20120814-162956.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Humanist Agenda Edition - 14-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 15:30:37 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Humanist Agenda Edition

This week we have an extend interview with BC Humanist Association executive director Ian Bushfield. We discuss what is humanism, religion and Christi Clark, a secular charter, the US election and much much more....

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Extended interview with BC Humanist executive director Ian Bushfield</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120814-153037-to-20120814-162956.mp3" length="56725472" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120814-153037-to-20120814-162956.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Humanist Agenda Edition - 14-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Humanist Agenda Edition

This week we have an extend interview with BC Humanist Association executive director Ian Bushfield. We discuss what is humanism, religion and Christi Clark, a secular charter, the US election and much much more....

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 178 - Extended interview with BC Humanist executive director Ian Bushfield</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120814-153000-to-20120814-163000.mp3" length="57335960" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120814-153000-to-20120814-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 177 - Back on Mars Edition - 07-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 15:38:01 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 177 - Back on Mars Edition

This week we discuss the landing of the Mars Curiosity lander  how it landed and what it will do while there, we review a recent article lists the 5 worst atheist  you might be surprised where we stand on this one, and Alternative medicine is not limited to humans; we discuss the state of alt-med for your pet and the ethical implications for pet owners.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 177 - Curiosity lands on Mars, Awful Atheist, and Quack Medicine for your pet</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120807-153801-to-20120807-163520.mp3" length="55724672" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120807-153801-to-20120807-163520.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker Episode 176 - Olympic Cyborg Edition -  31-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 15:31:44 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinker Episode 176 - Olympic Cyborg Edition

This week we discuss the first disabled athlete to compete in the regular Olympics, The possibility of the Olympics being ground zero in a anti-vax triggered pandemic, We discuss political protest, economic tension and religious oppression at the Olympics, and We explore the ramifications of The Alberta Ministry of Health elevating the Collage of Naturpaths to the same status as the College of Physician 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Episode 176 - Olympic Cyborg Sprinter, Possible Olympic Pandemic, Poliitcs-Economics-Religion at the Olympics and Naturopaths in Alberta</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120731-153144-to-20120731-163153.mp3" length="57501926" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120731-153144-to-20120731-163153.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 175 - Nuclear Salmon Edition -  24-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 15:32:29 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 175 - Nuclear Salmon Edition

This week we discuss news reports how Airport securitys porno twist, Nuclear Salmon of the West cost?, Drones stop Polio Eradication, Rocket Launchers new target at Olympics and Whats Ethans problem with the War of 1812?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft

Radio FreeThinkers Episode 175 - security porn, rocker toss at the Olympics, drones shoot down polio vaccination, and Ethan's 1812 ire.</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 175 - Security porn, rocket launcher Olympic event, drone stops polio vaccination, and Ethan's 1812 ire.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120724-153229-to-20120724-162850.mp3" length="53847338" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120724-153229-to-20120724-162850.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers - Best of the 160s - 17-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 15:32:46 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers - Best of the 160s

Its a best of Radio Free Thinker show. Today we revisit some of the best bits from past shows.

This episode: Fare-ness of Translink: Should mass transit be free for all?; Narconon - Scientology on Drugs: Recruiting from societies most vulnerable and Jane the Ripper: who committed the White Chapel Murders?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers - Best of the 160s - Fare-ness of Translink, Narconon - Scientology on drugs and Jane the Ripper</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120717-153246-to-20120717-163745.mp3" length="62091845" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120717-153246-to-20120717-163745.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 174 - Burning Fat Edition - 10-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 15:31:42 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 174 - Burning Fat Edition


This week we take a skeptical look at drug testing at the London Olympics, Dis-education - why would parent want their children to be intellectually retarded?, and and interview with author Edward Falzon, author of &quot;Being Gay is disgusting or Goes likes the smell of burning fat&quot;.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 174 - Doping the Olympics. Dis-education - Why do it? and an inteview with Edward Falzon</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120710-153142-to-20120710-163200.mp3" length="57643706" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120710-153142-to-20120710-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 173 - Dis-education Edition - 03-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 15:30:36 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 173 - Dis-education Edition

This week we talk about how corporal punishment of children is correlated with psychological aliments later in life, why standardized tests should not be the sole judge of effective  education, and dis-educating children - 
A look at the Accelerated Christian Educations curriculum and crazy stuff they teach.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 173 - hitting kids crazy, more than standard testing, and dis-educating children</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120703-153036-to-20120703-163049.mp3" length="57564476" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120703-153036-to-20120703-163049.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 172 - Avro Arrow Edition - 26-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 15:30:30 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 172 - Avro Arrow Edition

This week we talk about Pope sees female ordination equivalent to paedophilia, Roman remains in 5th century Japan - Aliens?, super human mutants, killer grass and
who killed the Avro Arrow? Pick your conspiracy.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 172 - Defrocked for ordination, a Roman in Japan, Super human mutants, killer grass and who killed the Avro Arrow</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120626-153030-to-20120626-163206.mp3" length="58890119" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120626-153030-to-20120626-163206.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 171 - Living Wage Edition - 19-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 15:30:26 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 171 - Living Wage Edition

This week we talk about china's manned rocket mission, Neanderthal painters, the conviction Alexander Aan for declaring himself a atheist in Indonesia, how sex in music may make your song a chart topper and
final part of an interview with Iglika Ivanova, research economist; this week a talk about poverty and a living wage.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 171 - Chinese rockets, old cave painting, man jailed for being an atheist, sex sells music, and economist Iglika Ivanova on poverty and the living wage</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120619-153026-to-20120619-163331.mp3" length="60311255" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120619-153026-to-20120619-163331.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 170 - Korean Fail Edition - 12-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 15:30:16 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 170 - Korean Fail Edition

This week we talk about in South Korea all references to evolution are being removed from science textbooks, Reading god's mind - how Autism spectrum provides a defense against belief in a personal god and
part 1 of 2 of an interview with Iglika Ivanova, research economist; this week a talk about tuition fees and the real cost of secondary eduction.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 170 - Korian Fail, Reading God's mind and Iglika Ivanova on Tuition fees and university funding</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120612-153016-to-20120612-162851.mp3" length="56023244" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120612-153016-to-20120612-162851.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 169 - Poisons Pastor Edition -  05-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 15:30:33 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 169 - Poisons Pastor Edition

This week we talk about the send the Queen up the river with questions about the press on the jubilee, Snake handling Pastor dies by snake bit like his father - a look at snake handling, Do dogs really feel guilt or are we projecting?  and
part 3 of 3 of an interview with Seth Klein from the Canadian Center of Policy Alternatives - This week a talk about Inequality - Its harms to society.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 169 - Queen flotilla, Snike bit pastor, guilty dogs? and Seth Klein on inequality</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120605-153033-to-20120605-163209.mp3" length="58889285" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120605-153033-to-20120605-163209.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 168 - Jane the Ripper Edition -  29-May-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 15:31:19 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 168 - Jane the Ripper Edition

This week we talk about the phenomena of celebrates offering parts of the selves for other to eat, A study explains why the oceans have more water than they should, part 2 of 3 of an interview with Seth Klein from the Canadian Center of Policy Alternatives - This week a talk about Taxes - What the story? and
A discussion about the Jack the Ripper and a new claim that Jack was actually Jane.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 168 - Celebraty Canabalism, Too much water, Taxes with Seth Klein and Jack the Ripper meme</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120529-153119-to-20120529-163120.mp3" length="57374324" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120529-153119-to-20120529-163120.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 167 - Global Austerity Edition -  22-May-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 15:26:33 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 167 - Global Austerity Edition

This week we talk about the launch of Dragon Space craft, A study about how overselling vaccination can backfire, Harper's Budget cuts are making Canadian scientist and endangered species and
part 1 of 3 of an interview with Seth Klein from the Canadian Center of Policy Alternatives - This week a talk about Austerity- does it work?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 167 - Space-X, overselling Vax, Endangered Scientist, Austerity- Does it work?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120522-152633-to-20120522-162816.mp3" length="59001875" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120522-152633-to-20120522-162816.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 166 - SkyTrain Fare-ness Edition -  15-May-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 15:32:19 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 166 - SkyTrain Fare-ness Edition

This week we talk about Norway changes constitution be become UN-christian nation, Meta study shows East Germans most Atheist nation, Vatican rebukes own academy for being open-minded, Catholic school refuses to play team with a girl on it and
a Discussing about SkyTrain, Fare-Gates and the value of public mass transit

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 166 - Apostate Norway, East German Atheist, The Vatican Bubble, Catholics Bad Sports, and the un-fare-ness of SkyTrain</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120515-153219-to-20120515-163306.mp3" length="58106993" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120515-153219-to-20120515-163306.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 165 - Profiling Sam Harris  Edition - 08-May-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 15:32:41 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 165 - Profiling Sam Harris  Edition 

This week we talk about the elections of no-Nazis in Greece and Socialists in France, the potential loss of cultural heritage sites in Asia, &quot;The Jesus T-shirt&quot; controversy and
Discussing Sam Harris's articles about ethnic/racial profiling for the TSA, political correctness and islamophobia - Is Harris a racist?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 165 - Right wins Europe, Asain Haritage sites, The Jesus T-shirt and Sam Harris on Profiling</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120508-153241-to-20120508-163259.mp3" length="57519440" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120508-153241-to-20120508-163259.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 164 - International Workers  Edition - 01-May-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 15:28:07 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Free Thinkers Episode 164 - International Workers  Edition

This week we talk about the Royal Mint releases first glow in the dark quarter, Plans to mine asteroids for rare-earth elements, Nutella convicted for NOT being health food, How analytical thinking will make you less religious and
NarcOnon The Scientology drug Detox/Rehab centers.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 164 - Glow-in-the-dark Coins, Mining Asteroids,  Nutella ain't health food, de-faithing analytics, and NarcOnon - Scientology on drugs</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120501-152807-to-20120501-163048.mp3" length="59885915" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120501-152807-to-20120501-163048.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 163 - Department of Silence Edition - 24-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 15:31:24 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 163 - Department of Silence Edition

This week we talk about Bureaucratic censorship of science, Human haired mice, Shoppers Drug Mart sued over selling homeopathy, and did ancient Asian travel to the Americas?
and, getting more than you bargained for in traditional Chinese medicine

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 163 - Bureaucratic censorship, Human haired mouse, Shoppers sued over homeopathy, Ancient Asian travels to the Americas and what's REALLY in TCM</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120424-153124-to-20120424-163603.mp3" length="61810787" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120424-153124-to-20120424-163603.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 162 - Freethinking President Edition - 17-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 15:34:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 162 - Freethinking President Edition Edition

This week we talk about vary hot March, Climate change now and then, Violent video games are socially good, Saskatoon has no exorcists, and interview with the new president of UBCs Freethinker Club.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 162 - Hot March, Climate Change 1981, the Good of violent video games, Saksatoon exorcism, and interview with new UBC Freethinker's club president</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120417-153400-to-20120417-163451.mp3" length="58172045" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120417-153400-to-20120417-163451.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 161 - Budget Busting Edition - 10-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 15:36:30 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 161 - Budget Busting Edition Edition

This week we talk about Largest feathered dinosaur found, Donald Trump sadly comes out to promote the Anti-Vax movement, Passover myth of slaves building Egyptian pyramids, How the budget cuts to the CBC makes Canadians dumber, and How budget austerity will hurt skepticism in Canada.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 161 - Ruffled paleontologist, Trumping Anti-Vax, Passover myths, Cutting the CBC, and Austerity Hurts Skepticism</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120410-153630-to-20120410-163250.mp3" length="53713898" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120410-153630-to-20120410-163250.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 160 - Somebodies Watching Me Edition 03-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 15:28:05 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 160 - Somebodies Watching Me Edition

This week we talk about Internet Surveillance, Improving Uranium, Anthropomorphic Extinction, Lucy's neighbors, and Pick you skeptic battles

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio FreeThinkers Episode 160 - Internet Surveillence, Improving Uranium, Anthropomorphic Exitinction, Lucy's neighbors, and Pick you skeptic battles</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120403-152805-to-20120403-162801.mp3" length="57213362" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120403-152805-to-20120403-162801.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker #159 - Trans-Atlantic Conservative Edition - 27-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 15:34:00 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT #159 - Trans-Atlantic Conservative Edition

This week we talk about 
Posthumous weddings, Pink Slime Warnings and Donâs interview with Tony Sobrado â Part 3(of 3), conservatism here and across the pond.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker #159 - Posthumous weddings, Pink Slime Warnings and Sobrado on conservatism</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120327-153400-to-20120327-163000.mp3" length="549" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120327-153400-to-20120327-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker #158 - Citing Canada Edition - 20-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2012 15:35:04 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT #158 - Citing Canada Edition

This week we talk about 
Canada's kick-ass scientist and Harper's plan to sell them, 
CFI Canada &quot;elects&quot; new board of directors, 
NASA sued for discriminating against believer in Intelligent Design, 
is St. Patrick's day demeaning to the Irish and 
part 2 interview with Tony Sobrado Conspiracy theory as political ideology.


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker #158 - Selling Canada Science, Intelligent Design sues NASA, St Patrick's Day bad for Irish and Tony Sobrado part 2</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120320-153504-to-20120320-162949.mp3" length="52245641" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120320-153504-to-20120320-162949.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker #157 - Earthworm Invasion Edition - 13-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 15:35:17 -0700</pubDate><description>RFT #157 - Earthworm Invasion Edition

This week we talk about invading earthworms, cancer and caramel colouring in cola, FFRF appeal to liberate Catholics from the church and part 1 interview with Tony Sobrado about a theory of conspiracy theories.


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker #157 - Alien worms, killer caramel, leaving Catholic Church and Tony Sobrado</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120313-153517-to-20120313-163328.mp3" length="56462762" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120313-153517-to-20120313-163328.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker #156 - Rational Compassion Edition - 06-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 15:38:21 -0800</pubDate><description>RFT Ep 156 - Rational Compassion Edition

This week we talk about zombie chickens, 
disconnect between religion and depression, 
part 2 of our interview with Leo Igwe where he talks about how he avoided 'unrational' thinking and rational compassion
and we discuss what happened to neanderthals and did were they sailors.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker #156 - Right to decieve, Leo Igwe and talking about Neanderthals</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120306-153821-to-20120306-163551.mp3" length="54964064" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120306-153821-to-20120306-163551.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Free Thinker #155 - Witch Hunter Edition - 28-Feb-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 15:37:24 -0800</pubDate><description>RFT ep 155 - Witch Hunter Edition
This weeks show we discuss Swiss attempts to clean space, The double standards of the Heartland Inst. and Glieck climate scandal being open minded, and an extended interview we discuss the growing problem of witch hunting in Africa with Leo Igwe, Nigerian skeptic, global humanist and tireless proponent of rational compassion.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Free Thinker Ep. 155 - cleaning space, Heartland-Glieck scandal, open mindedness, and witch hunting in Africa</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120228-153724-to-20120228-163729.mp3" length="57549464" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120228-153724-to-20120228-163729.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #154 on 21-Feb-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 15:35:53 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 154 - C-30 and Vic Toews, CAM in Oz, Vatican loses Tax-Exempt status, and Legislating Morality? 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 154 - C-30 and Vic Toews, CAM in Oz, Vatican loses Tax-Exempt status, and Legislating Morality?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120221-153553-to-20120221-163116.mp3" length="52738118" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120221-153553-to-20120221-163116.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #153 on  14-Feb-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2012 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate><description>A collection of some of our best bits from past episodes</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 153 - Home Alone Edition</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120214-153000-to-20120214-164000.mp3" length="67769300" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120214-153000-to-20120214-164000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #152 on 07-Feb-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 15:31:37 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 152 - Mystery Atheist in Vancouver, Is gender selection wrong? Secrets of Mona Lisa revealed? Men Try to impress Women and Canadian Imams issue fatwa against honor killings

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 152 - Mystery Atheist in Vancouver, Is gender selection wrong? Secrets of Mona Lisa revealed? Men Try to impress Women and Canadian Imams issue fatwa against honor killings</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120207-153137-to-20120207-163358.mp3" length="59482676" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120207-153137-to-20120207-163358.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #151on 31-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 15:38:33 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 151 - Artificial cell walls, Scientology evolving, Vitamin woo, and the Pseudoscience of &quot;positive thinking&quot;


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 151 - Artificial cell walls, Scientology evolving, Vitamin woo, and the Pseudoscience of &quot;positive thinking&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120131-153833-to-20120131-163639.mp3" length="55406084" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120131-153833-to-20120131-163639.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #150 on 24-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 15:37:23 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 150 - Scorpions are big eye balls, Andrew Wakefield Strikes Back, Pro-Piracy Group a Religion, And Is Skepticism too Paternalistic?


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 150 - Scorpions are big eye balls, Andrew Wakefield Strikes Back, Pro-Piracy Group a Religion, And Is Skepticism too Paternalistic?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120124-153723-to-20120124-163600.mp3" length="55900229" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120124-153723-to-20120124-163600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #149 on 10-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 15:30:50 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 149 - Is Sex Addiction Real? Can Mountain Due dissolve a Mouse? Is Time Travel Possible? If it were, Where would you go and why?  

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 149 - Is Sex Addiction Real? Can Mountain Due dissolve a Mouse? Is Time Travel Possible? If it were, Where would you go and why?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120110-153050-to-20120110-163126.mp3" length="57933104" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120110-153050-to-20120110-163126.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #148 on 03-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 15:31:08 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 148 - Saudi Arabia Witch killing, Cee-Lo changes John Lennons Imagine, Censoring A Pseudo-scientist, plus we are joined by fan of the show Andrew to hear how Radio Freethinker Changed his Life! 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 148 - Saudi Arabia Witch killing, Cee-Lo changes John Lennons Imagine, Censoring A Pseudo-scientist, plus we are joined by fan of the show Andrew to hear how Radio Freethinker Changed his Life!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120103-153108-to-20120103-163410.mp3" length="60263300" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120103-153108-to-20120103-163410.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #147 on 27-Dec-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 15:19:59 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 147 - Former Co-Host Rob Returns! Ethical Oil, Kelowna Menorah Controversy, Biggest Science Stories of 2011, Biggest Skeptical News Stories of 2011!!  

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 147 - Former Co-Host Rob Returns! Ethical Oil, Kelowna Menorah Controversy, Biggest Science Stories of 2011, Biggest Skeptical News Stories of 2011!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111227-151959-to-20111227-164110.mp3" length="77580476" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111227-151959-to-20111227-164110.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #146 on 20-Dec-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 15:31:38 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 145 - Remembering Christopher Hitchens, Deadly Cooky Dough, the Habs and homeopathy, Xmas Smells, hormonal Xmas and a reality check for Christmas.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 146 - Habs and Homeopathy, Smells of xmas, hormonal  xmas. Plus reality check for Christmas</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111220-153138-to-20111220-163153.mp3" length="57598253" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111220-153138-to-20111220-163153.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #145 on 13-Dec-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 15:30:17 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 145 - Kepler 22b, Suppressing ESP with Skepticism, Bare-faced Citizenship oath. Plus dealing with a mountain of data - how to manage it?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 145 - Kepler 22b, Suppressing ESP with Skepticism, Bare-faced Citizenship oath. Plus dealing with a mountain of data - how to manage it?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111213-153017-to-20111213-163352.mp3" length="60789971" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111213-153017-to-20111213-163352.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #144 on 06-Dec-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 15:30:26 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 144 - Fit while fat, beating babies in the name of Jesus, why are atheists distrusted by religious people? 


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 144 - Fit while fat, beating babies in the name of Jesus, why are atheists distrusted by religious people?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111206-153026-to-20111206-163237.mp3" length="59448482" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111206-153026-to-20111206-163237.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #143 on 29-Nov-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 15:30:04 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 143 - Thanks for the donations, Religious charities a black hole? Engineering Enzymes, and CFI Canada's recent problems. 


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 143 - Thanks for the donations, Religious charities a black hole? Engineering Enzymes, and CFI Canada's recent problems.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111129-153004-to-20111129-163200.mp3" length="59209958" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111129-153004-to-20111129-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #142 on 22-Nov-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2011 15:33:11 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 142 - Fundraising Episode! Pizza as a vegetable, Cyclops shark REAL, Viral Arsenal for Gene Therapy and more! Donate to CiTR and Radio Freethinker! 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 142 - Fundraising Episode! Pizza as a vegetable, Cyclops shark REAL, Viral Arsenal for Gene Therapy and more! Donate to CiTR and Radio Freethinker!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111122-153311-to-20111122-163216.mp3" length="56479859" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111122-153311-to-20111122-163216.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #141 on 15-Nov-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 15:30:03 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 141 - Light therapy, Wisdom Teeth anesthesia fail, Possible Ogopogo sighting, EEG on vegetative state patients, Catholic Church investigator charged with pedophilia

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 141 - Light therapy, Wisdom Teeth anesthesia fail, Possible Ogopogo sighting, EEG on vegetative state patients, Catholic Church investigator charged with paedophile</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111115-153003-to-20111115-163011.mp3" length="57485663" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111115-153003-to-20111115-163011.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #140 on 08-Nov-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 15:34:43 -0800</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 140 - CFI drops Reasonable Women's group, daylight savings saves lives, the Vatican loses an embassy, legalized bullying in Michigan, Pox Parties and Pox by Mail 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 140 - CFI drops Reasonable Women's group, daylight savings saves lives, the Vatican loses an embassy, legalized bullying in Michigan, Pox Parties and Pox by Mail</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111108-153443-to-20111108-162819.mp3" length="51248594" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111108-153443-to-20111108-162819.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #139 on 01-Nov-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 15:27:58 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 139 - World population reaches 7 billion, Catholic Church stealing babies in Spain, Canadian Wheat Board is scrapped, and the Golden Section meme.


Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 139 - World population reaches 7 billion, Catholic Church stealing babies in Spain, Canadian Wheat Board is scrapped, and the Golden Section meme</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111101-152758-to-20111101-163309.mp3" length="62298677" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111101-152758-to-20111101-163309.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #138 on 25-Oct-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 15:30:31 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 138 - Robots and Robot ethics with special guest Ajung Moon, biominetics, AI, and Robot-Human relations.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 138 - Robots and Robot ethics with special guest Ajung Moon, biominetics, AI, and Robot-Human relations</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111025-153031-to-20111025-163354.mp3" length="60598568" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111025-153031-to-20111025-163354.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #137 on 18-Oct-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 15:35:15 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 137 - Dreams are discussed, the philosophy of dreams, the history of dream interpretation and the current science on dreams.

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 137 - Dreams are discussed, the philosophy of dreams, the history of dream interpretation and the current science on dreams</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111018-153515-to-20111018-163153.mp3" length="54133400" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111018-153515-to-20111018-163153.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #136 on 11-Oct-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 15:27:50 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 136 - Dawkins banned from event, psychological disorders linked to religious belief? Understanding diversity in science testing, plus the Nobel and Ig-Nobel prizes 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 136 - Dawkins banned from event, psychological disorders linnked to religious belief? Understanding diversity in science testing, plus the Nobel and Ig-Nobel prizes</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111011-152750-to-20111011-163120.mp3" length="60686555" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111011-152750-to-20111011-163120.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #135 on 04-Oct-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 15:33:04 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 135 - Science in the Courtroom, Insite wins Supreme Court case, Italian scientists face manslaughter charges for failure to warn of earthquake. Plus how can scientist better communicate their concerns? 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 135 - Science in the Courtroom, Insite wins Supreme Court case, Italian scientists face manslaughter charges for failure to warn of earthquake. Plus how can scientist better communicate their concerns?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111004-153304-to-20111004-164034.mp3" length="64316540" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111004-153304-to-20111004-164034.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #134 on 27-Sep-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 15:31:49 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 134 - Interview with James Randi, Catholic enough for Canada? Faster than light possible? Why do people doubt climate change? 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 134 - Interview with James Randi, Catholic enough for Canada? Faster than light possible? Why do people doubt climate change?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110927-153149-to-20110927-163128.mp3" length="57022793" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110927-153149-to-20110927-163128.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #133 on 20-Sep-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 15:30:34 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 133 - Muting the immune system, Baby pains, Palestine statehood, and The Doom of Vancouver - Volcanoes or Earthquakes?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 133 - Muting the immune system, Baby pains, Palestine statehood, and The Doom of Vancouver - Volcanoes or Earthquakes?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110920-153034-to-20110920-163156.mp3" length="58665773" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110920-153034-to-20110920-163156.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #132 on 13-Sep-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 15:31:38 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 132 - Welcome to Winnipeg listeners, Catholic schools attract other religions, the coffee illusion, argument clinic, the scientist-journalist communication breakdown 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 132 - Welcome to Winnipeg listeners, Catholic schools attract other religions, the coffee illusion, argument clinic, the scientist-journalist communication breakdown</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110913-153138-to-20110913-163658.mp3" length="62465894" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110913-153138-to-20110913-163658.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #131 on 06-Sep-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 15:30:13 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 131 - School uniforms, climate change denial victim, sex offender laws, how to talk about ghosts

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 131 - School uniforms, climate change denial victim, sex offender laws, how to talk about ghosts</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110906-153013-to-20110906-163252.mp3" length="59896340" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110906-153013-to-20110906-163252.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #130 on 30-Aug-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 15:30:42 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 130 - Praying for poop, Countries going extinct, Caffeine and Cancer, Plus is the crime rate rising? Will more prisons lower it?

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 130 - Praying for poop, Countries going extinct, Caffeine and Cancer, Plus is the crime rate rising? Will more prisons lower it?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110830-153042-to-20110830-163230.mp3" length="59031899" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110830-153042-to-20110830-163230.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #129 on 23-Aug-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 15:33:02 -0700</pubDate><description>Radio Freethinker Episode 129 - Interview with Neil deGrasse Tyson, California teacher who criticized Christianity, Drug companies funding clinical trials and the Pope in Spain and Abortion forgiveness week. 

Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 129 - Interview with Neil deGrasse Tyson, California teacher who criticized Christianity, Drug companies funding clinical trials and the Pope in Spain and Abortion forgiveness week.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110823-153302-to-20110823-163358.mp3" length="59168258" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110823-153302-to-20110823-163358.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #128 on 16-Aug-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 15:32:02 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 128 - Interview with Elizabeth Loftus, Montreal Police investigate Dennis Markuze aka David Mabus, the Cost of Drug research is also discussed.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110816-153202-to-20110816-163138.mp3" length="56976089" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110816-153202-to-20110816-163138.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #127 on 09-Aug-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 15:31:16 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 127 - Interview with Jennifer Ouellette, Big Pharma on Social media, Elizabeth May on Wi-fi and the &quot;muzzling&quot; of a federal scientist</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110809-153116-to-20110809-163540.mp3" length="61572263" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110809-153116-to-20110809-163540.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #126 on 02-Aug-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 15:32:09 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 126 - Interview with Dr.'s Susana Martinez-Conde and Stephen Macknik, U.S Debt &quot;crisis&quot;, Christian Terrorism and the double standard of it</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110802-153209-to-20110802-162934.mp3" length="54904433" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110802-153209-to-20110802-162934.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #125 on 26-Jul-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 15:31:58 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 125 - Interview with Richard Wiseman, Creationism out of Textbooks in Texas, Reddit Co-founder in trouble, Pre-infected PC's, and Drug strategies.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110726-153158-to-20110726-162902.mp3" length="54571250" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110726-153158-to-20110726-162902.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #124 on 19-Jul-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 15:31:34 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 124 - Coverage of The Amazing Meeting 9 in Las Vegas, Prayer in Manitoba Schools, Placebo Effect Asthma Study</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110719-153134-to-20110719-163015.mp3" length="56098304" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110719-153134-to-20110719-163015.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #123 on 12-Jul-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 15:30:48 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 123 - Town revokes Hilter's citizenship, Was Putin sent by God for Russia? Bombs inside Terrorists and The power of language and Scientific Jargon</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110712-153048-to-20110712-163015.mp3" length="56829305" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110712-153048-to-20110712-163015.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #122 on 05-Jul-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 15:31:51 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 122 - Killing Hypnosis, Listener Emails, Controversial MS treatment gets funding. Plus, end of life and assisted sucide is discussed</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110705-153151-to-20110705-162936.mp3" length="55225523" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110705-153151-to-20110705-162936.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #121 on 28-Jun-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 15:30:50 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 121 - Baby Swinging, HIV Vaccine Breakthrough, New York Legalizes Gay Marriage, Interview with Ben Radford: Paranormal Investigator</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110628-153050-to-20110628-163401.mp3" length="60407165" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110628-153050-to-20110628-163401.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #120 on 21-Jun-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 15:31:51 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at info@radiofreethinker.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 120 - Introducing Jenna Capyk and Deidre Olson, Australian scientists organize over Climate Science plus the Psychology of Riots</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110621-153151-to-20110621-163117.mp3" length="56814710" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110621-153151-to-20110621-163117.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #119 on 14-Jun-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:30:34 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 119 - The Naturalistic Fallacy, Interview with DJ Grothe, Are Video Games Dangerous?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110614-153034-to-20110614-163040.mp3" length="57453971" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110614-153034-to-20110614-163040.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #118 on 07-Jun-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 15:29:39 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 118 - The WHO on cell phones and cancer, police state skepticism plus an interview with PZ Myers</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110607-152939-to-20110607-163207.mp3" length="59698265" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110607-152939-to-20110607-163207.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #117 on 31-May-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 15:31:53 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 117 - Email on Circumcision, Oprah retires but what legacy does she leave? Interview with Brian Dalton aka &quot;Mr. Deity&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110531-153153-to-20110531-163112.mp3" length="56702120" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110531-153153-to-20110531-163112.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #116 on 24-May-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 15:32:16 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 116 - Anti Vax Lecture in Vancouver, Obama and Israel, Interview with Christopher DiCarlo and Nate Phelps</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110524-153216-to-20110524-164019.mp3" length="65023772" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110524-153216-to-20110524-164019.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #115 on 17-May-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 15:32:33 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 115 - Slut Walk Vancouver, The Supreme Court of Canada, Course on Secularism, Interview with Stuart Bechman and Jen McCreight</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110517-153233-to-20110517-163541.mp3" length="60359210" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110517-153233-to-20110517-163541.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 114 on 10-May-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 15:30:36 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 114 - Coverage of the Imagine no Religion conference, Interview with Justin Trottier and Loren Price, Killing Bin Laden, Sharia Law in Canada</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110510-153036-to-20110510-163411.mp3" length="60790388" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110510-153036-to-20110510-163411.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #113 on 03-May-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 15:32:33 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 113 - Election results, Listener emails, SETI, Iphone tracking and Sony hacking and privacy</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110503-153233-to-20110503-163011.mp3" length="55089581" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110503-153233-to-20110503-163011.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #112 on 26-Apr-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 15:33:35 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 112 - Election special featuring returning co-host Rob Teska and Daniel Gipps, we dive into election issues and more answers for our skeptical questions to politicians</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110426-153335-to-20110426-163621.mp3" length="60007262" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110426-153335-to-20110426-163621.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #111 on 19-Apr-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 15:33:08 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 111 - Interview with Bill Ligertwood, MS Vein blocking treatment, election reality check, and we asked politicians skeptical questions, what did they say?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110419-153308-to-20110419-162942.mp3" length="54090449" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110419-153308-to-20110419-162942.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #110 on 12-Apr-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 15:32:28 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 110 - Email about Creationist Science minister, death anxiety linked to Intelligent design? Interview with Farzana Hassan on the Niqab, Discussion of multiculturalism in Canada.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110412-153228-to-20110412-163119.mp3" length="56255096" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110412-153228-to-20110412-163119.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #109 on 05-Apr-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2011 15:33:38 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 109 - Blasphemy day clarification, Interview with Loren Price of CFI Okanagan about the new Atheist Bus Ads in Kelowna and Kamloops, Political election funding, plus a discussion on the burning of a Koran and recent violence in A</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110405-153338-to-20110405-163047.mp3" length="54628379" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110405-153338-to-20110405-163047.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #108 on 29-Mar-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2011 15:36:07 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 108 - Listener Feedback, Ironic email, and Updates, Plus interview with Amanda Wanner UBC Freethinker President</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110329-153607-to-20110329-163214.mp3" length="53637170" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110329-153607-to-20110329-163214.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #107 on 22-Mar-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 15:31:55 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 107 - Hydraulic Fracturing, Humans using fire, Canadian Nuclear safety, Crucifixes in European schools, plus the Bicentennial of the War of 1812</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110322-153155-to-20110322-163104.mp3" length="56544077" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110322-153155-to-20110322-163104.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #106 on 15-Mar-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 15:32:35 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 106 - Gef the talking Mongoose, quack medicine on Global Calgary, Interview with Dennis and Melanie Stoiber, No fly zone in Libya, Nuclear concerns in Japan</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110315-153235-to-20110315-163010.mp3" length="55043294" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110315-153235-to-20110315-163010.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #105 on 08-Mar-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 15:33:06 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 105 - WiFi hysteria in Maple Ridge, poverty myths, Life in a Meteorite, Government intervention, and Can animals talk?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110308-153306-to-20110308-163222.mp3" length="56654999" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110308-153306-to-20110308-163222.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #104 on 01-Mar-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 15:34:09 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 104 - Pope charged with Crimes against Humanity, New Cell phone study, Fluoridation in Calgary's water, Questions to ask politicians in upcoming elections</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110301-153409-to-20110301-163624.mp3" length="59511449" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110301-153409-to-20110301-163624.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #103 on 22-Feb-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 15:31:33 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 103 - More on Veiled Voting, Is Math innate? Van Goth art degrading, Argument Clinic and the Protocols of the Elders of Zion</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110222-153133-to-20110222-163013.mp3" length="56079956" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110222-153133-to-20110222-163013.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #102 on 15-Feb-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 15:37:32 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 102 - Guest Host Baba Brinkman, Update on religious astronomer who sued university, Accomondation regarding religious and culture is discussed</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110215-153732-to-20110215-163246.mp3" length="52634285" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110215-153732-to-20110215-163246.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 101 on 08-Feb-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 15:32:41 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 101 - Archaeologists to rebury finds, cloaking device, Bill Gates on Anti-Vax, The Unerring Bible? Argument Clinic and Common misconceptions</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110208-153241-to-20110208-163130.mp3" length="56224655" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110208-153241-to-20110208-163130.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #100 on 01-Feb-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 15:39:33 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 100!! - Tricorder invention, Ancient Tool Kit discovered, bad year of disasters because of climate change, Germany won't return artifact to Egypt. Argument Clinic and A Skeptical Dispatch. Plus Science and Imperialism is discusse</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110201-153933-to-20110201-163702.mp3" length="54947801" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110201-153933-to-20110201-163702.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #99 on 25-Jan-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 15:32:06 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 99 - Pope John-Paul II a saint? Food production needs to be overhauled, plus an interview with Erica Johnson of CBC Marketplace!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110125-153206-to-20110125-163128.mp3" length="56751743" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110125-153206-to-20110125-163128.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #98 on 18-Jan-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 15:32:40 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 98 - CBC Marketplace? CBC Marketplace! Private hospital rooms, UBC Hospice vs Spirits, Witchcraft and Wizards abroad, plus Censorship is discussed</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110118-153240-to-20110118-163336.mp3" length="58252109" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110118-153240-to-20110118-163336.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #97 on 11-Jan-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 15:32:06 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 97 - Andrew Wakefield is a fraud, Conseratives have different brains (sort of), Influence of religion lowering in the U.S, Dispatch from Rob, and Corporal Punishment - does it work?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110111-153206-to-20110111-163256.mp3" length="58156199" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110111-153206-to-20110111-163256.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #96 on 04-Jan-2011</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 15:32:08 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 96 - Drug decriminalization in Portugal, Neanderthals ate vegetables, Salman Taseer murdered in Pakistan, mass bird death, and can we have ethics through science?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110104-153208-to-20110104-163053.mp3" length="56159186" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110104-153208-to-20110104-163053.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #95 on 28-Dec-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 15:32:27 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 95 - The Pope blames society for pedophilia, Head of King Henri IV is recovered, Denisovans are discussed. Plus consumerism, what should we know about what we buy?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101228-153227-to-20101228-163029.mp3" length="55472804" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101228-153227-to-20101228-163029.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #94 on 21-Dec-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 15:28:52 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 94 - Our mistakes, Evolution acceptance rises, astronomer sues university, UK tries to block porn, and is Wikileaks a good thing for democracy?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101221-152852-to-20101221-163403.mp3" length="62300345" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101221-152852-to-20101221-163403.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #93 on 14-Dec-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 15:31:04 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 93 - Anthropology Association drops science, ombudsman's G20 report, Julian Assange charges, and discussion on who can own land and/or property</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101214-153104-to-20101214-162913.mp3" length="55609163" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101214-153104-to-20101214-162913.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #92 on 07-Dec-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 15:36:24 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 92 - Polygamy laws in Canada, Entrapment and creating terrorists, plus horrible gifts to give skeptics and a few good ones too.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101207-153624-to-20101207-163212.mp3" length="53335262" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101207-153624-to-20101207-163212.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #91 on 30-Nov-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 15:36:34 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 91 - Canadian Archbishop and child molestation, Fox new north, Stress and maternal infanticide, plus an interview with Jennifer McCreight</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101130-153634-to-20101130-163126.mp3" length="52439963" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101130-153634-to-20101130-163126.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #90 on 23-Nov-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2010 15:30:20 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 90 - CiTR Fundraiser Episode Number 2!! Tycho Brahe exhumed, The Pope likes Condoms, Exorcisms and Anti-Vax ads and more! Please donate to CiTR at 604 822 8648 or at www.citr.ca/donate</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101123-153020-to-20101123-163056.mp3" length="57932687" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101123-153020-to-20101123-163056.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #89 on 16-Nov-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2010 15:31:09 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 89 - CiTR Fundraiser Episode!! Skeptical News and Arguments!! Please donate to CiTR at 604 822 8648 or at www.citr.ca/donate</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101116-153109-to-20101116-163300.mp3" length="59129894" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101116-153109-to-20101116-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #88 on 09-Nov-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 15:30:30 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 88 - Chupacabra, Jesus statue, science cheerleaders and Humanists ads by AHA. Plus Taxes</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101109-153030-to-20101109-163016.mp3" length="57134549" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101109-153030-to-20101109-163016.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #8t on 09-Nov-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 15:30:30 -0800</pubDate><description></description><itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101109-153030-to-20101109-163016.mp3" length="57134549" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101109-153030-to-20101109-163016.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #87 on 02-Nov-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2010 15:32:28 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 87 - Is CiTR too Corporate? Mummies, Cancer and the SGU, Sask Science Centre is haunted and an Interview with Marci McDonald author of the Armageddon Factor</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101102-153228-to-20101102-163024.mp3" length="55376894" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101102-153228-to-20101102-163024.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #86 on 26-Oct-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2010 15:31:12 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 86 - Syndicated in Kamloops! Creationist at UBC and SkeptiCamp 2010 II, Interview with Bill Ligertwood, discussion on Transportation</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101026-153112-to-20101026-163051.mp3" length="57021125" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101026-153112-to-20101026-163051.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #85 on 19-Oct-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 15:34:39 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 85 - The Google Car, Interview with Doctor Harriet Hall, Is Prostitution Harmful?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101019-153439-to-20101019-163216.mp3" length="55075820" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101019-153439-to-20101019-163216.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #84 on 12-Oct-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 15:30:50 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 84 - Coverage of the Secular Humanism Next 30 Years Conference in LA, Nobel Prizes, and the Babri Masjid Mosque in India</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101012-153050-to-20101012-163008.mp3" length="56687525" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101012-153050-to-20101012-163008.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #83 on 05-Oct-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 15:31:02 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 83 - Alien Ambassador, New Planet, Updates from past shows, Why do Atheists know more about Religion than Believers?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101005-153102-to-20101005-162743.mp3" length="54202205" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101005-153102-to-20101005-162743.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #82 on 28-Sep-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 15:31:05 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 82 - Van Praagh Skeptivism. Chloe explains herself, Winds parting the Red Sea? The Gulf Oil spill and Long Guns</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100928-153105-to-20100928-163026.mp3" length="56735480" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100928-153105-to-20100928-163026.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #81 on 21-Sep-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 15:33:55 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 81 - Vaccines and Heart Attacks, &quot;Super&quot; Potatoes, France bans head veils, HIV/Aids on decline in Africa, plus the Pope in the UK</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100921-153355-to-20100921-163020.mp3" length="53924483" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100921-153355-to-20100921-163020.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #80 on 14-Sep-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 15:30:43 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 80 - Buring the Qur'an follow up, Canadian government censoring science, anti-science leads to discrimination at CBS, and Diversity in the skeptical/atheist movement.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100914-153043-to-20100914-163010.mp3" length="56830973" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100914-153043-to-20100914-163010.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #79 on 07-Sep-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 15:32:49 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com and follow us on twitter at @citrrft</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 79 - Stephen Hawking says no creator in Big Bang, Burning the Koran on September 11th, New discoveries in Egypt, and the Venus Project</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100907-153249-to-20100907-163223.mp3" length="56943146" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100907-153249-to-20100907-163223.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #78 on 31-Aug-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 15:31:29 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 78 - Follow up on the Anti-Stoning Rally in Vancouver, Japan slams homeopathy, Stricter controls for the IPCC, plus an interview with the cast of the Reality Check podcast!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100831-153129-to-20100831-163102.mp3" length="56911037" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100831-153129-to-20100831-163102.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #77 on 24-Aug-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 15:30:36 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 77 - Intolerance and ignorance is the theme for Skeptical News, plus coverage of the Skeptics Tool Box Conference!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100824-153036-to-20100824-162811.mp3" length="55065812" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100824-153036-to-20100824-162811.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #76 on 17-Aug-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 15:30:44 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 76 -  John Edward's event in Vancouver, Wi-Fi in Schools, Should the Pope be banned from the UK? Rob's last Show! He reveals all!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100817-153044-to-20100817-163118.mp3" length="57900578" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100817-153044-to-20100817-163118.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #75 on 10-Aug-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 15:30:21 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 75 - Is Canada's crime rising? Google and Verizon, interview with Michael Shermer</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100810-153021-to-20100810-162918.mp3" length="56373107" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100810-153021-to-20100810-162918.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #74 on 03-Aug-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2010 15:30:10 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 74 - PZ Myers event and Pride Parade wrap up, listener emails, Blackberry security, Wikileaks and Skepticism</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100803-153010-to-20100803-163400.mp3" length="61029746" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100803-153010-to-20100803-163400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #73 on 27-Jul-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 15:29:08 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 73 - New Stonehenge, the Census, Was the H1N1 Vaccine worth it? Plus an interview with Dr. Rachael Dunlop</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100727-152908-to-20100727-162935.mp3" length="57787571" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100727-152908-to-20100727-162935.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #72 on 20-Jul-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 15:31:55 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 72 - Vandalization of the SFU Skeptics Banner, 18th Century Boat at Ground Zero, Hottest Year on Record, and an Interview with Joe Nickell</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100720-153155-to-20100720-163106.mp3" length="56574101" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100720-153155-to-20100720-163106.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #71 on 13-Jul-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 15:28:58 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 71 - G20 Conspiracy theories, TAM 8 coverage, Interview with Jennifer Michael Hecht</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100713-152858-to-20100713-162947.mp3" length="58139519" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100713-152858-to-20100713-162947.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #70 on 06-Jul-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 15:29:51 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 70 - Nuking BPs oil spill, UFO's in Europe, Should we change the name of Stanley Park?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100706-152951-to-20100706-162959.mp3" length="57478574" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100706-152951-to-20100706-162959.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #69 on 29-Jun-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 15:29:50 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 69 - Special guests Ian Cromwell and Jakob Liljenwall and discuss organic pesticides, Belgium police raid on Catholic Church and Confrontation vs Accommodation in the Skeptical Community</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100629-152950-to-20100629-163210.mp3" length="59569412" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100629-152950-to-20100629-163210.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #68 on 22-Jun-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 15:29:28 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 68 - Today we're joined by Jesse Brydle and discuss: NASA's Kelper, Canadian Catholic promotion, Heroification in History</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100622-152928-to-20100622-162806.mp3" length="56049515" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100622-152928-to-20100622-162806.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #67 on 15-Jun-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 15:29:47 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 67 - Update on the Constellation Project, AI Stock Trading, Autism study, Is Israel apartheid?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100615-152947-to-20100615-163158.mp3" length="59425964" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100615-152947-to-20100615-163158.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #66 on 08-Jun-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 15:29:40 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 66 - How did confronting Deepak go? Lucky charms, and a Skeptical look at Democracy</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100608-152940-to-20100608-163206.mp3" length="59664905" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100608-152940-to-20100608-163206.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #65 on 01-Jun-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 15:29:16 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 65 - Interview with Jeff Wagg of the JREF, Washing your hands, Food and Salt.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100601-152916-to-20100601-162903.mp3" length="57150395" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100601-152916-to-20100601-162903.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #64 on 25-May-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 15:30:15 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 64 - Monster found in Ontario, California and Texas Textbooks, Is sunscreen bad for you? Plus, is Dr. Venters artificial life a breakthrough?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100525-153015-to-20100525-163047.mp3" length="57867218" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100525-153015-to-20100525-163047.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #63 on 18-May-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 15:30:12 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 63 - New study on cellphones and cancer, Mayan city uncovered, racism and xenophobia, bio fuels</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100518-153012-to-20100518-163158.mp3" length="59034818" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100518-153012-to-20100518-163158.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #62 on 11-May-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 15:30:03 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 62 - Neanderthal genes in humans, teachers converting to Catholicism, election reform in the UK, interview with The Globe and Mail's Andre Picard</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100511-153003-to-20100511-164520.mp3" length="71961401" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100511-153003-to-20100511-164520.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #61 on 04-May-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 61 - Folk lore pediatricians, the Kludge, Mormon Temple in Langley, Cold Fusion, Deepak Redux</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100504-153000-to-20100504-163300.mp3" length="60141953" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100504-153000-to-20100504-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #60 on 27-Apr-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 60 - Giant animals, sleep studies, cold fusion, Deepak Chopra</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100427-153000-to-20100427-163000.mp3" length="19135841" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100427-153000-to-20100427-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #59 on 20-Apr-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 59 - Skeptical news, taxing churches, racism, coverage of the CFI debates and Rob talks about Brains</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100420-153000-to-20100420-163000.mp3" length="57335960" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100420-153000-to-20100420-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #58 on 13-Apr-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 58 - HST email and Polish conspiracy, interview with Dr. Rob Tarzwell on homeopathy and upcoming debate with Dr. Hugh Ross</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100413-153000-to-20100413-163200.mp3" length="59251658" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100413-153000-to-20100413-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #57 on 06-Apr-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 57 - Skeptic News, Interview with Melany Fulgham on SkeptiCamp 2010, Email on Free speech, Is the Pope a Criminal?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100406-153000-to-20100406-163100.mp3" length="58293392" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100406-153000-to-20100406-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #55 on 23-Mar-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 55 - Our 1 Year Anniversary Episode, Skeptical News, Nuclear Power and Special Guest Elan!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100323-153000-to-20100323-163200.mp3" length="59250407" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100323-153000-to-20100323-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker Episode 54 on 16-Mar-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 54 - Texas has a problem with Thomas Jefferson, Which religious group has the richest members? Doctors need to talk to people more</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100316-153000-to-20100316-163100.mp3" length="58291724" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100316-153000-to-20100316-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #53 on 09-Mar-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 53 - Coverage of the first national CFI Canada Conference</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100309-153000-to-20100309-163100.mp3" length="58292141" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100309-153000-to-20100309-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #52 on 02-Mar-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 15:29:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Episode 52 - Jenny McCarthy, seeing red, space exploration, drake equation</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100302-152900-to-20100302-163000.mp3" length="58292141" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100302-152900-to-20100302-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #51 28-Feb-2010</title><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2010 18:17:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker Special Online Only Episode 51 - The cost of Homeopathy in the UK, Update on Rom Houben, Over population, is it a problem?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100228-181700-to-20100228-191900.mp3" length="59273342" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100228-181700-to-20100228-191900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #50 on 16-Feb-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2010 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 50 - Skeptical news, email on influencing water with thought, is peer review all its made up to be?</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100216-153000-to-20100216-163100.mp3" length="58293809" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100216-153000-to-20100216-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #49 on 09-Feb-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 49 - Whooping cough outbreak, snail/plant hybrid, politics of fear with special guest Chris Erikson</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100209-155900-to-20100209-163400.mp3" length="33457706" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100209-155900-to-20100209-163400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #48 on 02-Feb-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 15:58:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 48 - We're joined with CFI's Justin Trottier to discuss skeptical tribalism and free speech</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100202-155800-to-20100202-163300.mp3" length="33456872" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100202-155800-to-20100202-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #47 on 26-Jan-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 47 - Hour long Olympic's episode, we discuss civil rights, security and media</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100126-153000-to-20100126-163200.mp3" length="59249573" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100126-153000-to-20100126-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #46 on 19-Jan-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 46 - Pub Quiz follow up, lost episode 45, Ignatieff talk at UBC, Slaves didn't build the pyramids</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100119-155900-to-20100119-163300.mp3" length="32500274" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100119-155900-to-20100119-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #44 on 05-Jan-2010</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 44 - Dr. Paul Offit being sued by anti-vaccination groups, Ahead of the curve with Don, Skeptical challenge from Desiree Schell</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100105-155900-to-20100105-163000.mp3" length="29626727" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100105-155900-to-20100105-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #43 on 29-Dec-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2009 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 43 - TSA's new regulations, Skeptical activism with special guest Jesse Brydle</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091229-155900-to-20091229-163100.mp3" length="30584159" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091229-155900-to-20091229-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #42 on 22-Dec-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 42 - Old Cereal,  water on Titan, H1N1 Silver lining, Copenhagan</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091222-155900-to-20091222-163100.mp3" length="30584576" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091222-155900-to-20091222-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #41 on 15-Dec-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 41 - Economics email, the logic of Sonya McLeod, Science reporting vs Science</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091215-155900-to-20091215-163200.mp3" length="31542842" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091215-155900-to-20091215-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #40 on 08-Dec-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 40 - Ecole Polytechnique massacre, the Swiss Ban Minarets, Interview with Justin Trottier</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091208-155900-to-20091208-163200.mp3" length="31542425" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091208-155900-to-20091208-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #39 on 01-Dec-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 15:58:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 39 - We discuss Science and Media with special guest Jennifer Kaban</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091201-155800-to-20091201-163200.mp3" length="32499440" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091201-155800-to-20091201-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #38 on 24-Nov-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com

You can donate by calling 604-822-8648 or at www.citr.ca/donate Great swag awaits you!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 38 - Our Second Fundraising Episode!! Vaccines and poor journalism by the Georgia Straight</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091124-160000-to-20091124-163200.mp3" length="30583742" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091124-160000-to-20091124-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #37  on 17-Nov-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 37 - Our First Fundraising Episode!! Craziness ensues!!  You can donate by calling 604-822-8648 or at www.citr.ca/donate Great swag awaits you!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091117-153000-to-20091117-163300.mp3" length="60207422" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091117-153000-to-20091117-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker #36 on 10-Nov-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2009 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 36 - Carl Sagan Day, more Body Soul and Spirit expo</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091110-155900-to-20091110-163200.mp3" length="31540340" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091110-155900-to-20091110-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 03-Nov-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 15:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 35 - &quot;Ahead of the Curve&quot;, Drug advisor fired, Mind Body and Spirit expo is discussed</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091103-155900-to-20091103-163200.mp3" length="31542425" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091103-155900-to-20091103-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 01-Nov-2009</title><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 20:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 34 - Economic's Special! Topics include bailouts, HST, and Libertarianism vs Liberalism</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091101-200100-to-20091101-210700.mp3" length="63103904" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091101-200100-to-20091101-210700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 01-Nov-2009</title><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 20:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 34 - Economic's Special! Topics include bailouts, HST, and Libertarianism vs Liberalism</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091101-200100-to-20091101-210700.mp3" length="63103904" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091101-200100-to-20091101-210700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 27-Oct-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 33 - Halloween Special! Origins of Halloween, Trick or Treating, Scarey Myths</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091027-155900-to-20091027-163100.mp3" length="30585827" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091027-155900-to-20091027-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 20-Oct-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 32 - &quot;Priming the well&quot;, Placebo effect study, Science and skepticism</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091020-155900-to-20091020-163300.mp3" length="32499440" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091020-155900-to-20091020-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 18-Oct-2009</title><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 20:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 31- Holocaust denial is discussed</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091018-200200-to-20091018-210200.mp3" length="57357227" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091018-200200-to-20091018-210200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 13-Oct-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 30 - Space news, Shroud of Turin, Joseph Stalin's grandson sues newspaper</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091013-155900-to-20091013-163300.mp3" length="32499440" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091013-155900-to-20091013-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 06-Oct-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Check us out online at www.radiofreethinker.com and email us at radio.freethinker@gmail.com</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 29 - Noble Prize thoughts, Ardipithecus ramidus, interview with Steve Thoms</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091006-155900-to-20091006-163300.mp3" length="32498606" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091006-155900-to-20091006-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 29-Sep-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 28 - Anti Vax rally in Vancouver, Global Warming/Climate Change and denial</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090929-155900-to-20090929-163200.mp3" length="31540757" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090929-155900-to-20090929-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 22-Sep-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 27 - A talk on evolutionary psychology, poor journalism by the Georgia Straight</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090922-155900-to-20090922-163300.mp3" length="32499440" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090922-155900-to-20090922-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 15-Sep-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 26 - Today we discuss Scientology with special guest Gerry Armstrong and interviews with Vanonymous</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090915-160000-to-20090915-163100.mp3" length="29592950" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090915-160000-to-20090915-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 08-Sep-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 25 - This week in science, discussion on cults, interview with a cult survivor</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090908-155900-to-20090908-163100.mp3" length="30549965" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090908-155900-to-20090908-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 01-Sep-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 24 - This week in science, Are men funnier than men? , science exams</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090901-155900-to-20090901-163100.mp3" length="30551633" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090901-155900-to-20090901-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freeethinkr on 25-Aug-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 23 - This week in science, email on anti-vax posters, WHO on homeopathy, acupuncture study</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090825-155800-to-20090825-163100.mp3" length="31509065" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090825-155800-to-20090825-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 18-Aug-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 22 - This week in science, email on organic food, debate on Race and Genetics</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090818-155900-to-20090818-163300.mp3" length="32468582" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090818-155900-to-20090818-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 11-Aug-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 21 - Honour Killings, Prayed to death, abortion and captial punishment</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090811-155900-to-20090811-163100.mp3" length="30554135" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090811-155900-to-20090811-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 04-Aug-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 20 - Our first 1 hour show!! Comic-con, Wafergate closure, H1N1 vaccine, copyright laws</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090804-155900-to-20090804-170100.mp3" length="59189525" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090804-155900-to-20090804-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 28-Jul-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 19 - Email on woo-woo convention, Paul Ingraham, Organic food revisited</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090728-155900-to-20090728-163100.mp3" length="30555803" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090728-155900-to-20090728-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 21-Jul-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 18 - Temple of Artemis, Viking map, Eclipse, How bees fly</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090721-155900-to-20090721-163300.mp3" length="32498606" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090721-155900-to-20090721-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 14-Jul-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 17 - Stephen Harper Communion, Miracle in Vancouver, Special Guest Kennedy Goodkey</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090714-155900-to-20090714-163300.mp3" length="32498606" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090714-155900-to-20090714-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 07-Jul-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 15:55:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 16 - Turkish TV Show, Interview with Steve Lundquist and Organic Food</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090707-155500-to-20090707-163200.mp3" length="35372987" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090707-155500-to-20090707-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 30-Jun-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 15 - Michael Jackson conspiracies, interview with Sense about Science, Baloney dection kit</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090630-155900-to-20090630-163300.mp3" length="32489015" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090630-155900-to-20090630-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 23-Jun-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 14 - This day in History, Interview with Rebecca Watson, new internet laws</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090623-155800-to-20090623-163100.mp3" length="31541174" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090623-155800-to-20090623-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 16-Jun-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2009 15:57:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 13 - Shooting at the USHMM, Interview with Chris French, Computers on 24</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090616-155700-to-20090616-163300.mp3" length="34415138" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090616-155700-to-20090616-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 09-Jun-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 12 - This Day in History, Change in Conservative drug policy, Interview with Jon Abrams, the Dali Lama</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090609-155800-to-20090609-163400.mp3" length="34394288" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090609-155800-to-20090609-163400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 02-Jun-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 11 - &quot;In the news&quot;, listener email, Dispatches from a skeptical traveler, part 2 of interview with Phil Plait, Science and Media</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090602-155800-to-20090602-163100.mp3" length="31542425" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090602-155800-to-20090602-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 26-May-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 10 - This day in history, Racist Parents, Part 1 of interview with Phil Plait, Anti-vaccination</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090526-155800-to-20090526-163400.mp3" length="34415555" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090526-155800-to-20090526-163400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 19-May-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2009 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 9 - Conspiracy Convention, Dispatches from a Skeptical Traveler, Morality and Religion</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090519-155800-to-20090519-163000.mp3" length="30583325" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090519-155800-to-20090519-163000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 12-May-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 8 - Email on natural medicine, BC Votes, Ghosts</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090512-160000-to-20090512-163400.mp3" length="32499857" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090512-160000-to-20090512-163400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 05-May-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 15:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 7 - Scopes, Evolution in Alberta, Bill 44, Interview with Elan</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090505-155800-to-20090505-163200.mp3" length="32498189" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090505-155800-to-20090505-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Outakes from 05-May-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 15:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>We accidentaly started the show at 3:30 instead of 4. So we went for around 15 minutes until we realized our mistake.</description><itunes:subtitle>OOPS!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090505-153000-to-20090505-154500.mp3" length="14347013" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090505-153000-to-20090505-154500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 28-Apr-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 6  - Education myths, evaluating medicine, swine flu.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090428-160000-to-20090428-163100.mp3" length="29626727" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090428-160000-to-20090428-163100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 21-Apr-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 5 - Astrology, numerology, naturalpaths prescribing medicine.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090421-160000-to-20090421-163400.mp3" length="32500274" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090421-160000-to-20090421-163400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 14-Apr-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 4 - Evolution and morality in the Bible.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090414-160000-to-20090414-163300.mp3" length="31542425" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090414-160000-to-20090414-163300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 07-Apr-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 3 - Email questions, historical accuracy of Passover, James Randi interview part 3.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090407-160000-to-20090407-163400.mp3" length="32498189" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090407-160000-to-20090407-163400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 31-Mar-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 16:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 2 - U.N. Resolution of &quot;Defamation of Religion&quot;, war on drugs, James Randi interview part 2.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090331-160000-to-20090331-163200.mp3" length="30582491" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090331-160000-to-20090331-163200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Radio Freethinker on 24-Mar-2009</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 15:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A radio show by the UBC Freethinkers club</description><itunes:subtitle>Radio Freethinker episode 1 - Dangers of pot, the Pope and condoms, Canada's science minister, James Randi interview part 1.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090324-155900-to-20090324-163100.mp3" length="30584993" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090324-155900-to-20090324-163100.mp3</guid></item></channel></rss>