<?xml version="1.0"  ?>

	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" ><channel><title>CiTR -- Rumbletone Radio A Go-Go</title><description></description><itunes:summary></itunes:summary><itunes:author>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>Spinnin' Primitive-Fuzzed out-Garage-Sexplosions!!!</itunes:subtitle><itunes:owner> <itunes:name>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:name><itunes:email>technicalservices@citr.ca</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="http://a421.ac-images.myspacecdn.com/00614/02/42/614902420_m.jpg"/><itunes:link rel="image" type="video/jpeg" href="http://a421.ac-images.myspacecdn.com/00614/02/42/614902420_m.jpg">CiTR -- Rumbletone Radio A Go-Go</itunes:link><image><link>http://www.myspace.com/frankrumbletone</link><url>http://a421.ac-images.myspacecdn.com/00614/02/42/614902420_m.jpg</url><title>CiTR -- Rumbletone Radio A Go-Go</title></image><link>http://www.myspace.com/frankrumbletone</link><generator> podcast mate 2000</generator><item><title>30 NOVEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  --Psychobeat-Freakout--</title><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Stompin' to the Psychobeat Freakout with the interview with Mick of The Deadcats and tunes by: THE DEADCATS, THE URGES, THE VOODUO, THE MAXINES, THEE MERRY WIDOWS, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE DRAGS, THE SIN-TONES, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE IRVING KLAWS, THE DEADCATS, THE PROPHYLACTICS, LADIES NIGHT, DEADBOLT, THE KOFFIN KATS, THE BOBBYTEENS, THE SADDLESORES, THE DEADCATS, MAX GREGOR, THE FALLEL BROS., UG AND THE CAVEMEN, LOS SHAINS, DEADCATS, B-MONSTER, THE FIENDS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE BRAINS, THE BELADEANS, THEE AH'S.   ... with The Reverberators and Link Protrudy and his Jay-Men behind my voice.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Sex-plosions!!  with: THE DEADCATS, THE URGES, THE VOODUO, THE MAXINES, THEE MERRY WIDOWS, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE DRAGS, THE SIN-TONES, THE WOLLY BANDITS, THE IRVING KLAWS, THE DEADCATS, THE PROPHYLACTICS,</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111130-150100-to-20111130-170000.mp3" length="113735627" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111130-150100-to-20111130-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>16 NOVEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! --- 'Occupy the Garage'</title><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>'Occupy the Garage' undemocratically brought to you by Rumbletone Radio a-Go-Go featuring: THE SATELLITERS, THE SUPERBEES, WILD BILLY CHILDISH AND THE MBE's, THE MIDWAYS, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE MAXINES, THE SMUGGLERS, THE ZARARY THAKS, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, THE SECRET V's, PUJOL, JUVINELLE HALL, THE WILLOWZ, THE LOVE ME NOTS, ODONIS ODONIS, THE SOUNDS, JO MENT'S HAPPY SOUND, SECRET SQUIRREL AND MOROCO MOLE, HUEVOS RANCHEROS, THE UNTOLD FABLES, THE GROWN-UPS, THE POINTED STICKS, HELLO POLLY, THE EARACHES, THE DREAM SYNDICATE, THE PRIMATES, THE TRESPASSERS, THE EXTERMINATORS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS.  ...with Los StraightJackets in the background.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Sex-plosions!!! - 'Occupy the Garage' with THE SATELLITERS, THE SUPERBEES, WILD BILLY CHILDISH AND THE MBE's, THE MIDWAYS, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE VICIOUS </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111116-150100-to-20111116-170200.mp3" length="115647572" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111116-150100-to-20111116-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>9 NOVEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!.</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 15:25:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Sped-up, Revved-up, Full-throttle Rock'n'Roll Garage Action with: THE GORIES, THE NERVEBREAKERS, THE POLYMORPHINES, THE TRASHIES, MAOW, THE BELADEANS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE SPIVIES, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADES, JACKSON PHIBES, THE TRANZMITORS, THE GOLDEN GATE STRINGS, EMERGENCY, THE BOYS, THE PARALLELS, THE MAXINES, CHAINS OF LOVE, THE BAD VIBRATIONS, NEEDLES//PINS, THE BALLANTYNES, HEADQUARTERS, THE NERVES, RAY BRANDES, B-LINES, THE AUTHORITIES, THE PRABES, ODONIS ODONIS, THE BRAINS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES;  ...and The James T. Kirks in the background behind my voice.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!. - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!. - with THE GORIES, THE NERVEBREAKERS, THE POLYMORPHINES, THE TRASHIES, MAOW, THE BELADEANS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE SPIVIES, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADES, JACKSON PHIBES, THE T</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111109-152500-to-20111109-170200.mp3" length="92707151" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111109-152500-to-20111109-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>2  NOVEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!.</title><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The Perv-a-sonic, sex-plosive sounds of: THE BEAT KILLERS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, CHEAP TIME, THE SPANKS, THE TASMANIANS, NEEDLES//PINS, COLOUR ME PSYCHO, THE IRVING KLAWS, THE FARREL BROS., THE LOVE CUTS, B-LINES, THE EVAPORATORS, THE BAD VIBRATIONS, THE BENT SCEPTERS, THE BOTTOMLESS PIT, THE IRRITATIONS, THE CRUSADERS, INDIAN WARS, THE SATISFACTION, THE PRABE, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, REAL ESTATE, LIVING MARIMBAS, MONDO TOPLESS, THE NERVE BREAKERS, THE CREEPY CREEPS, THE TVees, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, RICH HOPE AND HIS EVIL DOERS, THE SPECTERS, THE NASHVILLE RAMBLERS, MANUAL SCAN, THE FUNSEEKERS, THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE CAVEMANISH BOYS, THE CANADIAN SQUIRES, 1977. (with The Mag Four and The James T. Kirks behind my voice)</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!. - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!. - with: THE BEAT KILLERS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, CHEAP TIME, THE SPANKS, THE TASMANIANS, NEEDLES//PINS, COLOUR ME PSYCHO, THE IRVING KLAWS, THE FARREL BROS., THE LOVE CUTS, B-LINES, THE </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111102-150100-to-20111102-170200.mp3" length="115647572" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111102-150100-to-20111102-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>26  OCTOBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio au Ghoul-Ghoul !!  presents Spook-a-rama!</title><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Doin' the Graveyard Stomp to the scary monster hits of: THE GROOVIE GHOULIES, THE COFFIN SHAKERS, SOUTHERN CULTURE ON THE SKIDS, THE GRUESOMES, THE INCREDIBLE STAGGERS, THE FIENDS, THE KEYTONES, THE MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE DEADCATS, THE CANNIBLES, THE FUZZTONES, KING DAPPER COMBO, THE PANDORAS, THE PLEASURE SEEKERS, THE WORST, THE HOODS, ROB ZOMBIE with THE GHASTLY ONES, THE MISFITS, B-MONSTER, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, DO-RE-MI CHILDRENS CHORUS, MR. GASSER &amp; THE WIERDOS, THE HILLBILY VARMINTS, THE HOLLYWOOD FLAMES, BLOODDHOT BILL, THE MANSFIELDS, THE KNURLINGS, THE FIENDS, SCREAMING LORD SUTCH, GRAVEDIGGER V, BLACK EYES AND NECKTIES, THE FUZZTONES, THE SWINGIN' NECKBREAKERS,THE 3-D INVISIBLES, THE REVILLOS, THE STEMS, JAMES DUHON, THE WORST, THE FIENDS.   ...with The Ghastly Ones in the background.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Ghoul-Ghoul !! -Scary, Spooked-up, Monster Hex-plosions!!  with: THE GROOVIE GHOULIES, THE COFFIN SHAKERS, SOUTHERN CULTURE ON THE SKIDS, THE GRUESOMES, THE INCREDIBLE STAGGERS, THE FIENDS, THE KEYTONES, THE MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE DE</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111026-150100-to-20111026-170400.mp3" length="117563270" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111026-150100-to-20111026-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>19  OCTOBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>That's not mold, IT'S GREEN FUZZ!!! with Voices Green &amp; Purple by: THE ULTRA 5, LINDY BLASKEY and The LAVELLS, NEEDLES//PINS, THE EXPLODING HEARTS, CHAINS OF LOVE, THE GROWN-UPS, THE NERVES, THE FIENDS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, HOLLY GO-LIGHTLY, THE SADIES, THE PROPHYLACTICS, THE LOVE CUTS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE PRABES, SISTER LOVERS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THEE PIRATES, YUNG MUMS, SIR JULIAN, LIZ BRADY, GREG ARCADE, THE DIABOLIKS,  ALTHEA AND THE MEMORIES, THE LOONS, BLONDEWICH, THE THINGZ, THE CARPET SELLERS, THE EVE OF SOUND, THE EMBROOKS, THE TRASHIES, THE FALLEN LEAVES, THEE VICARS, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE SPHINXS, THE POINTED STICKS THE BRAINS..  with the instrumental sounds of IMPALLA.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!! - with: THE ULTRA 5, LINDY BLASKEY and The LAVELLS, NEEDLES//PINS, THE EXPLODING HEARTS, CHAINS OF LOVE, THE GROWN-UPS, THE NERVES, THE FIENDS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, HOLLY GO-LIGHTL</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111019-150300-to-20111019-170000.mp3" length="111817427" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111019-150300-to-20111019-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>12  OCTOBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!.</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 15:13:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Primortial screams, busted tambourines and broken guitar strings from the likes of THE TRELIKS, THE URGES, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, RUBY AND HIS ANGELS, KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, LOVE CUTS, THE MAKES NICE, THE FIENDS, THE VOODUO, THE POLYMORPHINES, CHEAP TIME, THE REAL LOSERS, THE STONEAGE HEARTS, AUTHORITIES, THE BON, THE LONG RIDERS, THE FOUR FOURS, THE PACK A.D., DICK DIA, THE GUANA BATZ, THE UGLY BEATS, B-LINES, DUM DUM GIRLS, THE STATIC JACKS, TRANZMITORS, THE JOLTS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE OMENS, THE WILDEBEASTS, THE BUG NASTIES, DEAN KOHLER, THE FUGITIVES, BLONDEWICH, MARTIN DENNY. ...with The Men from S.P.E.C.T.R.E. in the background.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!. - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!. -- THE TRELIKS, THE URGES, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, RUBY AND HIS ANGELS, KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, LOVE CUTS, THE MAKES NICE, THE FIENDS, THE VOODUO, THE POLYMORPHINES, CHEAP TIME, THE RE</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111012-151300-to-20111012-170100.mp3" length="103219721" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111012-151300-to-20111012-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>05  OCTOBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!.</title><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Gettin' it On with the In-Set and the Outcasts with shindigin' tunes by: THE FIENDS, THE LYRES, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE GREENHORNES, LOS SAICOS, LOVE CUTS, MON OR ASTROMAN, THE SPITS, THE MINDS, THE TRANZMITORS, POLYMORPHINES, THE SPECTRES, THE MIRACLE WORKERS, THE BRAINS, STICHES, THE ISOTOPES, THE GOLDEN LEMONS, B-MONSTER, BILLY STRANGE, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, THE THANES, THOSE DARLINS, B-MONSTER(int), THE CHAINS, THE MUMMIES, THE SICK ROSE, THE TONICS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE JOLTS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE PLASTIC CLOUD! ...and in the background Los StraightJackets.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!. - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!. -- Gettin' it On with the In-Set and the Outcasts with shindigin' tunes by: THE FIENDS, THE LYRES, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE GREENHORNES, LOS SAICOS, LOVE CUTS, MON OR ASTROMAN, THE SP</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111005-150300-to-20111005-170300.mp3" length="115430732" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111005-150300-to-20111005-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>28  SEPTEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>SO-CAN ya dig the fuzz? SO-CAN ya rave it up! SO-CAN ya pay the bandz that deserve it alot? Dig It! ..with: THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE WORST, THE POINTED STICKS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, FUN 100, B-LINES, THE LEATHER UPPERS, THE BON, THE VINDICATORS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE TRANZMITORS, MAOW, THE FIENDS, THE VON ZIPPERS, THE SATELLITERS, NEEDLES//PINS, THE VOODUO, GIRLS, BILLY STRANGE, SWANK, THE CHEEPSKATES, THE 3 O'CLOCK, THE EVAPORATORS, THE JOLTS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE LOVE CUTS, BLACK EYES AND NECKTIES, THE MORLOCKS, THE PRIMATES, RIFF RANDELLS, TIME COPZ, B-MONSTER, THE LOONS, THE JAZZ BUTCHER, THE LAUNDRONAUTS and in the background THE TREBLEMAKERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!. - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!. -- SO-CAN ya dig the fuzz? SO-CAN ya rave it up!  Dig It! with: THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE WORST, THE POINTED STICKS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, FUN 100, B-LINES, THE LEATHER UPPERS, THE BO</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110928-150000-to-20110928-170000.mp3" length="114666371" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110928-150000-to-20110928-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>21  SEPTEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzie, modie, trashie, twistie, shimmie &amp; shakie soundz by: THE CREEPS, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, THE BEAT KILLERS, CHEAP TIME, THE BLOCKED, RIDE THEORY, YOUNG RIVAL, THE PARALLELS, THE REAL PILLS, THE CURTAINS, TRANZMITORS, INDIAN WARS, WILD BILLY CHILDISH AN D THE MBE's, THE WIPEOUTERS, B MONSTER, THE SWELL MAPS, THE TRASHIES, HARLEM, LOS HIPPIE-LOYAS, THE HOODS, BATTLESNAKES, THE ROYAL BLUE, THE BRISTOLS, LOS 3 SUDAMERICANOS, YOUNG RIVAL (with an interview), THE BANGLES, THE BOBBYTEENS, JUVENILE HALL, CHAINS OF LOVE, PROPHYLACTICS, THE PACK A.D.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  -- Fuzzie, modie, trashie, twistie, shimmie &amp; shakie soundz by: THE CREEPS, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, THE BEAT KILLERS, CHEAP TIME, THE BLOCKED, RIDE THEORY, YOUNG RIVAL, THE PARALLE</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110921-150000-to-20110921-170200.mp3" length="116584154" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110921-150000-to-20110921-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>14  SEPTEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Outta the garage and into the circus! Fuzzy-bumblin' clown-antix by: THE GREEN HORNETS, THE FIENDS, THE MARKED MEN, THE SPLIT-UPS, THEE FINE LINES, B-MONSTER, UNDER THE BIG TOP, RAISED BY WOLVES, THEE CRUCIALS, PAWNEE DRIVE, THE DEL-VETTS, THE JOLTS, THEE FOURGIVEN, THE HEADLESS HORSEMEN, THE STEMS, THE SIGHTS, THE SMUGGLERS, TRANZMITORS, EMERGENCY, BEASTS OF BOURBON, THE SEEDS LADYTRON, BUTTHOLE SURFERS, THE NERVE BREAKERS, THE HOODS, CUBY AND THE BLIZZARDS, CHAINS OF LOVE, THE BON, THE EXTERMINATORS, THE TUNESPINNERS, THE TEMPLARS, UNDER THE BIG TOP, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE POINTED STICKS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  -- Fuzzy-bumblin' clown-antix by: THE GREEN HORNETS, THE FIENDS, THE MARKED MEN, THE SPLIT-UPS, THEE FINE LINES, B-MONSTER, UNDER THE BIG TOP, RAISED BY WOLVES, THEE CRUCIALS, PAWN</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110914-150200-to-20110914-170200.mp3" length="114690974" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110914-150200-to-20110914-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>7  SEPTEMBER  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz-a-delic, Tone-Benders by: THE WOOLLY BANDITS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THEE VICARS, THE TIKI TONES, THE SATISFACTION, LES MINSTRELS, CHEAP TIME, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE RUINERS, ROYAL GRAND PRIX, THE WIGS, SOUTHERN CULTURE ON THE SKIDS, B MONSTER, THE CRYPTONES, THE BLUESTARS, SURFERS de LOS CAMPONES, THE GUESS WHO, THE MONKS, THE EVAPORATORS, FUN 100, MR GASSER AND THE WEIRDOS, B-LINES, DICK DIA, DEADBOLT, THE UNCLAIMED, FENWYCK, CHAINS OF LOVE, THE TEMPLARS, B-LINES, THE MONKS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, THE BON, THE TRANZMITORS, THE HORRORS, PLEASURE SUIT, TEEN ANGEL.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  -- Fuzz-a-delic, Tone-Benders by: THE WOOLLY BANDITS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THEE VICARS, THE TIKI TONES, THE SATISFACTION, LES MINSTRELS, CHEAP TIME, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE RUINERS, ROY</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110907-150200-to-20110907-170300.mp3" length="115649240" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110907-150200-to-20110907-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>31  AUGUST  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Mods'n'GarageRockers with: THE FUZZTONES, STUPOR STARS, THE THICK SHAKES, JERRY AND THE LANDSLIDES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, SECRET SQUIRREL AND MOROCCO MOLE, THE VOODUO, THE SCOUTS, THE GRUESOMES, I CINQUE MONELLI, B MONSTER, BABY WOODROSE, THE MAGGOTS, THE SWAMP RATS, CHAINS OF LOVE, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE ETTES, THE SPANKS, B MONSTER, THE FIBONACCIS, NIKITA THE K, THE NELSONICS, THE SHARPSHOOTERS, THE RAYDERS, THE TVees, THE SHAMBLES, THE NASHVILLE RAMBLERS, THE RESONARS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE BARE WIRES, THE FALL-OUTS, THE DECIBELS, NERVEBREAKERS, THE EXOTICS, DAVILA 66, BLACK EYES AND NECKTIES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!!  -- Mods'n'GarageRockers with: THE FUZZTONES, STUPOR STARS, THE THICK SHAKES, JERRY AND THE LANDSLIDES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, SECRET SQUIRREL AND MOROCCO MOLE, THE VOODUO, THE SCOUT</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110831-150200-to-20110831-170300.mp3" length="115542905" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110831-150200-to-20110831-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>24  AUGUST  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Outta the cave and into your living-room! w/ THE DUKES OF HAMBURG, THE SIN-TONES, THE HATEBOMBS, THE BON, THOSE DARLINS, THE MISTREATED, CEREBRAL BALLZY, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, LOS YAKI, THE EVAPORATORS, SECRET SQUIRREL AND MOROCCO MOLE, THE ORANGE ALABASTER MUSHROOM, THE DOWN'N'OUTS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, HUNX AND HIS PUNX, THE TONICS, WHEELS ON FIRE, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE HORRORS, CLAUDE DENJEAN AND HIS MOOG, THE CLONES, THE CHORDS, HEADQUARTERS, TRANZMITORS, UNDERCOVER, THE OUTSIDERS, THE WAILERS, THE FLAKES, B-MONSTER, THE WEIRDIES, B-MONSTER, THE JESSICA FLETCHERS, PINEAPPLE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!! --  Outta the cave and into your living-room! w/ THE DUKES OF HAMBURG, THE SIN-TONES, THE HATEBOMBS, THE BON, THOSE DARLINS, THE MISTREATED, CEREBRAL BALLZY, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, LOS Y</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110824-150000-to-20110824-170500.mp3" length="119327597" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110824-150000-to-20110824-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10  AUGUST  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Power-popin' Fuzz-drenchers by: MONDO TOPLESS, THE BEAT KILLERS, LOS STRAIGHTJACKETS, THE TRELIKS, NEEDLES/PINS, THE BELADEANS, THE NERVES, THE NERVE BREAKERS, THE POINTED STICKS, JFA, THE TELL TALE HEARTS, THE DEADLINES, TRANZMITORS, THE BON, THE WEIRDIES, THE DELMONAS, THE B-LINES, RALPH CARMICHAEL, THE ZINEDINES, THE PRIESTS, THE EXTERMINATORS, SHANNON AND THE CLAMS, THE DESPONDANTS, THE NASHVILLE RAMBLERS, SATURN V featuring ORBIT, THE SPANKS, KING SALAMI, THE BREAKAWAYS, THE GROOVIE GHOULIES, THEE MERRY WIDOWS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE JIGSAW SEEN, THE THINGZ.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!! --- Power-popin' Fuzz-drenchers by: MONDO TOPLESS, THE BEAT KILLERS, LOS STRAIGHTJACKETS, THE TRELIKS, NEEDLES/PINS, THE BELADEANS, THE NERVES, THE NERVE BREAKERS, THE POINTED STICK</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110810-150300-to-20110810-170000.mp3" length="111817427" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110810-150300-to-20110810-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>20 JULY  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!.</title><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Take the hip tyme trip with cranked-up, fuzzed-up, shin-kickers by: THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE GO-NUTS, SHUTDOWN 66, THE CHAINS, THE NERVBREAKERS, THE VOODUO, THE 3-D INVISIBLES, THE THICK SHAKES, THE DWARVES, RON DRAND ORCHESTRA, THE SATELLITERS, THE GORE GORE GIRLS, SOUTHERN CULTURE ON THE SKIDS, THE ZIPPS, WHITE LUNG, JAMES LAST, RAISED BY WOLVES, CHRIS &amp; TAD, QUINTRON &amp; MISS PUSSYCAT, NO FUN, POINTED STICKS, THE FRESH AND ONLYS, HARLEM HIPPIES, LES SEXERENOS, MONGROL'S BAND, THE LAUNDONAUTS, TRANZMITORS, UNDERCOVER, GUSTOV TEMPLE &amp; THE BLADES, THE SHINDIGGERS, THE SHILOHS, THE GRAVEDIGGER 5, THE WORST, CHAINS OF LOVE, YOUNG RIVAL.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!. ---  Take the hip tyme trip with cranked-up, fuzzed-up, shin-kickers by: THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE GO-NUTS, SHUTDOWN 66, THE CHAINS, THE NERVBREAKERS, THE VOODUO, TH</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110720-150300-to-20110720-170500.mp3" length="116607089" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110720-150300-to-20110720-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>13 JULY  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!.</title><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz-adelica, Distorto, Shimmy-shakin' Garage Action with: THE MAGGOTS, THE MOPS, THE CYNICS, LES BREAST-FEEDERS, LES TERRIBLES, THEE VICARS, THE MAKES NICE, THE MIDWAYS, THE INSOMNIACS, THE MIGHTY CAESARS, THE WERDIES, CHAINS OF LOVE, THE DIRT BOMBS, DOCTOR's EXPLOSION, THE PUSSYCATS, THE NOMADS, THE CORDS, THE UGLY BEATS, THE TRANZMITORS, B-MONSTER, THE WAIKIKIS, THE LOONS, THEW VICIOUS CYCLES, LES HELL ON HEELS, HUNX AND HIS PUNX, JUVINILE HALL, B-MONSTER, THE GIRLS, BLONDEWICH, MOVIE STAR JUNKIES, THOSE DARLINS, THE FLESHTONES, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE EXTERMINATOR, MR. GASSER &amp; THE WEIRDOS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!. --- Fuzz-adelica, Distorto, Shimmy-shakin' Garage Action with: THE MAGGOTS, THE MOPS, THE CYNICS, LES BREAST-FEEDERS, LES TERRIBLES, THEE VICARS, THE MAKES NICE, THE MIDWAYS, THE I</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110713-150200-to-20110713-170400.mp3" length="116607506" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110713-150200-to-20110713-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>6 JULY  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Revved-up Romps &amp; Stomps  and  Gearing-up for the Odd Ball with: THE PANDORAS, THEE CRUCIALS, LES BREAST-FEEDERS, THE BARRACUDAS, THE SMUGGLERS, THEE VICARS, KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, THE BEAT KILLERS, THE TIJUANA BIBLES, THE LEATHER UPPERS, THE BON, THE NERVE BREAKERS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THEE OH NO's, THE WEIRDIES, THE EVAPORATORS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, PLASTICLAND, GIRL TROUBLE, THE LIVING DEADBEATS,  SHEARING PINX, YUNG MUMS, THE STRUGGLERS, LITTLE GUITAR ARMY, THE EAST VAMPS, THE LIQUOR KINGS, THE FIENDS, SLOW POKE AND THE SMOKE, THE POINTED STICKS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!! --- Revved-up Romps &amp; Stomps  and  Gearing-up for the Odd Ball with: THE PANDORAS, THEE CRUCIALS, LES BREAST-FEEDERS, THE BARRACUDAS, THE SMUGGLERS, THEE VICARS, KING KHAN AND THE S</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110706-150200-to-20110706-170400.mp3" length="116605838" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110706-150200-to-20110706-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>29 JUNE  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shimmy-shakin', Fuzz-rattlin', Reverb-soakin', Garage-bustin' with: THE MIRACLE WORKERS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE SPECTORS, THE HIVES, THEE VICARS, CROCODILES, SURF CITY, THE PRETTY THINGS, THE GREEN TELESCOPE, NIGHT CRAWLERS, THE FROWNING CLOUDS, THE OTHERS, SHANNON AND THE CLAMS, THE BOOBY TRAPS, THE EXPLODING HEARTS, BABY WOODROSE, THE GOLDEN LEMONS, THE STAGGERS, WASTED LIVES, THE ORANGU-TONES, THE REAL KIDS, YUNG MUMS, THE OUTDOORSMEN, C'MON, THE BEAT KILLERS, B-LINES, LOS SHAINS, LOS PEYOTES, THE NERVE BREAKERS, THE SADIES, THE POINTED STICKS, THE BARACUDAS, THE MONKEES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!!     --Shimmy-shakin', Fuzz-rattlin', Reverb-soakin', Garage-bustin' with: THE MIRACLE WORKERS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE SPECTORS, THE HIVES, THEE VICARS, CROCODILES, SURF CITY, THE P</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110629-150200-to-20110629-170400.mp3" length="116607506" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110629-150200-to-20110629-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>15  JUNE  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>60's Garage Puck Rock</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110615-145900-to-20110615-170400.mp3" length="119456450" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110615-145900-to-20110615-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>8  JUNE  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz, Flakes &amp; 60's Shakes!! -- Extra! Extra! Little Guitar Army invades CITR plus tunes by: THE SATILLITERS, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADERS, THE BLACK LIPS, NO BUNNY, SUPERNOVA, THE TVees, THE BEAT KILLERS, THE BREADMAKERS, MARK SULTAN, THE LOONS, RICH HOPE AND HIS EVIL DOERS, THE THICK SHAKES, HUEVOS RANCHEROS, THE GRUESOMES, THE TRANZMITORS, THE WASPS, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE EVAPORATORS, LITTLE GUITAR ARMY, HOT BUTTER, THE WIPEOUTERS,  THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE WEIRDOS, THE UPPER CRUST, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, REDD KROSS, LITTLE GUITAR ARMY, THE POINTED STICKS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  with: THE SATILLITERS, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADERS, THE BLACK LIPS, NO BUNNY, SUPERNOVA, THE TVees, THE BEAT KILLERS, THE BREADMAKERS, MARK SULTAN, THE LOONS, RICH HOPE AND HI</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110608-150300-to-20110608-170300.mp3" length="114690140" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110608-150300-to-20110608-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>1  JUNE  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Youth Gone Wild... featured in Every Mother's Nightmare-- staring in 'Garage-mainia' with performances by: GIRL TROUBLE, THE STUPER STARS, MONSTERS FROM MARS!, THE STONAGE HEARTS, THE SPECTORS, THOSE DARLIN'S, PRETTY VANILLA, THE REAL PILLS, THE BELADEANS, LES BREASTFEEDERS, THE LYRES, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, THE VINDICATORS, HUNX AND HIS PUNX, THE FALL-OUTS, THE UGLY BEATS, THE FIENDS,  LUCIANO, THE VOODUO, THE LIME SPIDERS, WILD BILLY CHILDISH AND THE MBE's, THE BEAT KILLERS, THE BLACK DIAMONDS, THE NASHVILLE RAMBLERS, THE MISSUNDERSTOOD, THE NEW CREATION, SIT &amp; SPIN, LOS EXPLOSIVOS!, THEE VICARS, B-LINES, THE SMUGGLERS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE MYSTEROUS TAPEWORMS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  with:  GIRL TROUBLE, THE STUPER STARS, MONSTERS FROM MARS!, THE STONAGE HEARTS, THE SPECTORS, THOSE DARLIN'S, PRETTY VANILLA, THE REAL PILLS, THE BELADEANS, LES BREASTFEEDERS, THE </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110601-150200-to-20110601-170300.mp3" length="115648823" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110601-150200-to-20110601-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>31   MAY  2011 -- Bryce-Bryce au Go-Go!! --filling in for Third Time's the Charm</title><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 09:30:00 -0700</pubDate><description>All Bryce! All the Time!!
Spinnin' THE VINDICATORS, THE SMUGGLERS, NEW TOWN ANIMALS, THE TRANZMITORS</description><itunes:subtitle>Filling in for Third Time's the Charm -- All Bryce!  All the Time!!   --Spinnin' THE VINDICATORS, THE SMUUGGLERS, NEW TOWN ANIMALS, THE TRANZMITORS .</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110531-093000-to-20110531-113000.mp3" length="114671375" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110531-093000-to-20110531-113000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25   MAY  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Organ-pulsing, skin-pounding, string-strumming and maniacal-screaming (or singing) by: THE PRISONERS, NELSON RIDDLE, THE MIDWAYS, THE BELADEANS, LEO AND THE PROPHETS, THE WILLOWZ, THE STINKIES, THE WHITE WIRES, THE VOODUO, THE UGLY BEATS, THE HIGH DIALS, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE EYES, THE SPECTERS, TEE AND THE CRUMPETS, THE VIBRATING BEDS, SUMMER CATS, THE SIN-TONES, THE THINGZ, SHARON JONES AND THE DAP-KINGS, THE KAZOO BROTHERS, PERRY &amp; KINGSLEY, THE SCRAMBLERS, TEENGENERATE, GUITAR WOLF, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, MONIQUE THUBERT, THE NASHVILLE RAMBLERS, THE BARRACUDAS, THE NEW CREATION, THE NASHVILLE RAMBLERS, THE PRIMITIVES, THE SPANKS, CHEEP TIME, THE BEAT KILLERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  with: THE PRISONERS, NELSON RIDDLE, THE MIDWAYS, THE BELADEANS, LEO AND THE PROPHETS, THE WILLOWZ, THE STINKIES, THE WHITE WIRES, THE VOODUO, THE UGLY BEATS, THE HIGH DIALS, THE GR</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110525-150200-to-20110525-170200.mp3" length="114690557" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110525-150200-to-20110525-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>18   MAY  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>DeeKlein Radio with Dave Klein and the Garage Explosion! featuring: THE GO-NUTS, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE BEGILED, VOODUO, THE UGLY BEATS, THE PANDORAS, JACKIE AND THE CEDRICS, THE THICK SHAKES, SKY SAXON AND FIREWALL, THE FUZZTONES, THEE CRUCIALS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE GREENHORNES, THE FINKS, THE UNTOLD FABLES, SHANNON AND THE CLAMS, THE INVISIBLE EYES, AGENT ORANGE, LOS CORVETS, THE BOMBORAS, THE GO-NUTS, THE LEGENDARY INVISIBLE MEN, THE FINKS, THE WITCH DOCTORS, THE LEGENDARY INVISIBLE MEN, AGENT ORANGE, CHAINS OF LOVE, CHEAP TIME.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  with: an interview with Dave Klein of Agent Orange and a million great garage bands plus-THE GO-NUTS, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE BEGILED, VOODUO, THE UGLY BEATS, THE PAN</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110518-145900-to-20110518-170400.mp3" length="119456867" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110518-145900-to-20110518-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>11   MAY  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shakin' some fuzz fantastic with: THE URGES, THE STEMS, THE BOBBYTEENS, HUNX AND HIS PUNX, THE HEARTACHES, SUN WIZARD, THE LOONS, THE VINDICATORS, THE SPITS, THEE CRUCIALS, THE B-LINES, THE HUMAN EXPRESSION, THE WALKING SCREAMS, THE MAKES NICE, LES BREASTFEEDERS, THE NERVES, THE PLEASURE SUIT, THE GREENHORNES, MOOG GROOVE, THE VOODUO, THE ETTES, DEADBOLT, THE BRAINS, THE CRIPPLE CREEK FAIRIES, THE TRAP DOORS, 84 ROOMS, CHEAP TIME, GIRLS NAMES, THE PLAYMATES, GUITAR WOLF, THE JOLTS, AGENT ORANGE, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE SHAKE UPS, WIRE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!!  with: THE URGES, THE STEMS, THE BOBBYTEENS, HUNX AND HIS PUNX, THE HEARTACHES, SUN WIZARD, THE LOONS, THE VINDICATORS, THE SPITS, THEE CRUCIALS, THE B-LINES, THE HUMAN EXPRESSION</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110511-150200-to-20110511-170200.mp3" length="114689723" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110511-150200-to-20110511-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>4   MAY  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz-drenched, Pop-Riveted Garage Pounders with:
THE UNTAMED YOUTH, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, LOS EXPOSIVOS, THE BROOD, THE POINTED STICKS, THE UGLY BEATS, THE RELATED SEGMENTS, THE FLYS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE UNCLAIMED, B-LINES, POISON 13, THE BLOODY HOLLIES, THE SPLIT-UPS, EDDIE AND THE HOTRODS, WE THE PEOPLE, THE BELADEANS, HOT BLOOD BOMBERS, EDDIE AND THE HOTRODS, MAX GREGOR, THE HATE BOMBS, THE VOODUO, THE CHAINS, SHANNON AND THE CLAMS, LOS BICHOS, THE SECRET V's, SOMETHING FIERCE, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE PRIMA DONNAS, LES BREASTFEEDERS, BILLY CHILDISH AND THE MBE's, THE FAMOUS MONSTERS, THE BONITOS, TV IDOLS, EDDIE AND THE HOTRODS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! - Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!!  with: THE UNTAMED YOUTH, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, LOS EXPOSIVOS, THE BROOD, THE POINTED STICKS, THE UGLY BEATS, THE RELATED SEGMENTS, THE FLYS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE UNCLAIMED, B-LINES,</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110504-150200-to-20110504-170200.mp3" length="114690974" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110504-150200-to-20110504-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>27  APRIL  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>ShAkE sOmE AcTiOn at Party au Go-Go with:
THE PRIMORDIALS, THE ODD NUMBERS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE WORST, THE SURF COASTERS, THE UGLY BEATS, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY, THE 5 CANADIANS, THE DRAGS, LOS SAICOS, THE VIBRATING BEDS, THE SICK ROSE, THE OUTSIDERS, THE LUST-O-RAMA, THE OUTSIDERS, THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE WIERDIES, REDD KROSS, THE BLACK ANGLES, JAMES LAST, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE STOMACH MOUTHS, THE PENETRATIONS, SUN WIZARD, JUVENAL HALL, THE BELADEANS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE POINTED STICKS, LOS MOCKERS, THE THICK SHAKES, THE UNTOLD FABLES, THE THINGZ.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! -Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!!  with: THE PRIMORDIALS, THE ODD NUMBERS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE WORST, THE SURF COASTERS, THE UGLY BEATS, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY, THE 5 CANADIANS, THE DRAGS, LOS SAICOS, THE VIBRATING BEDS, </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110427-150300-to-20110427-170200.mp3" length="113733959" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110427-150300-to-20110427-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>20  APRIL  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Wyld_Frantic_Crazed_Raw Garage-Stompers! plus an interview with Billy Bones of The Vicious Cycles and tunes by:
THE MAGGOTS, WHEELS ON FIRE, BOTUMLESS PIT, NO BUNNY, THE GREENHORNES, THE UGLY BEATS, THE TVees, THE WHITE WIRES, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE AARDVARKS, THE ORANGE ALABASTER MUSHROOM, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE BEES, THE POINTED STICKS, THE JOLTS, THE MUMMIES, THE BLACK ANGLES, LOS YAKI, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE MANTS, BLACK EYES AND NECKTIES, THE LEGENDARY INVISIBLE MEN, THE TRANZMITORS, WHITE LUNG, SKATERHATER.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! -Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!!  with:THE MAGGOTS, WHEELS ON FIRE, BOTUMLESS PIT, NO BUNNY, THE GREENHORNES, THE UGLY BEATS, THE TVees, THE WHITE WIRES, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE AARDVARKS, THE ORANGE ALABASTER MUSHRO</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110420-150100-to-20110420-170100.mp3" length="114690140" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110420-150100-to-20110420-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>13  APRIL  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The Jet-set are go! meet The Rebel Kind with:
THE FUZZTONES, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, THE EX-BOYFRIENDS, THE FIENDS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, LOS SAICOS, THE NUTHIN'S, MONDOTOPLESS, THE VIBRATING BEDS, BBQ, THE FARREL BROS., ELDORADO, THE LOONS, TRANZMITORS, THE BREAKAWAYS, THE CAVEMANISH BOYS, THE PIPETTES, SURF CITY, DIZZY EYES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE CREEPY CREEPS, THE VOODUO, THE MORLOCKS, YUNG MUMS, CRYSTAL STILTS, THE SEEDS, SOMETHING FIERCE, HUNX AND HIS PUNX, THE GO-DEVILS, THOSE DARLINS, TRANZMITORS, THE FIENDS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! -Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  with: THE FUZZTONES, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, THE EX-BOYFRIENDS, THE FIENDS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, LOS SAICOS, THE NUTHIN'S, MONDOTOPLESS, THE VIBRATING BEDS, BBQ, THE FARREL BROS., ELDORADO, TH</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110413-150100-to-20110413-170100.mp3" length="114712241" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110413-150100-to-20110413-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>6  APRIL  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tripped-up Twang tossed with Fuzzed-up Reverb served Go-Go style. Today's receipe included: MONDO TOPLESS, THE HARA-KEE-REES, THE ETTES, THE CRAWDADDYS, THE LOONS, THE HEATSCORES, HARLEM, THE WEIRDIES, THE SPITS, TH' LOSIN' STREAKS, THEE CRUCIALS, THE VOODUO, THE UGLY BEATS, THE BELADEANS, THE MATADORS (Czech), THE THINGZ, THE SHITBIRDS, EX-BOYFRIENDS, THE BENT SCEPTERS, THE OMENS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, LOS YAKI, GUNSMOKE, THE MISTEATERS, LES BREASTFEEDERS, TRANZMITORS, THE TONICS, THE SCIENTISTS, THE SUNSETS, THE NOTEKILLERS, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, THE NEW CREATION, WHEELS ON FIRE, SPEEDBALL BABY, EX-BOYFRIENDS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! -Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  with: MONDO TOPLESS, THE HARA-KEE-REES, THE ETTES, THE CRAWDADDYS, THE LOONS, THE HEATSCORES, HARLEM, THE WEIRDIES, THE SPITS, TH' LOSIN' STREAKS, THEE CRUCIALS, THE VOODUO, THE UGL</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110406-150100-to-20110406-170200.mp3" length="115647989" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110406-150100-to-20110406-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>30  MARCH  2011 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Back in action! The far-out soundz of full-bored 6Ts high octane R'n'R with bad brakes!! In the 8-track player: DOCTOR EXPLOSION, THE MADADORS, THE URGES, THE PRIMATES, THE VOODUO, BLACK EYES AND NECKTIES, THE GRUESOMES, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE ZEROS, THE BLOWHOLES, THE DUKES OF HAMBURG, JOHN WESLEY COLEMAN, THE UGLY BEATS, HEADQUARTERS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE WASPS, THE DODOS, LOS FREDDYS, THE NERVES, THE STRANGE MAGIC, THE STEMS, THE THANES, DEAD GHOSTS, EVE HELL AND THE RAZORS, THE NEW CREATION, THE EVAPORATORS, THE LOONS, THE BELADEANS, SPECTRES, AGENT ORANGE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! -Primative, Fuzzed-up, Garage Sex-plosions!!  with DOCTOR EXPLOSION, THE MADADORS, THE URGES, THE PRIMATES, THE VOODUO, BLACK EYES AND NECKTIES, THE GRUESOMES, LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE ZEROS, THE BLOWHOLES, THE DUKES OF HAMBURG, JOH</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110330-150200-to-20110330-170300.mp3" length="115647155" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20110330-150200-to-20110330-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>1 DECEMBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 15:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Distorto-spazz-fuzz-rock-au-go-go with special guest Bob Scott of The Mongrel Zine and tunes by:
THE FLAKES, THE BELADEANS, THE FUCK KNIGHTS, ROSS SERGOTHER, DEMON'S CLAWS, MANIC ATTRACTS, THE POINTED STICKS, B-LINES, THE SPREADS, S.C.U.M., JACK OF HEARTS, SHIMMERING HEARTS, TY SEGALL, GOLDEN CATALINAS, RICHARD CATWRANGLAR, THE TRAP DOORS, THE TANDOORI KNIGHTS, THE EVAPORATORS, TOPLESS MONGOS, BUMMER HIGH, DEAD GHOSTS, THE JOLTS, PERSONAL AND PIZZAS, THE OUTDOORSMEN, YUNG MUMS, RED MASS, PERSIAN CLAWS, DEMON'S CLAWS, THE GROOVIE GHOULIES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!!  with: THE FLAKES, THE BELADEANS, THE FUCK KNIGHTS, ROSS SERGOTHER, DEMON'S CLAWS, MANIC ATTRACTS, THE POINTED STICKS, B-LINES, THE SPREADS, S.C.U.M., JACK OF HEARTS, SHIMMERING HEA</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101201-150300-to-20101201-170200.mp3" length="113732708" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101201-150300-to-20101201-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>17  NOVEMBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !</title><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>FunDrive-FunDrive-FunDrive!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!' -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! -FunDrive</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101117-150000-to-20101117-170000.mp3" length="114675962" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101117-150000-to-20101117-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10  NOVEMBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Reverbed, twanged, drugged, revved, gassed, tilted, greased Rock'n'Roll with:
THE IRVING CLAWS, THE DRAGS, THEE OH NOs, NOBUNNY, THE MAKES NICE, THE KAISERS, THE BLACK ANGLES, THE DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, THE ORANGE ALABASTER MUSHROOM, THE FROWNING CLOUDS, THE ORPHEANS, THE RUINERS, THE SHIMMYS, GRANDMA'S TONIC, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, LOS CHICOS, THE FARRELL BROS., THE CAVE SINGERS, TERRY BAXTER, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE SALVATION ARMY, THE INSOMNIACS, THE SPLIT-UPS, REDD KROSS, THE PERSIAN RUGS, THE CHEEKS, THE LUCKY ONES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE WHAT FOR, THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE FRAT KINGS, B-LINES, THE CHECKERS, THE TAMRONS, PERREY &amp; KINGSLEY.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!' -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  with: THE IRVING CLAWS, THE DRAGS, THEE OH NOs, NOBUNNY, THE MAKES NICE, THE KAISERS, THE BLACK ANGLES, THE DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, THE ORANGE ALABASTER MUSHROOM, THE FROWNING CLOUD</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101110-150100-to-20101110-170100.mp3" length="114660116" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101110-150100-to-20101110-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>03  NOVEMBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Ass stompin' Garage thumpers with: LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE BALLOON FARM, THE URGES, THE RAYMEN, THE EVAPORATORS, THE HIGH DIALS, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY, SKY SAXON AND FIREWALL, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, FEAR OF LIPSTICK, THE ZEROS, B-LINES, THE OMENS, THE LEN PRICE 3, THEE CRUCIALS, THE MIDWAYS, THE CANNIBALS, THE SPECTRES, NASHVILLE PUSSY, DINO, DESI &amp; BILLY, CHRIS &amp; TAD, THE CHAINS, THE LUCKY ONES, JAMES T. KIRKS, GABRIEL AND HIS ANGELS, NOBUNNY, INTOXICA, THE MESS MAKERS, KNUCKLEHEAD, THE BOOBY TRAPS, 10 FOOT FACES, CHARGERS STREET GANG, THE UGLY BEATS, THE GRAVEDIGGER V, THE DRIVING STUPID.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  with: LOS EXPLOSIVOS, THE BALLOON FARM, THE URGES, THE RAYMEN, THE EVAPORATORS, THE HIGH DIALS, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY, SKY SAXON AND FIREWALL, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, FEAR OF LIPSTICK, THE </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101103-150000-to-20101103-170000.mp3" length="114668039" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101103-150000-to-20101103-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>27  OCTOBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'</title><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Rumbletone Radio a Ghost-Ghost: a hollow-weenie fuzz-tacular with Ben Frith of Neptoon Records/Thee Manipulators and tunes by: THE GHASTLY ONES, NOBUNNY, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE WEEDS, MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE RIPPERS, THE MAKERS, THE DWARVES, BLACK BELLES, THE KNURLINGS, NICK CURRENT &amp; THE LOW LIFES, THE DEADCATS, ROKY ERICKSON, LOS PEYOTES, THE WORST, ROY ETZEL &amp; HIS BAND, THE CRAMPS, THE 3-D INVISIBLES, THE MYSTERONS, LUV MACHINE, THE LIZARD PEOPLE, THE PANDORAS, THE SONICS, THE BEGILED, THE WICKED ONES, THE A-BONES, DEADBOLT, GRAVEYARD, THE FIENDS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'  -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  with: THE GHASTLY ONES, NOBUNNY, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE WEEDS, MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE RIPPERS, THE MAKERS, THE DWARVES, BLACK BELLES, THE KNURLINGS, NICK CURRENT &amp; THE LOW LIFE</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101027-150100-to-20101027-170400.mp3" length="117580784" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101027-150100-to-20101027-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>20  OCTOBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'</title><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>It's more than a mod, mod world. It's a mod-garage-fuzzadelic freakout! -Baby! Today an interview with Jarrod of The Parallels playing ultra-rare, unreleased Parallels' songs!! Plus tunes by:
THE HOODS, THE BUG NASTIES, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE GREEN TELESCOPE, NO BUNNY, THE EPOXIES, THE VASELINES, THE THREE O'CLOCK, PRETTY VANILLA, THE SHAKEUPS, Q 65, FRANKIE ROSE AND THE OUTS, THE BLACK ANGLES, THE ORPHEANS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE PRISONERS, THE PARALLELS, SIR JULIAN, THE PRISONERS, SIR JULIAN, THE SMOKE, THE PARALLELS, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, THE BIRDS, THE PARALLELS, THE CLONES, THE PARALLELS, THE FIENDS, THE PARALLELS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'  -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  with</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101020-150000-to-20101020-170300.mp3" length="117493631" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101020-150000-to-20101020-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>13  OCTOBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This ain't no tie-dye hippy hour! It's ass kickin', boot stompin', fuzz-tromental garage-pounders with THE GHASTLY ONES, LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE FORTY FIVES, THE ZAKARY THAKS, DEAD BOLT, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE BLACK LIPS, THE DOUBLEHAPPYS, THE PRETTY THINGS, OPAL, THE SADIES, THE SHINOLAS, THE GIRLS, THE MURDER CITY DEVILS, THEE FINE LINES, THE MOTARDS, THE RUINERS, SIT'N'SPIN, THE GRUESOMES, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCT, HEALTHY STUDENTS, HIGH SCHOOL SWEETHEARTS, LOVE, THE FLESHTONES, THE ORPHEANS, THE PACK AD, NOBUNNY, THE VASELINES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  with: THE GHASTLY ONES, LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE FORTY FIVES, THE ZAKARY THAKS, DEAD BOLT, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE BLACK LIPS, THE DOUBLEHAPPYS, THE PRETTY THINGS, </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101013-150100-to-20101013-170000.mp3" length="113731457" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101013-150100-to-20101013-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>6  OCTOBER  2010 -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Take the hip time trip with the fuzz-bustin',organ-poundin', rattle-knockin', garage-shakin' 6T's soundz of Rumbletone Radio a go-go!!!  (!!! outta !!!!) Shake it baby, shake it!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  -Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101006-150000-to-20101006-170000.mp3" length="114668039" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20101006-150000-to-20101006-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>29 SEPTEMBER  2010  -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'</title><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz drenched, keg-a-rama grooviness with:
sandro brugnolini, united states of existence, green hour band, the paybacks, the others, the ruiners, the resonars, the nerves, nobunny, poison 13, the black angels, os mutantes, the spaceshits, the makes nice, thee manipulators, the laundronauts, intelligence, the heatscores, murder city devils, the sin-tones, the original sins, dead bolt, fresh and onlys, crystal swells,lord beginners, the fairies, crocodiles, the chains, bbq, oviatt brothers, the mystic eyes, thee vicars.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!' Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with sandro brugnolini, united states of existence, green hour band, the paybacks, the others, the ruiners, the resonars, the nerves, nobunny, poison 13, the black angels, os mutante</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100929-150200-to-20100929-170100.mp3" length="113716445" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100929-150200-to-20100929-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>22  SEPTEMBER  2010  -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'</title><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Summer-endin' Fuzzed-up Freak-out with:
THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, TH' LOSIN' STREAKS, THE PRIMORDIALS, BBQ, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE UGLY DUCKLINGS, THE INVISIBLE EYES, THE BOSS MARTIANS, LUIGI LOPEZ, THE STEMS, THE EASYS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE RUINERS, THE DEADLY SNAKES, MONSTERS FROM MARS!, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY, CRYSTAL SWELLS, THEE FOURGIVEN, THE SPITS, THE WASPS, THE BRIEFS, LADIES NIGHT, LOS SAICOS, THE GRANNY SMITHS, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCT, BABES ON THE BEACH, B-LINES, THE CREEPY CREEPS, THE BLACK ANGLES, THE DOWN'N'OUTS, THE VASELINES, PINEAPPLE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!' Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, TH' LOSIN' STREAKS, THE PRIMORDIALS, BBQ, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE UGLY DUCKLINGS, THE INVISIBLE EYES, THE BOSS MARTIANS, LUIGI LOPEZ, THE STEMS, THE EASYS,</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100922-150200-to-20100922-170100.mp3" length="113730623" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100922-150200-to-20100922-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>8  SEPTEMBER  2010  -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'   with The Zeros Interview!</title><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 03:22:27 -0700</pubDate><description>4-3-2-1 ZEROS!  It's all about THE ZEROS -baby! The whole show centered around THE ZEROS!  with their friends &amp; cohorts:
THE WEIRDOS, THE BARRACUDAS, THE NERVES, THE POINTED STICKS, THE SALVATION ARMY, THE ZEROS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, ZOLAR X, THE DICKIES, DEVO, THE ZEROS, THE BREAKAWAYS, JAVIER ESCOVEDO, THE LAST, THE CRAWDADDYS, THE MYSTERY MACHINE, THE HOODS, THE ZIP GUNS, LOS DILLY SISTERS, THE ZEROS, THE TREBLES, THE NOMADS, THE WIGS, THE ZEROS, THE ELECTRIC CHAIRS, THE FAST, THE 101ers, THE SAINTS, NO FUN, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, THE ZEROS interview.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!' Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with an interview with The Zeros and tunes by: THE WEIRDOS, THE BARRACUDAS, THE NERVES, THE POINTED STICKS, THE SALVATION ARMY, THE ZEROS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, ZOL</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100916-032227-to-20100916-054000.mp3" length="131456876" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100916-032227-to-20100916-054000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on Sept 15 2010</title><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 15:00:44 -0700</pubDate><description></description><itunes:subtitle>Gareth &amp; Bryce fill in for the hour!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100915-150044-to-20100915-160353.mp3" length="60375473" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100915-150044-to-20100915-160353.mp3</guid></item><item><title>01  SEPTEMBER  2010  -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!'</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shake, Rattle and Roll with the wyld, primeval soundz of:
THE WOGGLES, THE LIPSTICK KILLERS, THE TRESPASSERS, THE MINSTRELS, THE RIDE THEORY, LOS SAICOS, THE DEL MONAS, THE SHAKEUPS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE MURDER CITY DEVILS, THE GIRLS, THE ZEROS, THE HUMPERS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE UNTOLD FABLES, THE SCENICS, THE NEKROMANTIX, THE CLONES, THE SPLIT-UPS, THE DOWNLINERS SECT, ELECTRIC FRANKENSTEIN, THE FURYS, TRANZMITORS, DEFEKTORS, SEX CHURCH, THE RUINERS, OUTRAGEOUS CHERRY, YOUNG RIVAL.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!' Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with:  THE WOGGLES, THE LIPSTICK KILLERS, THE TRESPASSERS, THE MINSTRELS, THE RIDE THEORY, LOS SAICOS, THE DEL MONAS, THE SHAKEUPS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE MURDER CITY DEVILS, THE GI</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100901-150000-to-20100901-170100.mp3" length="115622135" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100901-150000-to-20100901-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25  AUGUST  2010  -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!'</title><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Full-tilt, Revved-up, Big Muff, Wall of Fuzz Action with:
THE SUPER STARS, THE URGES, LOS PEYOTES, TH' LOSIN STREAKS, FORTUNE AND MALTESE, THE INVADERS, THE WICKED ONES, THE CHECKERS, BIG BOBBY &amp; THE NIGHTCAPS, LOS SAICOS, THE EVAPORATORS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE RESONARS, THE DRAGS, MIESHA &amp; THE SPANKS, THE WYLDE MAMMOTHS, SPEEDBALL BABY, THE CYBERMEN, THE MAKES NICE, THE ORPHEANS, MOOG GROVE, THE VERDICTS, THEE CRUCIALS, THE KILL-A-WATS,THE ANGTY SAMOANS, VAPID, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE GRANNY SMITHS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE BUSINESS, THE ZIP GUNS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, THEE MANIPULATORS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!' Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with: THE SUPER STARS, THE URGES, LOS PEYOTES, TH' LOSIN STREAKS, FORTUNE AND MALTESE, THE INVADERS, THE WICKED ONES, THE CHECKERS, BIG BOBBY &amp; THE NIGHTCAPS, LOS SAICOS, THE EVAPOR</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100825-150200-to-20100825-170400.mp3" length="116605838" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100825-150200-to-20100825-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>11  AUGUST  2010  -- Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Demented, Twanged, Reverbed, Swaggered, Jolted, Fuzzed R'n'R with:
THEE CRUCIALS, POISON 13, OVERNIGHT LOWS, THE MUMMIES, THE BUSINESS, THE BREAKAWAYS, THE MAD 3, THE WIPEOUTERS, THE TRELIKS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE MORNING SHAKES, ZOLAR X, THE UPPER CRUST (Boston), THE UPPER CRUST (Vancouver), THE FIENDS, THE MAKERS, THE WEATHERED PINES, LOS ROCKIN' DEVILS, ALEX CHILTON, THE NOMADS, MARBLE ORCHARD, THE MONO MEN, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, JUNIOR MAJOR, YOUNG RIVAL, SWANK, THE WEATHERED PINES interview.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  with:  THEE CRUCIALS, POISON 13, OVERNIGHT LOWS, THE MUMMIES, THE BUSINESS, THE BREAKAWAYS, THE MAD 3, THE WIPEOUTERS, THE TRELIKS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE MORNING SHAKES, ZOLAR X, THE U</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100811-150200-to-20100811-170400.mp3" length="116605838" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100811-150200-to-20100811-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>04  AUGUST  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 15:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz-adelic, Garage-busters by:
THE SATELLITERS, THEE ULTRA BIMBOOS, THE BLOODY HOLLIES, HARALD RAY LIVE IN CONCERT, THE SONICS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE DOWNLINERS SECT, THE CHIMPS, THE DIPLOMATS OF SOLID SOUND, RE-VOLTS, BEAU-DENTURES, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE SPLIT UPS, B-LINES, THE BUSINESS, THE 13TH FLOOR ELEVATORS, THE CYNICS, THE MAGIC PLANTS, THE HIGHBALLS, THE DESTINATIONS, D &amp; T, THE CUTE LEPPERS, STATIC STATIC, FRANTIC CITY, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, LOS EXPLOSIVES, THE MOURNING AFTER, THE HANGEE V, DEFEKTORS, WAX MANNIQUIN, MOOSEHEART FAITH, ANGRY SAMOANS, THE SHADES, THE FIVE BY FIVE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  with: THE SATELLITERS, THEE ULTRA BIMBOOS, THE BLOODY HOLLIES, HARALD RAY LIVE IN CONCERT, THE SONICS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE DOWNLINERS SECT, THE CHIMPS, THE DIPLOMATS OF SOLID SOUND, RE-</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100804-150400-to-20100804-170100.mp3" length="111817427" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100804-150400-to-20100804-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>28 JULY  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Knockin' over Hippies with Fuzz, Reverb, &amp; busted Maracas!! This Ain't No Sandal-Rock Baby! It's: THE LOVE ME NOTS, LES SEXAREENOS, THE EXPLODING HEARTS, THE OTHERS, REDD KROSS, BATTLE SNAKES, DURANGO 95, THE BOBBYTEENS, THE NE'ER DO WELLS, TERRY KNIGHT AND THE PACK, THE BOSS MONSTERS, THE LEATHER UPPERS, THE PRIMATES, THE SHANDELLS, KING KHAN &amp; BBQ, WILLIE ALEXANDER, THE OHIO EXPRESS, THE YOUNG SAVAGES, THE YOUNG CANADIANS, THE HYPSTERZ, INDIAN WARS, THE LOSIN' STREAKS, THE JOLTS, DEAD GHOSTS, LIKE ANIMALS AGAIN, THE ZIP GUNS, THE KARTOONS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THEE VICARS!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! Today we're Knockin' over Hippies with Fuzz, Reverb, &amp; busted Maracas!! This Ain't No Sandal-Rock Baby! It's: THE LOVE ME NOTS, LES SEXAREENOS, THE EXPLODING HEARTS, THE OTHERS, REDD</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100728-150100-to-20100728-170300.mp3" length="116605838" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100728-150100-to-20100728-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>21 JULY  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Summer Sweltering Roughneck Garage Pounders with:
THE GET QUICK, THE MIDWAYS, LARRY AND THE LOAFERS, LOS SHAKERS, THE CLAMOUR, MARK SULTAN, THE CHORDS, THE REAL KIDS, THE SOLARFLARES, THE HOLY SOUL, LORDS OF ALTAMONT, HIGH SCHOOL SWEETHEARTS, MARBLE ORCHARD, THE CHESSMEN, SONORA SCOTCH, THE GOODNIGHT LONG SUPPER CLUB, GOLDIE WILSON, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, 64 FUNNY CARS, LAWRENCE WELK, THE EPOXIES, IT'S ALL MEAT, THE PANDORAS, FRANCE GALL, MONIQUE THAUBART, THEE SPIVIES, DAVE DEE DOZY..., THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE OBITS, THE STOLEN MINKS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, AUTO-LITE STRIKE, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, THE SCOUNDRELLES, THE THANES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with:  THE GET QUICK, THE MIDWAYS, LARRY AND THE LOAFERS, LOS SHAKERS, THE CLAMOUR, MARK SULTAN, THE CHORDS, THE REAL KIDS, THE SOLARFLARES, THE HOLY SOUL, LORDS OF ALTAMONT, HIGH SCH</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100721-150000-to-20100721-170100.mp3" length="115625471" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100721-150000-to-20100721-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>14  JULY  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>All mucked-up with nowhere to go? Then get down'n'dirty the Rumbletone way with: MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE PARKADES, SHUTDOWN 66, INTOXICA, THE BUG NASTIES, BATTLE SNAKES, AGENT ORANGE, THE EVAPORATORS, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE DETROIT COBRAS, THE HELLBOUND HEPCATS, THE SUBURBAN NIGHTMARE, INDIAN WARS, THE PERSIAN RUGSA, THE SHARPSHOOTERS, THE POINTED STICKS, THE MISSING LINKS, ALTHEA AND THE MEMORIES, 64 FUNNY CARS, KLAUS WUNDERLICH, THE ALOHAS, THE DIRTBOMBS, THE PRIVATE SEA OF DREAMS, THE PIERCED ARROWS, THE MAGNETIC IV, THEE MANIPULATORS, MAKEOUT VIDEOTAPE, THE B-LINES, JJ PEARSON, THE POINTED STICKS, THE BRIEFS, THE TREBLEMAKERS, THE KRONJIG DEVILS, DEVO.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with: MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE PARKADES, SHUTDOWN 66, INTOXICA, THE BUG NASTIES, BATTLE SNAKES, AGENT ORANGE, THE EVAPORATORS, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE DETROIT COBRAS, THE HELLBOUND HEPC</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100714-150100-to-20100714-170100.mp3" length="114690140" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100714-150100-to-20100714-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>07  JULY  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>WORLD CUP A-GO-GO! Dutch, Spanish and German garage featured along with: THE MAGGOTS, Q65, SMOKIE, THE FAB, THE HARE-KEE-REES, MAOW, SEX MUSEUM, LOS SALVAJES, THE SIN-TONES, THE POINTED STICKS, TRANZMITORS, THE NELSONICS, THE BARRACUDAS, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE SAINTS, LES PROBLEM, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE BEATDOWN, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, AART BROEWER AND THE CELLAR ROCKS, THE BLUE STARS, THE GOLDEN LEMONS, LOS SONAMBULOS, THE UNTAMED YOUTH THE GO-NUTS, THE SWINGIN' NECKBREAKERS, THE OUTSIDERS, THE WAILERS, THE CREEPY CREEPS, GERRY ALVEREZ ODYSSEY, COBY &amp; THE BLIZZARDS, THE MERCURY FOUR, THE AGGROLITES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with: WORLD CUP A-GO-GO! Dutch, Spanish and German garage featured along with: THE MAGGOTS, Q65, SMOKIE, THE FAB, THE HARE-KEE-REES, MAOW, SEX MUSEUM, LOS SALVAJES, THE SIN-TONES, TH</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100707-150100-to-20100707-170200.mp3" length="115648406" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100707-150100-to-20100707-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>30  June  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Wyld tymes with the likes of:
THE STEMS, THE APACHES, THE BOOBY TRAPS, THE PRIESTS, THE SQUARES, THE GREEN CIRCLES, OUTRAGEOUS CHERRY, THE LYRES, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADE, THE MIGHTY CAESARS, ANDRE WILLIAMS, THE ORPHEANS, THE ZEROS, THEE FOURGIVEN, THE CARAVELLES, ZOLAR X, TEDDY AND HIS PATCHES, JUNIOR MAJOR, OBITS, TOMORROW'S KEEPSAKES, THE SCRAMBLERS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE BUSINESS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THEE INSENSIBLE EGGS, THE TEST PATTERNS, THE DOWN'N'OUTS, THE SHIMMYS, THE BREAKAWAYS, THE SCREAMIN' FURYS, THE B-LINES, THE MUNKS, RANGERS SOUND, I CINQUE MONELLI, DEVO, THE AGGROLITES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!! Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! with: THE STEMS, THE APACHES, THE BOOBY TRAPS, THE PRIESTS, THE SQUARES, THE GREEN CIRCLES, OUTRAGEOUS CHERRY, THE LYRES, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADE, THE MIGHTY CAESARS, ANDRE WI</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100630-150000-to-20100630-170200.mp3" length="116584988" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100630-150000-to-20100630-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>23  June  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!</title><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>THE SATELITERS, THE A-BONES, THE TVees, THE BROOD, THE CLONES, SIR LANCE A LOT, THE INVISIBLE EYES, LOS MAYEN ZIODES, THIS MOMENT IN BLACK HISTORY, THE POINTED STICKS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, LOVE, GIRL TROUBLE, THE PARALLELS, PLASTICLAND, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE SEEDS, THE GRAVE MISTAKES, DIZZY EYES, THE SICK ROSE, THEE OH NOs, THE LUNA RIOT, DEVO.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  Foot Stompin',  Goal Scorin'  Red Cardin'  a go-go with: THE SATELITERS, THE A-BONES, THE TVees, THE BROOD, THE CLONES, SIR LANCE A LOT, THE INVISIBLE EYES, LOS MAYEN ZIODES, THIS MOMENT IN BLACK HISTORY, THE POINTED STICKS, </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100623-150000-to-20100623-170300.mp3" length="117542420" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100623-150000-to-20100623-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>16  June  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The sounds of busted strings, shattered tambourines and wailin' screams!!! Courtesy of: THE FLESHTONES, SUPERNOVA, THE REAL PILLS, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, BATTLE SNAKES, THE GRUESOMES, PEABODY HERMITAGE, FORTUNE AND MALTESE, POINTED STICKS, THE HEXTALLS, THE BOMBORAS, 3-D INVISIBLES, THE UNINVITED, THE FIENDS, THE WINDOW PAYNES, THE ERE OF SOUND, RAY COLUMBUS, THE ZOMBIE IV, SLEEPY SUN, JAMES LAST, THE SONICS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE STOMACH MOUTHS, DIZZY EYES, THE JOLTS, THE BELEDEANS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, HOT LIVE GUYS, DEVO!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! --The sounds of busted strings, shattered tambourines and wailin' screams!!! Courtesy of: THE FLESHTONES, SUPERNOVA, THE REAL PILLS, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, BATTLE SNAKE</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100616-150200-to-20100616-170300.mp3" length="115647989" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100616-150200-to-20100616-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>09  June  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE STONEAGE HEARTS, THE SADDLESORES,ELDORADO, DESOTO REDS, THE JESSICA FLETCHERS, RIDE THEORY, YOUNG RIVAL, POINTED STICKS, ARMITAGE SHANKS, LOS GRIMM, LOS MONSTUOS, DELMONAS, CRIMSON SHADOWS, BEAT PACK, THE WHAT FOUR, SONIC AVENUES, THE CLEAN, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE GET DOWN, THE BROOD, THE NAME LOSERS, THE ORPHEANS, THE OUTSIDERS, A, B &amp; C.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE STONEAGE HEARTS, THE SADDLESORES,ELDORADO, DESOTO REDS, THE JESSICA FLETCHERS, RIDE THEORY, YOUNG RIVAL, POINTED STICKS, ARMITA</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100609-150200-to-20100609-170400.mp3" length="116605004" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100609-150200-to-20100609-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>02  June  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>THE BOSS MARTIANS, THE PERCOLATORS, THE EARACHES, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE GROOVIE GHOULIES, THE APACHIES, THE DRAGS, B-LINES, THE SATELLITERS, POINTED STICKS, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCTS, THE RAWDYMEN, THE MUMMIES, THE MUNKS, THE PERVERTS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, LOS AARGHS!, AL HIRT, LES SINNERS, THE ALOHAS, LOS SERFERS, THE MYSTIC EYES, THE SADIES, THE BARE WIRES, BIVAROS, KING KHAN &amp; BBQ, THE TRAP DOORS, DIZZY EYES, TRANZMITORS, THEE MANIPULATORS, NEEDLES//PINS, CLEAR LIGHTS, YOUNG RIVAL.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! THE BOSS MARTIANS, THE PERCOLATORS, THE EARACHES, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE GROOVIE GHOULIES, THE APACHIES, THE DRAGS, B-LINES, THE SATELLITERS, POINTED ST</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100602-150000-to-20100602-170200.mp3" length="116583320" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100602-150000-to-20100602-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>26 May  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2010 15:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>GIRL TROUBLE, THE PRISONERS, CLAWHAMMER, THE REAL LOSERS, THE MAKERS, YOUNG RIVAL, HOODOO GURUS, RIFF RANDELLS, THE BON, THE DELMONAS, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY AND THE BROKEOFFS, THE PUSSYCATS, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE BUTCHERS, RAY ANTHONY AND THE BOOKENDS, YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, THE PHANTOMS, THE WOGGLES, THE URGES, THE MISCREANTS, CINNAMON FLYING PEOPLE, DEFEKTORS, JUVENILE HALL, PIERCED ARROWS, THE ORPHEANS, BUZZCOCKS, TRANZMITORS, LES MISERABLES, THE TELEPATHIC BUTTERFLIES, THE JIGSAW SEEN, THE LUNA RIOT.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  Mayhem by: GIRL TROUBLE, THE PRISONERS, CLAWHAMMER, THE REAL LOSERS, THE MAKERS, YOUNG RIVAL, HOODOO GURUS, RIFF RANDELLS, THE BON, THE DELMONAS, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY AND THE BROKEOFFS, </itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100526-150400-to-20100526-170300.mp3" length="113732291" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100526-150400-to-20100526-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>19  May  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Gareth of The Laundronauts makes another special appearance. With tunes by: THE LEGENDARY INVISIBLE MEN, THE KRONTJONG DEVILS, LORDS OF GRAVITY, THE EMBROOKS, THE MAGGOTS, THE STOLEN MINKS, THE SUPER BEES, LES SEXAREENOS, JUST TOO MUCH, THE VON ZIPPERS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE MONSTERS, EDGAR ALLEN AND THE PO BOYS, THE NIGHT KINGS, THE TONICS, THE BRAINS, 1313 MOCKINGBIRD LANE, THE CAVEMANISH BOYS, THE B-LINES, MAOW, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, HARMONICATS, SANDRO, DIK VAN DYKES, MARK SULTAN, CRIMSON SHADOWS, THE SEEDS, WHITE LUNG, LET'S DANCE, THE STOMACH MOUTHS, THE SADIES, THE VOLCANOES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE BUG NASTIES, THE ORPHEANS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! -Gareth of The Laundronauts makes another special appearance. With tunes by: THE LEGENDARY INVISIBLE MEN, THE KRONTJONG DEVILS, LORDS OF GRAVITY, THE EMBROOKS, THE MAGGOTS, THE STOL</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100519-150100-to-20100519-170300.mp3" length="116606255" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100519-150100-to-20100519-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>12  May  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>With special guest Gareth of the Laundronauts, and tunes by:
SURFERS de los CAMPONES, THE DIRTBOMBS, THE EVAPORATORS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE FALL, THE ODD NUMBERS, THE GRUESOMES, THE BLACK HOLLIES, MARK SULTAN, S.C.O.T.S., LOS HOLYS, WILLY WONKA, CLEAR LIGHT, DUKES OF STRATOSPHEAR, SHOUT OUT LOUDS, THE VENTURES, THE HATES, LOS PEYOTES, LOS TEENAGERS, THE ORPHEANS, BOATS, INDIAN WARS, ELEMENT 79, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE DRASTICS, THE STRANGLERS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, TRANZMITORS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions! !  With special guest Gareth of the Laundronauts, and tunes by: SURFERS de los CAMPONES, THE DIRTBOMBS, THE EVAPORATORS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE FALL, THE ODD NUMBERS, THE GRUESOMES, THE B</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100512-150000-to-20100512-170300.mp3" length="117536582" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100512-150000-to-20100512-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>28 April  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>THEE MANIPULATORS, THE GOLDSTARS, THE OUTSIDERS, THE DWARVES, AWESOME COLOR, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE BRIEFS, THE STEMS, THE NERVES, THE TUNESPINNERS, THE BLACK HOLLIES, THE DUKES OF STRATOSPHERE, THREE 4 TENS, KALEIDOSCOPE, THE EXOTICS, THE WOLLY BANDITS, RAY COLUMBUS, LENNY DEE, LOS GATOS SALVAJES, THE HEATSORES, THE FLAKES, THE SHARPSHOOTERS, PURPLE MERKINS, THE WOODEN SHIJPS, THE ORPHEANS, THE LONG RYDERS, MARK SULTON, THE BON, BLOODSHOT BILL, GRAND TRINE, THEE ULTRA BILBOOS, PETROLEUM BY-PRODUCT.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  Primative, Fuzzed-up,  Garage Sex-plosions!  Featuring: THEE MANIPULATORS, THE GOLDSTARS, THE OUTSIDERS, THE DWARVES, AWESOME COLOR, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE BRIEFS, THE STEMS, THE NERVES, THE TUNESPINNERS, THE BLACK HOLLIES, TH</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100428-150200-to-20100428-170100.mp3" length="113732291" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100428-150200-to-20100428-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>21 April  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Power-Pop a Go-Go!!! Special two hours of Power-Pop from 1976-1986 with guest Pete Fiend (The Living Deadbeats) from his 'Poppers' 8 volume mixtape series.
Featuring:
THE YOBS, THE BEAT, JILTED JOHN, POINTED STICKS, THE FINKS, THE FLYS, THE VIBRATORS, SPIZZENERGI, THE SCIENTISTS, THE 101ERS, THE ROUSERS, THE FORGOTTEN REBELS, THE DOLL, WHITE HEAT, WRECKLESS ERIC, SALFORD JETS, THE FINKS, RED CROSS, THE QUICK, HAZEL O'CONNER, COCK SPARRER, THE REZILLOS, THE SWINGER, THE UNKNOWNS, KLARK KENT, THE SECRET V's, TINA PEEL, NASTY FACTS, THE EXTRAS, THE BANGS, POP DETECTIVES, THE DOGS, ACTION NOW.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  Primative, Fuzzed-out,  Garage Sex-plosions!1976-1986 with guest Pete Fiend (The Living Deadbeats) from his 'Poppers' 8 volume mixtape series. Featuring: THE YOBS, THE BEAT, JILTED JOHN, POINTED STICKS, THE FINKS, THE FLYS, T</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100421-150100-to-20100421-171000.mp3" length="123277838" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100421-150100-to-20100421-171000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>14 April  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>More trippin' the fuzz fantastic with:
THE GREEN HORNETS, THE DIRTBOMBS, THE MAKERS, THE SATELLITERS, YOUNG RIVAL, THOMAS FUNCTION, THEE OH NOs, THE 5 TORQUAYS, THE VIPERS, 5 AMERICANS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE FRESH &amp; ONLYS, THE STRANGLERS, THE BREADMAKERS, THE CRUSADERS, THE DEADCATS, HOLLY GOLIGHTLY, THE PANDORAS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE EVAPORATORS, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCT, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE JOLTS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE ORPHEANS, DEAD GHOSTS, PHANTOM SURFERS AND DAVIE ALLEN, INDIAN WARS, THE CLAMOUR, THE MIRACLE WORKERS plus an hour with The Shabby Shiek.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-out,  Garage Sex-plosions!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100414-150200-to-20100414-175200.mp3" length="162468332" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100414-150200-to-20100414-175200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>07 April  2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shakin' the dust off yer Beatle Boots with Fuzz Bustin' Garage Action!
Plus interviews with the Laundronauts and The James T. Kirks and tunes by:
THE MIDWAYS, LOS SAICOS, THE WOLLY BANDITS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE STOLLEN MINKS, LES TERRIBLES, THE ROOKS, PLASTICLAND, THE HITS, RAMBLIN' AMBASSADORS, THE PARKADES, THE ORANGE ALIBASTOR MUSHROOM, THE VINDICATORS, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, CRAZY OTTO, THE OPTIC NERVE, THE WORST, SERFERS DE LOS CAMPEONS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, B-LINES, KARMA DEL SUTRA, THE URGES, THE AARDVARKS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE LOONS, TWANGZILLA, THE PRPHEANS, RICH HOPE, TRANZMITORS, THE UGLY BEATS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS plus 30 minutes of a new program called Shabby Shiek.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-out,  Garage Sex-plosions!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100407-150100-to-20100407-180000.mp3" length="171066038" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100407-150100-to-20100407-180000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>24 March 2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Full-tilt Garage Action to sweat you up!!!  Featuring:
LOS SHAINS, THE FLESHTONES, THE SATISFACTION, CHRISTIAN D &amp; THE HANGOVERS, THE MARKED MEN, PIERCED ARROWS, THE UPPER CRUST, REDD KROSS, THE SALVATION ARMY, POINTED STICKS, LOS HOLYS, THE BEGILED, THE REAL LOSERS, THE CHORDS, THE NERVES, THE CLAMOUR, THE SPLINTERS, THE SHIMMYS, THE MOODDOGGIES, JAMES LAST, YOUNG FRESH FELLOWS, THE BRISTOLS, SIT &amp; SPIN, GOLDEN TRIANGLE, THE MORNING BENDERS, WHITE LUNG, SWANK, THE MIXTURES, THEE MANIPULATORS, LOS VIDRIOS QUEBRADOS, LOS JUANITOS, HARLEM.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-out,  Garage Sex-plosions!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100324-150300-to-20100324-170400.mp3" length="115693025" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100324-150300-to-20100324-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>17  March 2010  -Hosting Ska-T's Scenic Drive</title><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 10:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Ska, Ska and more Ska. Back to my roots with:
THE SLACKERS, CHRIS MURRAY, THE ISRAELITES, ONE NIGHT BAND, THE SELECTER, THE EXPOS, BIM SKALA BIM, THE PIETASTERS, ARTHER KAY AND THE ORIGINALS, RUDE CITY RIOT, THE SPECIALS, EASY BIG FELLA, JUDGE DREAD, MADNESS, THE TOASTERS, PHATTY PHATTY AND THE ROACHES, RED EYE EMPIRE, MOBTOWN, BIG D AND THE KIDS TABLE, THE UNTOUCHABLES, THE VALUABLES, MAD BOMBER SOCIETY, THE KING PINS, SUBCITY DWELLERS, LOS FURIOS, THE SLACKERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Ska-T's Scenic Drive hosted by Frank Rumbletone</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100319-100100-to-20100319-120200.mp3" length="115637147" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100319-100100-to-20100319-120200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>17  March 2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>St. Patty's Green Fuzz soaked Garage Swill!! -with rompers by: THE INSOMNIACS, THE PRISONERS, THEE MANIPULATORS, LOS ASS DRAGGERS, THE OMENS, THE BLACK HOLLIES, THE STEMS, THE PILLS, ROCKIN' ROADRUNNERS, THE BENT SCEPTERS, THE EVAPORATORS, EAST VAMPS, 3-D INVISIBLES, THE LIVING DEADBEATS plus interview with DeadPete Fiend, THE HI-FIVES, MUCK AND THE MIRES, SONIC AVENUES, LOS APSON,  THE BARRACUDAS, CURSE OF THE HORSEFLESH, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE LUNA RIOT, THE JIGSAW SEEN, THE OKMONIKS, THE MINDS, PETROLEUM BY-PRODUCT, THE GHASTLY ONES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, OVER NIGHT LOVER, THE JOLTS, B-LINES, BUD &amp; KATHY, TRANZMITORS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  Primative, Fuzzed-out,  Garage Sex-plosions!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100317-150000-to-20100317-170200.mp3" length="116589992" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100317-150000-to-20100317-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10  March 2010  --Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 15:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>STILL TRIPIN' THE FUZZ FANTASTIC plus interviews with Twilight Tony of Slowpoke &amp; the Smoke and  D.B. Buxton of The Orpheans --with tunes by:
THE IRVING KLAWS, THE FUZZTONES, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE PLAYMATES, CHEAP TIME, THE DEADCATS, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE DISHRAGS, THE HIGHBALLS, EAST VAMPS, SONIC AVENUES, POINTED STICKS, THE ORANGU-TONES, THE UNTAMED YOUTH, THE NICE BOYS, JENNIFER GENTLE, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE ORPHEANS, BLOODSHOT BILL, KING KHAN &amp; BBQ, TRANZMITORS, HOWARD RIX &amp; THE TRESSPASSERS, THE LUNA RIOT, THE BON.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Primative, Fuzzed-out,  Garage Sex-plosions!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100310-150200-to-20100310-170300.mp3" length="115647989" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100310-150200-to-20100310-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>03  March 2010  -Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</title><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 15:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Music your momma warned you about! Demented Garage Pounders that lead to sex, drugs and beating the hell out of your guitar! 
THE URGES, THE SATELLITERS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, FRESH &amp; ONLYS, THE GREEN PAJAMAS, RED MASS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE MAKERS, THE MAGGOTS, THE LYRES, HUEVOS RANCHEROS, CHRISTIAN D. AND THE HANGOVERS, KING KHAN &amp; BBQ, THE CANADIAN SQUIRES, POINTED STICKS, SIR JULIAN, THE NEW CHRISTS, THE ZEROS, THE TREBELS, THE DATSONS, THE BON, THE JOLTS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, CHAIN AND THE GANG APOLLO GHOSTS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!   *Fuzzed-out Garage Sexplosions*</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100303-150300-to-20100303-170200.mp3" length="113733542" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100303-150300-to-20100303-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>24  February  2010</title><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Spinnin' 6Ts Garage for the non-hockey crowd! (Go Canada!)
THE SCIENTISTS, THE LIME SPIDERS, FUCKED UP, MONDO TOPLESS, YOUNG FRESH FELLOWS, THE GIRLS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADE, NEAL FORD AND FANATICS, THE TONICS, SONIC AVENUES, THE SHIT BIRDS, THE STEMS, ASTROID #4, THE FRESH AND ONLYS, HUSKER DU, THE PARALLELS, THE HOODS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE BOBBYTEENS, THEE MAKEOUT PARTY, THE SEEDS, THE CLEAN, THEE FINE LINES, THE KRAVIN' A'S, THE PAYBACKS, THE BON, THE KING KHAN &amp; BBQ SHOW, CHRISS MURRAY, THE EXPOS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100224-150100-to-20100224-170400.mp3" length="117563687" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100224-150100-to-20100224-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>17  February  2010</title><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>R'n'R with busted garage springs and guitar strings. Now with extra Go-Go Power!! And tunes by:
THE INVISIBLE EYES, CLAWHAMMER, THE BOOBYTRAPS, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE TREBLEMAKERS, THE ULTRA 5, LORD HIGH FIXERS, THE REAL LOSERS, THE SHADES, SIMPLY SAUCER, THE WAVE DWELLERS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE NERVES, THE CHAINS, THE DETROIT COBRAS, THE CRAWDADDYS, THE DEADCATS, THE HEATSCORES, THE MUSIC CONVENTION, THE LEG HOUNDS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE PARALLELS, THE GOLDSTARS, THE POLYMORPHINES, THE DOWN'N'OUTS, DEMOLITION DOLL RODS, BLOODSHOT BILL, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE CREEPY CREEPS, DEAD GHOSTS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100217-150100-to-20100217-170300.mp3" length="116606255" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100217-150100-to-20100217-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10  February  2010</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Trippin' the Mod, Garage, Power-Pop Fantastic with a slight feature on the &quot;Paisley Underground&quot;. With tunes by:
THE FOUR FOURS, HOODOO GURUS, POINTED STICKS, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE URGES, THE STONEAGE HEARTS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE PRISONERS, THE WAVE DWELLERS, THE TVees, THE ODD NUMBERS, B-LINES, THE CHORDS, TRANZMITORS, SONIC AVENUES,THE FIENDS, DICK HYMAN, HUNTINGTON CADS, DREAM SYNDICATE, THE RAIN PARADE, ASTROID #4, THE THREE O'CLOCK, THE SHARPSHOOTERS, THE ORPHEANS, THE OUTSIDERS, PIERCED ARROWS, VIVIAN GIRLS, THE POLYMORPHINES, PRETTY VANILLA, THE BOSS MONSTERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100210-150000-to-20100210-170300.mp3" length="117535331" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20100210-150000-to-20100210-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>16  December  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>An entire show featuring and dedicated to the Late Great Gregory Johnson -main man behind The Fiends and The Worst! Featuring interviews by various members of The Fiends and rare and never before heard tracks by The Fiends and The Worst!
--Hear the CiTR studios taken over by multiple generations of Fiends members who tell their stories about their late bandmate, plus Nardwaur and other surprises!--

Plus a bonus hour featuring some of Greg's favourite bands:
including THE CYNICS, THE MUMMIES, THE NIGHTSTALKERS, THE MIRACLE WORKERS, MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE GRUESOMES, THE OMENS, THE GRAVEDIGGER V, THE 14th WRAY, PLEASURE SUIT, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, THE UPPER CRUST, GIRL TROUBLE...</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  Special 'Gregory Johnson/Fiends' Edition</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091216-150000-to-20091216-180400.mp3" length="175819421" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091216-150000-to-20091216-180400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>09  December  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Garage-Punk'n'Spazztic-Power-Pop.Plus an on-the-air party with THE POINTED STICKS and tunes by:
THE FIENDS, THE DICKIES, DEVO, THE EPOXIES, THE POINTED STICKS, THE HEARTACHES, THE EXPLODING HEARTS, THEE MANIPULATORS, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, THE EBINIEZER SCROOGE APPRECIATION SOCIETY, THE FARREL BROS., THE DEAD CATS, THE LUNATICS, PAPPYS, THE WEIRDOS, WASTED LIVES, B-LINES, THE REAL PILLS, THE GIRLS, PRETTY  VANILLA, THE NERVES, THE EVAPORATORS, POINTED STICKS.....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!  with Pointed Sticks Interview</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091209-150000-to-20091209-170300.mp3" length="117540752" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091209-150000-to-20091209-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>02  December  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2009 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>High Speed, Chord-rippin' Fuzztro-mentals with:
THE FIENDS, THE CYNICS, DOCTOR EXPLOSIO9N, THE GOLDEN LEMONS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE UNCLAIMED, HIGH SCHOOL SWEETHEARTS, THE CLONES, THE ELECTRIC KISSES, THE SEEDS, THE VIVIAN GIRLS, THEE ULTRA BIMBOS, THE CHEAPSKATES, THE PAINTED SHIP, JIM NABORS, THE HIGHBALLS, BLOODSHOT BILL, SLOWPOKE AND THE SMOKE, PACK A.D., LENNY DEE, DEMOLITION DOLL RODS, THE GRUESOMES, THE TRAP DOORS, THE WORST, PRETTY VANILLA, POINTED STICKS, THEE VICARS, THE SPITFIRES, MOTORAMA, YARD TRAUMA, THE BRAINS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE FIENDS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091202-150000-to-20091202-170200.mp3" length="116579984" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091202-150000-to-20091202-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25  November  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 15:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Offerin' swell goods for swell times -with plenty of action to go around. Plus a revved-up interview with Tim of The Vicious Cycles and garage-tunes by: THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE ELEMENT 79, THE TVees, THE FIENDS, THE BUG NASTIES, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE JOLTS, SWANK, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, PRETTY VANILLA, THE EVAPORATORS, VANCOUGAR, THE SOFT BOYS, THE BARACUDAS, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, BLOODSHOT BILL, POINTED STICKS, STRANGE MAGIC, LA SEVERA MATACERA.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  --Fuzzed-up FUNdrive a go-go!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091125-150300-to-20091125-170500.mp3" length="116606255" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091125-150300-to-20091125-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>11  November  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Wheelie Poppin', Scab Pickin', Tire Burnin', Gear Jammin' Garage Rock'n'Roll-overs!
THE MIDWAYS, THE LEG HOUNDS, THE SHAMBLES, THE NERVES, THE JUANITOS, FRESH &amp; ONLYS, MEN FROM S.P.E.C.T.R.E., THE TUNESPINNERS, THEE FOURGIVEN, THOMAS FUNCTION, THE HEATSCORES, THE DEADCATS, THEE VICARS, THE PAINTED SHIP, POINTED STICKS, PRETTY VANILLA, THE THANES, THE MUSIC CONVENTION, DEMENTIA 13, THE NOVAKS, SUPERNOVA, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE SMUGGLERS, TRANZMITORS, SPIZZENERGI, THE JOLT, BATTLESNAKES, THE ZIP GUNS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, ALTERNATE ACTION, THE TVees, THE INVADERS, HIGH SCHOOL SWEETHEARTS, S. LORNE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!  --Wheelie Poppin' Rock'n'Roll-overs</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091111-150000-to-20091111-170500.mp3" length="119456867" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091111-150000-to-20091111-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>THE ARTS REPORT -- Wednesday, November 4, 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>- Nick Pannu's coverage of BLOODSHOTS 2009
- Cultural Olympiad Program Director Robert Kerr
- Paul Zurbeir's review of THE MASTER BUiLDER</description><itunes:subtitle>Hosted by Tracy Fuller</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091104-170000-to-20091104-180400.mp3" length="61166939" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091104-170000-to-20091104-180400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>04  November 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>From the tyme that land forgot- Fuzz-adelic,Garage-tunes from the Stone-age! With grunts from:
THE MAGGOTS, THE PANDORAS, THEE MANIPULATORS, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE FOUR FOURS, THE BUDDHAS, POINTED STICKS, PRETTY VANILLA, Les HELL ON HEELS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THEE OH NO'S, THE THIRD BOOTH, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE SATELLITERS, THE SAINTS, THE DISHRAGS, MAOW, THE GREEN HORNETS, DENISE AND CO., THE BELLS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, B-LINES, THE ORPHEANS, THE FIENDS, PLASTIC BLUES BAND.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !! -'Love Me Nots' feature and interview</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091104-150000-to-20091104-170200.mp3" length="116583320" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091104-150000-to-20091104-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>28 October  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2009 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A Grave-stompin' good time with:
MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE WITCHDOCTORS, ROCKIN' RYAN AND THE REAL GONERS, THE STEMS, THE DEADCATS, THE SWING RAYS, THE SUBURBAN NIGHTMARES, THE CRUSADERS, THE FIENDS, THE FAMOUS MONSTERS, KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADE, THE PRIMATES, KING DAPPER COMBO, THE GO-KATZ, THE DEADLINERS, THE HILLBILLY VARMENTS, THE MUMMIES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, BIG JOHN BATES, BEASTS OF BOURBON, BLOODSHOT BILL, THE BEES, THE MONOCLES, THE GRUESOMES, THE GHASTLY ONES, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE FIENDS, POINTED STICKS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS.</description><itunes:subtitle>A Rumble-ween a Go-Go Special</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091028-150100-to-20091028-170500.mp3" length="118522787" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091028-150100-to-20091028-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>21 October  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Bringin' ya full tilt Go-Go power! ala
THE CREEPY CREEPS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE UNRELATED SEGMENTS, THE GRAVEDIGGER V, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE NOMADS, LOS ARRRGHS, THE PRIMORDIALS, DRASTIC GASTIC, THE SOLARFLARES, THE DEADCATS, KC AND THE MOONSHINE BAND, THE REVERBERATORS, THE CRAMPS, THE MYSTERONS, HOT BLOOD BOMBERS, PAT BOONE, VINYL RADIO, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE EXOTICS, THEE VICARS, THE MYSTIC EYES, THE ENIGMAS, THE FIENDS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE GIRLS, ADAM AND THE ANTS, THE JOLTS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, DEJA VOODOO, BATTLE SNAKES, MIESHA &amp; THE SPANKS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091021-150000-to-20091021-170200.mp3" length="116583320" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091021-150000-to-20091021-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>14  October  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Reverb-drenched Fuzz-mania with:
THE FUZZTONES, THE ETTES, THE BUG NASTIES, THE HATE BOMBS, THE DETROIT COBRAS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE FLIP TOPS, THE EX-BOYFRIENDS, THE GIMMICKS, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE FALL-OUTS, LOS STRAIGHTJACKETS, B-LINES, THE NERVES, THE POINTED STICKS, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, THE MANVILS, THE SEEDS, FORTUNE AND MALTESE, THE STEMS, THE SOLARFLARES, THREE 4 TENS, THE GREEN PAJAMAS, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, THE ZIP GUNS, THE DEAD GHOSTS, DEMON'S CLAWS, HOT BLOOD BOMBERS, THEE VICARS, THE WAILIN' SOULS, THE LOVE ME NOTS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091014-150000-to-20091014-170400.mp3" length="118499852" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091014-150000-to-20091014-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>07  October  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 15:09:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Finger Blisterin', Organ Throbbin', Ass Shakin' Garage!!!
plus an interview with The Lizard People and tunes by:
THE BOSS MARTIANS, THEE OH NOs, THE CRUSADERS, THE HOODS, THE ACTION, VIVIAN GIRLS, THE SALVATION ARMY, THE LIVING DEADBEATS, THE SMEARS, EPOXIES, WAU y LOS ARRRGHS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE WORST, SHONEN KNIFE, KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADE, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE LIZARD PEOPLE, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE IRVING CLAWS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, PRETTY VANILLA, THE ETTES, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE KRAVIN' A's.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091007-150900-to-20091007-170500.mp3" length="110859578" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20091007-150900-to-20091007-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>30 September  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Toe Tappin', Waist Wobblin', Mind Meltin', Garage Goofs from:
THE TELL TALE HEARTS, THE SATELLITERS, THE FONDAS, THE CRAWLING WALLS, THE MISCREANTS, THE REVILLOS, THE KNIGHTS OF THE NEW CRUSADE, THE NIGHT MARCHERS, THE INVISIBLE EYES, THE SHACKLES, THE QUEEN ANNES, THE B-LINES, THE SOFT BOYS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE MOTHBALLS, LIQUID GENERATION, THE DICKIES, THE STRANGE MAGIC, YOUNG FRESH FELLOWS, THE WILLOWS, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE ZIP GUNS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE SABOTEURS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, DEREK'S ACCENT, THE CRAMPS, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE HOT BLOOD BOMBERS, THE STUPES, PRETTY VANILLA, THE POINTED STICKS, THE B-LINES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090930-150000-to-20090930-170500.mp3" length="119456867" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090930-150000-to-20090930-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>16 September  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Playin' Oily Garage Numbers and Board-bustin' Surf Tunes!! Plus interviews with Nicole Steen of 'Low Brow On The High Seas' and Chopper of The Reverberators.  And of course songs by:
LOS PLANTRONICS, GORE GORE GIRLS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE MAGGOTS, THE DUKES OF HAMBURG, THE DEL MONAS, RICH HOPE, DEMON'S CLAWS, THE STINGERS, DAVIE ALLEN AND THE ARROWS, THE REVERBERATORS, JUAN EL MATEMATICO, THE GO-NUTS, THE ZIP GUNS, THE GETAWAY STICKS, THE DAGMARS, LAWRENCE WELK, THE SURF COASTERS, THE GHASTLY ONES, THE WIPE-OUTERS, JACKIE AND THE CEDRICS, THE REVERBERATORS, THE SURF MESSIAHS, THE MODELOS, THE A-BONES, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, HOT BLOOD BOMBERS, STEREOPHONIC SPACE SOUND UNLIMITED, WAU y LOS ARRRGHS!!!, THE REVERBERATORS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090916-150000-to-20090916-170500.mp3" length="119321342" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090916-150000-to-20090916-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>09 September  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Outta the nest and into the garage! Twaang, wyld beats, fuzz'n'thumps from the likes of:
THE MIDWAYS, THE TVees, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE SOLARFLARES, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE EVAPORATORS, THE LEATHER UPPERS, THE HEATSCORES, THE BRAINS, SWANK, THE MONKS, GOOBER AND THE PEAS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE FIENDS, THE NIGHTSTALKERS, THE REIGNING SOUND, BUGHOUSE 5, FENWTCK featuring JERRY RAYE, THE VIPERS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE LOVVE ME NOTS, BILLY CHILDISH AND THE FRIENDS OF THE BUFF MEDWAY FANCIERS ASSOCIATION, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE SURF MESSIAHS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE HITS, THE THIRD BARDO, LINDY BLASKEY AND THE LAVELLS, THE TRAP DOORS, TRANZMITORS, SCREAMING FEMALES, RAT FINK, ALAN SHERMAN, THE MODELOS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090909-145900-to-20090909-170400.mp3" length="119327597" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090909-145900-to-20090909-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>02 September  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shakin' Some Fuzzed-up Action with:
SHUTDOWN 66, MONDO TOPLESS, THE OMENS, THE SIN-TONES, THE SQUARES, REIGNING SOUND, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE MAG SEVEN, GIRL TROUBLE, THE FLAMIN' GROOVIES, THE CYNICS, THE GRUESOMES, THE PHENOMENAUTS, TRANZMITORS, THE MOVIE STAR JUNKIES, THE FLAKES, THE HENTCHMEN,  THE PURPLE MERKINS, THE GET DOWN, SHE DEVILS, THE CHEAPSKATES, THE MUSSIES, DEE AND TEE, THE BUG NASTIES, LES TERRIBLES, THE BOX ELDERS, SIMPLY SAUCER, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE WALKING SCREAMS, PRETTY VANILLA, THE STRANGE MAGIC, THE JIGSAW SEEN, THEE MANIPULATORS....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090902-150000-to-20090902-170600.mp3" length="120295871" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090902-150000-to-20090902-170600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>26  August  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Takin' the Hip Tyme Trip with:
THE HYPSTERZ, THE TREBLEMAKERS, THE CHRIS &amp; TAD SHOW, THE INVADERS, THE RIDE THEORY, JAY REATARD, LES SEXAREENOS, THEE MERRY WIDOWS, HAZEL ATKINS, THE HEATSCORES, BIG JOHN BATES, THE NELSONICS, THE EVAPORATORS, SIT'N'SPIN, THEE PASSION KILLERS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE FLESHTONES, THE EYES, YOUNG RIVAL, RAT PFINK THEME, THE TIKI TONES, THE HEADLESS HORSEMEN, THE TOP DRAWERS, MIESHA AND THE SPANKS, THE 99th FLOOR, THE DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, THE STRANGE MAGIC, LOVE SCULPTURE, THE BOX ELDERS, THE HIGH FIVE, THE SUNDAY SINNERS, THE MANIPULATORS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE HOODOO GURUS, RAYGUN COWBOYS, VANCOUVER NIGHTS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090826-150000-to-20090826-172000.mp3" length="133649045" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090826-150000-to-20090826-172000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>19  August  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2009 14:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shakin' the Go-Go cages Mongrel-style with special guest Bob Scott(editor &amp; co-publisher) of The Mongrel Zine.  Tunes by: THE MIDWAYS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE BI-FIVE, THHE FINE LINES, THEE FOURGIVEN, THE PHENOMENAUTS, THE POINTED STICKS, THE SMUGGLERS, THE HARA-KEE-REES, THE REAL PILLS, PISSED JEANS, THE PIERCED ARROWS, THE PRIMATES, PEABODY'S HERMITAGE, THE STONEAGE HEARTS, THE GORIES, PRETTY VANILLA, THE REAL KIDS, THE CREATION, LAWRENCE WELK, THE SUNDAY SINNERS, DEMON'S CLAWS, RED MASS, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, THE TRAP DOORS, THE HIGHER STATE, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE GOOD NIGHT LOVING, THE SPITS, THE DEAD GHOSTS, DEMON'S CLAWS, DAVILLA 666, BLOODSHOT BILL, YOUNG RIVAL, GAVEN DIANDA, RED MASS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE GRUESOMES....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090819-145800-to-20090819-173500.mp3" length="149884523" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090819-145800-to-20090819-173500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>12  August  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2009 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Outta the dark and dusty corners of the Rumbletone-vault comes the demented, totally fuzzed-up, and snarly sounds from: THEE ULTRA BIMBOS, BLACK LIPS, THE BUG NASTIES, DIGGER AND THE PUSSYCATS, THE CRUSADERS, THE RAYMEN, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE KAISERS, RIDE THERRY, THE SHOUTLESS, THE DEVIL DOLLS, THE PANDORAS, THE SHIMMYS, WAU y LOS ARRRGHS!!!, NO BUNNY, THE NEW FIDELITY, THE GET QUICK, NANCY SINATRA, WESTBOUND TRAIN, THE FIREMEN, THE DOLLYROCKER MOVEMENT, THE TRAP DOORS, THE WORST, PRETTY VANILLA, THE ELECTRIC KISSES, THE HOODS, THE PINK FITS, THE PRISONERS, THE SOLAR FLARES, GRAHAM DAY AND THE GAOLERS, THE RATS, THE EVAPORATORS, SHAWN STIBBARDS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, MURPHY AND THE MOB, THE MORLOCKS, THE STRANGLERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090812-145900-to-20090812-172000.mp3" length="134588546" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090812-145900-to-20090812-172000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>5  August  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 14:57:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A Blast from the Sixties Cartoon Past. Wyld Garage Action with Hanna Barbera Satisfaction!! Music and Theme-Tunes by:
THE ATOM ANT SHOW, ADAM AND THE ANTS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE CHAINS, PEBBLES AND BAM BAM, THE MAKERS, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE LAUGHING SKY, PRETTY VANILLA, REDD KROSS, THE DICKIES, FAMOUS MONSTERS, NO USE FOR A NAME, JOSIE AND THE PUSSYCATS, RIFF RANDELLS, THE YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, HONG KONG PHOOEY, ROCKIN' RYAN AND THE REAL GONNERS, GUANA BATS, THE BRAINS, MANIC HISPANIC, JAPANDROIDS, THE MOOG COOKBOOK, NOT SENSIBLES, ALIEN SEX FIEND, DASTARDLY AND MUTTLEY, INTOXICA, THE HI-FIVES, THE WAY OUTS, THE METEORS, JOHNNY QUEST, PIERCED ARROWS, ROBY AND HIS ANGELS, FRIGG A GO-GO, TRANZMITORS, YOUNG RIVAL, DICKIES, THE MANIPULATORS, WESTBOUND TRAIN.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumble-Toon Radio a Go-Go !!!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090805-145700-to-20090805-170800.mp3" length="125074274" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090805-145700-to-20090805-170800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>5  August  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 14:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A Blast from the Sixties Cartoon Past. Wyld Garage Action with Hanna Barbera Satisfaction!! Music and Theme-Tunes by:
THE ATOM ANT SHOW, ADAM AND THE ANTS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE CHAINS, PEBBLES AND BAM BAM, THE MAKERS, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE LAUGHING SKY, PRETTY VANILLA, REDD KROSS, THE DICKIES, FAMOUS MONSTERS, NO USE FOR A NAME, JOSIE AND THE PUSSYCATS, RIFF RANDELLS, THE YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, HONG KONG PHOOEY, ROCKIN' RYAN AND THE REAL GONNERS, GUANA BATS, THE BRAINS, MANIC HISPANIC, JAPANDROIDS, THE MOOG COOKBOOK, NOT SENSIBLES, ALIEN SEX FIEND, DASTARDLY AND MUTTLEY, INTOXICA, THE HI-FIVES, THE WAY OUTS, THE METEORS, JOHNNY QUEST, PIERCED ARROWS, ROBY AND HIS ANGELS, FRIGG A GO-GO, TRANZMITORS, YOUNG RIVAL, DICKIES, THE MANIPULATORS, WESTBOUND TRAIN.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumble-Toon Radio a Go-Go !!!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090805-140000-to-20090805-170800.mp3" length="180440615" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090805-140000-to-20090805-170800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>1  August  2009</title><pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 11:57:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Generation Anihilation hosted by yours truly. Spinnin'my favorite punk rock jems with rarities and surprises! Tune by: TOY DOLLS, THE ADVERTS, THE ADDICTS, THE WEIRDOS, THE EARACHES, CIRCLE JERKS, FORGOTTEN REBELS, THE SCREAMERS, CRASS, STIFF LITTLE FINGERS, SPIZZENERGI, TRANSMITORS, ADAM AND THE ANTS, THE BUSINESS, THE TEMPLARS, THE JOLT, THE DWARVES, B-LINES, WASTED LIVES, ROYAL GRAND PRIX, THE PARTISIANS, THE DISH RAGS, THE BOYS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Generation Anihilation (Show Swap)</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090801-115700-to-20090801-130400.mp3" length="63977519" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090801-115700-to-20090801-130400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>15  July 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Outta the Garage and into the Pop Factory. From Fuzzy Garage to Over the Top Power-Pop courtesy of:
THE SURF TRIO, HIDDEN PEACE, WAU y LOS ARRRGHS!!!, THE WOGGLES, THE DETROIT COBRAS, THE INTERNATIONAL NOISE CONSPIRACY, THE GRUESOMES, THE MUFFS, LES HELL ON HEELS, THEE MERRY WIDOWS, THE BELLES, ALTHEA AND THE MEMORIES, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCTS, THE EMBROOKS, THE BARACUDAS, THE MODELOS, MOGOLLAR, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, THE PURPLE MERKINS, THEE VICARS, THEE SNUFF PROJECT, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE EVAPORATORS, ROCK GARDEN, PRETTY VANILLA, THE PLEASURE SUIT, THE ZEROS, THE THREE O'CLOCK, THE BREAKAWAYS, SISTER LOVERS, THE POINTED STICKS, THE B-LINES.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090715-150000-to-20090715-170200.mp3" length="116584571" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090715-150000-to-20090715-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>08  July 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Full-tilt Garage Action! Blisterin' Power-Pop! Toes on the Nose Surf, Acid-laced Psych, and even some Swank Ska!!! Tunes provided by:
MUCK &amp; THE MIRES, THE SATELLITERS, THE MINSTRELS, THE STONEAGE HEARTS, THE UNKNOWNS, WAU y LOS ARRRGHS!!!, THE EVAPORATORS, FUN 100, THE POINTED STICKS, THE INVADERS, THE TVees, PRETTY VANILLA, THE TONICS, THEE ULTRA BIMBOOS, THE PINK FITS, THE HEARTACHES, THE MOVIE STAR JUNKIES, LOS STRAIGHT JACKETS, THE ISOTOPES, THE MAKERS, DEMON'S CLAWS, THE SHAMS, THE OMENS, THE UNCLAIMED, THEE OH NO'S, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, FUREASEEN, MEN FROM S.P.E.C.T.R.E.,FRANCIS HAROLD AND THE HALOGRAMS, THE TOP DRAWERS, DEAD GHOSTS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE SLACKERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090708-150000-to-20090708-170400.mp3" length="118498601" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090708-150000-to-20090708-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>01  July 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2009 14:57:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Trippin' the Fuzz Fantastic with a feature on Sky Saxon, an interview with Rik Crusader of The Woolly Bandits and the world premier of the new Laundronauts CD!!
with tracks by:
SKY 'SUNLIGHT' SAXON AND THE SEEDS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE FIENDS, THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE DWARVES, B-LINES, THE DRIVING STUPID, THE CREEPY CREEPS, THE LEATHER UPPERS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, LAWRENCE WELK, THE WITCH DOCTORS, WAU y LOS ARRRGHS!, THEE VICARS, THE TVees, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE MANIPULATORS, THE MATADORS, THE TRAP DOORS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090701-145700-to-20090701-170600.mp3" length="123277004" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090701-145700-to-20090701-170600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>17 June 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 14:57:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Now with more fuzz! More action! The new and improved Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go offers twice the fuzz, double the action and at least one explosion! Hear it to believe it! Made with:
THE MIDWAYS, DMZ, LOS PLANTRONICS, THE GRUESOMES, THE GENTLEMAN CALLERS, LOS STRAIGHTJACKETS, THE GREEN HORNETS, X, THE MOVIE STAR JUNKIES, THE FLAMING SIDEBURNS, LOS CHICOS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE UNCALLED FOR, THE MISSING LINKS, NOT SENSIBLES, THE CLONES, MAN OR ASTROMAN, THE PACK A.D., STEREOPHONIC SOUND SPACE UNLIMITED,  THE LOVE ME NOTS, WE THE PEOPLE, THE UNTOLD FABLES, THE SPACESHITS, THE DEADCATS, SWANK, THE NERVOUS FELLAS, THE NIGHT STALKERS, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE BLOODY HOLLIES, THE CANNIBALS, SHAWN STIBBARDS, THE EVAPORATORS, THE TVees, THE WOOLLY BANDITS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090617-145700-to-20090617-170500.mp3" length="122320406" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090617-145700-to-20090617-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10 June 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2009 14:57:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzy-GoGo-Numbers to make you Twist, Shake and Rumble!!
Plus an interview with Petroleum By Products with tunes by:
THE STONEAGE HEARTS, TEE AND THE CRUMPETS, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE FORBIDDEN DIMENSION, KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, THE EVAPORATORS, THE STINKIES, THE PORCH GHOULS, PRETTY VANILLA, THE JUPITER AFFECT, ASTEROID NO. 4, THE FORTY FIVES, RAVIN BLUE, THE CHILLS, MASHA ORELLA, THE CLEAN, THE FROWNING CLOWN, THE BOLD, QUINTRON, JUNIOR MAJOR, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCTS, THE MUMMIES, THE TVees, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE JOLTS, TRANZMITORS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE BUTCHERS, THE PARALLELS, URBAN GUERRILLA, GREEN ON RED.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090610-145700-to-20090610-170600.mp3" length="123277004" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090610-145700-to-20090610-170600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>03 June 2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 14:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Hip Shakin', Strummin' Fuzz-ta-mentals!!! with
THE PRIMORDIALS, THE GRUESOMES, THE TOP DRAWERS, MERCURY FOUR, PRETTY VANILLA, REDD KROSS, THE FIENDS, THE REVOLVING PAINT DREAM, THE DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, THE OUTRAGEOUS CHERRY, THE EVAPORATORS, THE MONKS, FUN 100, WASTED LIVES, THE POLYSICS, TRANZMITORS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE DETROIT COBRAS, THE VON BONDIES, THE JIGSAW SEEN, THE PINK FITS, THE ELECTRIC KISSES, NIKKI AND THE CORVETTES, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCTS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, WHITE FLAG, MAOW, THE ODD NUMBERS, THE ENIGMAS, THE WOGGLES, THE TVees, THE MOVIE STAR JUNKIES, SWANK, TRANZMITORS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090603-145800-to-20090603-170500.mp3" length="121364225" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090603-145800-to-20090603-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>27 May  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2009 14:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Gettin' PSYCHO in the GO-GO cage while smacked with the BILLY-klub at 60's RPM!! and topping it with an interview with THE BRAINS!! ... plus tunes by:
THE MIDWAYS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE BOMBORAS, THE ODD NUMBERS, THE MOVIE STAR JUNKIES, THE KURLINGS, THE IRVING KLAWS, THE SPECTRES, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, THE GORIES, CRASH 13, THE EVAPORATORS, THE SIN-TONES, THE DELUXETONE ROCKETS, ROCKIN' RYAN AND THE REAL GONERS, EL VEZ, UG AND THE CAVEMEN, THE BRAINS, THE SURF MESSIAHS, THE BRAINS, LEVI DEXTER AND THE RIPCHORDS, THE BLAZERS, THEE WALTONS, THE SCREAMIN' RAYS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE AGGROLITES, THE NEW YORK DOLLS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090527-145800-to-20090527-170400.mp3" length="120403040" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090527-145800-to-20090527-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>20 May  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Garage-pop, Psyche-pop, Glam-pop, Surf-pop, Fuzz-pop, Party-pop! - Two hours of gut soakin' pop with 
THE HATE BOMBS, THE TVees, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE WEIRDOS, THE BOSCH, THE ISOTOPES, THE COUNTDOWNS, DIGGER AND THE PUSSYCATS, THE MAGGOTS, THE ELECTRIC KISSES, THE REIGNING SOUND, THE SADIES, INTOXICA, THE PORCH GHOULS, THE ROUTE 66 KILLERS, KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, THE SATELLITERS, THE STOMACH MOUTHS, THE MOPS, THE JESSICA FLETCHERS, PRETTY VANILLA, PLEASURE SUIT, CHARIOTS OF EGGS, WAU y LOS ARRRGHS!, PETROLEUM BY PRODUCTS, THE DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, THE SQUIRES, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, TRANZMITORS, THEE FOURGIVEN, THE CENTREES, THE GRUESOMES, THE PINK FITS, CIRCA NOW.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090520-145900-to-20090520-170400.mp3" length="119449361" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090520-145900-to-20090520-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>13 May  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 14:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Wound-up Spring Garage Door Openers with Acid Drenched Batteries, Stacked Beer Cans, Oil Stains and Sticky Joints that add to the Experience:
THE CAVEMANISH BOYS, THE GET DOWN, THE BREADMAKERS, THE OMENS, THE MONOMEN, THE FLAKES, THE MOVIE STAR JUNKIES, THE EYES, THE PRIMATES, THE HAUNTED, THE RAIN PARADE, PETROLEUM BY-PRODUCTS, JUNIOR MAJOR, THE ELECTRIC KISSES, THE RED AUNTS, THE ULTRA-SONICAS, THE YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, THE PUSSYCATS, THE MANATEES, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE PAYBACKS, THE THANES, HOT BLOOD BOMBERS, THE PINK FITS, THE TVees, THE EXPLODING HEARTS, THE SHAKES, THE LACKLOVES, THE VASELINES, THE DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, THE MYSTERY TREND, STRANGE MAGIC, THE WOOLLY BANDITS</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090513-145800-to-20090513-170000.mp3" length="116574146" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090513-145800-to-20090513-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>06 May  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2009 14:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz, twang, and thumpin' organ plus an interview with The Strange Magic and tunes by:
THE STONEAGE HEARTS, THE FIENDS, NEAL FORD AND FANATICS, RAISED BY WOLVES, THE TELL-TALE HEARTS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE EVAPOTATORS, THE DT'S, DEJA VOODOO, ANGRY DRAGONS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, DOCTOR'S EXPLOSION, 5 AMERICANS, DEE &amp; TEE, THE STEMS, THE BALLOON FARM, THE RADIO, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE NEW FIDELITY, THE STRANGE MAGIC, THE LOBSTER QUADRILLE, GOLDEN DAWN, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE TVees, IMACULATE MACHINE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090506-145800-to-20090506-170200.mp3" length="118486508" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090506-145800-to-20090506-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>29 April  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 15:15:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shakin' it up Mongrel style and gettin' inky with Bob Scott artist and editor of the Mongrel Zine plus tunes by:
THE BEND SCEPTERS, THE FUZZTONES, THEE OH NO's, THEE ULTRA BIMBOS, THE LYRES, Q 65, LOVE, THE CHAINS, THE TRAPMEN, THE SICK ROSE, KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, THE UPPER CRUST, THE NEW FUGITIVES, THE SAINTS, THE BARRACUDAS, THE GRUESOMES, THE TRANZMITORS, DEAD GHOSTS, THE TRAP DOORS, THE TVees, THE MANIPULATORS, THE SALVATION ARMY, THE FAMINES, THE GREEN HOUR BAND.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090429-151500-to-20090429-170200.mp3" length="102254783" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090429-151500-to-20090429-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>22 April  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Revved-up, high octane Garage R'n'R that's roarin' down the road with:
THE MAGGOTS, THE LOVE ME KNOTS, DEAD BOLT, GOLDEN BALLS, THE FARREL BROS., KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, THE FOUR CORNERS, THE GENTLEMEN, THE NEW CHRISTS, THE MASONICS, THE TVees, THE HIGH FIVES, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE SHAMBLES, THE TROGGS, REIGNING SOUND, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, CHARRIOT OF EGGS, THE MODELOS, THE HARA-KEE-REES, THE REAL PILLS, THE HEARTACHES, THE LEGENDARY INVISIBLE MEN, THE SMUGGLERS, THE BOGUES, THE BRAINS, THE SURFADELICS, THIS MOMENT IN BLACK HISTORY, THE MORLOCKS, SICK SICK YEAH, THE SHATNERS, THE GO-GOs, THE GET DOWN, OSCAR AND THE MAJESTICS, THE SADDIES, THE STRANGE BOYS, VALERIE GHAHAM.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090422-145900-to-20090422-170200.mp3" length="117521987" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090422-145900-to-20090422-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>15 April  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Throbbing Organs, Vibrating Reverb Springs, Full-on Fuzz, Pounding Bass, and Beer-soaked, Worn-out Vocal Chords make up todays show with:
THE MIDWAYS, THE MYSTERONS, ATOMIC 7, THE JAY BEES, THE TREBLES, THE TVees, THE BLACK LIPS, THE MYSTIC EYES, THE BLOODY HOLLIES, THE WILLOWZ, THE B-LINES, THE LOVE ME NOTS, THE PANDORAS, THE SUNSETS, THE HIGHBALLS, THE WORST, THE CONDO FUCKS, THE DREAM SYNDICATE, CHARIOTS OF EGGS, THE MODELOS, THE GO-BETWEENS, THE STEPFORD HUSBANDS, THE APEMEN, STRANGE MAGIC, THE ORANGE ALABASTOR MUSHROOM, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE TRAP DOORS, HUEVOS RANCHEROS, THE BOSS MONSTERS, HUSKER DU, THE SURF MESSIAHS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE DEAD GHOSTS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090415-145900-to-20090415-170400.mp3" length="119456450" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090415-145900-to-20090415-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>01 April  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Beer-chuggin', Pop-swillin', Pill-poppin' Garage-party tunes from the likes of:
THE SHITBIRDS, THE BENT SCEPTERS, THE FLESHTONES, THE SHINOLAS, THE DRAGS, PLASTICLAND, THE JESSICA FLETCHERS, THE EXOTICS, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE JIGSAW SCENE, THE SUR-FINKS, THE WIGS, THE CRUSADERS, THE UNTAMED YOUTH, THE ORANGU-TONES, THE MOTARDS, FUAD AND THE FEZTONES, THE HITSVILLE HOUSE BAND, JAY REATARD, THE OMENS, DEAD GHOSTS, HOT PANDA, KLAUS WUNDERLICH, SKATERHATER, THE EVAPORATORS, THE ALAHOS, THE B-LINES, THE POINTED STICKS, THE TONICS, CONDOFUCKS, THE INVISIBLE EYES, THE TVees, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE BARRIER, THE CHESTERFIELD KINGS, PRETTY VANILLA, DEFEKTORS,THE TRANZMITORS, THE BLACK LIPS, SLOWPOKE AND THE SMOKE.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090401-145900-to-20090401-170400.mp3" length="119447693" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090401-145900-to-20090401-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25 March  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Four exclaimation marks of Maximum Full-tilt Rockin' Garage Action! We've cracked the foundation and busted the springs on the garage door courtesy of:
THEE FOURGIVEN, REDD KROSS, THE GOLDSTARS, LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE MUSSIES, THE FUZZTONES, THE MAYNARDS, THE 45s, CURSE OF THE HORSEFLESH, THE BEECHNUTS, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, DAVIE ALLAN AND THE ARROWS, THEE MERRY WIDOWS, THE GRUESOMES, THE DECIEVERS, THE TVees, THE NELSONICS, THE PARALLELS, THE UGLY BEATS, THE RAMBLIN' AMBASSADORS, BABY MONGOOSE, DEVO, TRANZMITORS, THE EMERALDS, THE FACEFULL, GOOGLE A, SKY SAXON with Firewall, THE SEEDS, THE DWARVES, THE BUGNASTIES, DANTES, THE STRANGE MAGIC.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090325-145900-to-20090325-170400.mp3" length="119448944" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090325-145900-to-20090325-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>20 March  2009</title><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fillin' in for Ska-T and doin' his Scene-ik Drive. Tis Ska-Ska au Go-Go! &quot;Pick-it-up&quot; with:
THE TOASTERS, THE UNTOUCHABLES, AUTHER KAY &amp; THE ORIGINALS, THE PLANET SMASHERS, INSPECTOR, SUB CITY DWELLERS, THE SELECTOR, SKANIC, THE SKATOMATICS, THE BUSTERS, ONE NIGHT BAND, THE KING PINS, THE HEPTONE &amp; SHAKA SHAMBA, THE RADIATION KINGS, MADNESS, LOS FURIOS, THE NELSONICS, FUNNY BRASSKA, FILIBUSTER, BIM SKALLA BIM, RUDE CITY RIOT, EASY BIG FELLA, THE DUBLINS, GANGSTERS, MARK FOGGO'S SKASTERS, DIPLOMATS OF SOLID SOUND, FUN BOY THREE, JUDGE DREAD, NY SHA ENSAMBLE, THE AGGROLITES BAD MANNERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>FrankenSka / Ska-T's Scene-ik Drive</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090320-100000-to-20090320-120200.mp3" length="116582486" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090320-100000-to-20090320-120200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>18 March  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Ready, Set, Go-Go!! All Action.. All the time! Just Thrills , Action and Spills! Todays episode stars... THE COME ONS, THEE OH NO'S, THE UNTAMED YOUTH, THE NEW FIDELITY, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE MOTHBALLS, GASOLINE, THE CREEPY CREEPS, OBITS, THE STOMACHMOUTHS, THE MAGGOTS, THE HANGEE V, BUD &amp; CATHY, THE EVAPORATORS, THE LAUNDRANAUTS, THE UPPER CRUST, MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE MOXIES, LOS PEYOTES, THE TIME STOPPERS, THE TVees, THE TOP DRAWERS, MUCK AND THE MIRES, PLATON et LES CAVES, THE TONICS, CHARIOTS OF EGGS, THE MIRACLE WORKERS, THE SATELLITERS, BLACK LIPS, THE STOLEN MINKS, THE GREEN TELLESCOPE, THE VIPERS, BOW WOW WOW.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090318-150000-to-20090318-170300.mp3" length="117533663" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090318-150000-to-20090318-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>11 March  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This ain't your mainstream 'broad-rock'. These tunes by girls that'll kick your ass! Part of CiTR's International Woman's Week a special edition of R.R.aG.G. featuring only all gal bands or woman led bands- with tracks by:
THE VENDETTAS, FABULOUS DISASTER, THE FOXATIONS, SIT &amp; SPIN, THE BOBBYTEENS, THE LOVE ME NOTS, VANCOUGAR, JUNIOR MAJOR, MAOW, THE CINCH, LES TERRIBLES, THE DEL-MONAS, THE BRISTOLS, THE DIABOLIKS, THEE ULTRA BIMBOOS, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE SIN-TONES, B-GIRLS, THE NEPTUNAS, SOUTHER CULTURE ON THE SKIDS, APRIL MARCH, LIZ BRADY, FRANCE GALL, CAMILLE, THE BANGS, LES HELL ON HEELS, THE BOOBY TRAPS, THE SHIMMYS, THE PEBBLES, ALTHEA AND THE MEMORIES, THE RIFF RANDELLS, AMANDA JONES, THE YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, NIKKI &amp; THE CORVETTES, THE GIRLS, THE PANDORAS, MODE MODERN.</description><itunes:subtitle>'Chick-Chick au Go-Go'/ Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090311-150000-to-20090311-170200.mp3" length="116569142" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090311-150000-to-20090311-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>04  March  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 15:58:00 -0800</pubDate><description>1 hour mini-edition of Rumbletone Radio fuzz-plosions! featuring THE BELLES, THE OKMONIKS, THE 5,6,7,8'S, THE ROYAL PENDLETONS, THE MASONICS, THE WEIRDIES, THUNDERCRACK, THE ELEMENT 79, THE HITS, THE GRUESOMES, THE TVEES, THE GREEN OUR BAND, THE UPSIDEDOWN, SPINDRIFT.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090304-155800-to-20090304-170200.mp3" length="61157348" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090304-155800-to-20090304-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25 February  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 14:59:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Reverb, Rumble, Thumps and Fuzz comin' yer way full speed,
plus a spotlight on The Pandoras and an interview with Spike of Spike &amp; Mike's Sick &amp; Twisted Animation with tracks by:
THE FIENDS, THE NIGHTCRAWLERS, WAU Y LOS ARRRGHS!!!, THE NEW FUGITIVES, THE MAGGOTS, THE INVADERS, THE TVEES, THE OMENS, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE PANDORAS, THE MUFFS, THE BEARDS, THE SCREAMIN' FURYS, SISTER LOVERS, THEE VICARS, THE REAL PILLS, THE CRAWDADDYS, THE DUKES OF HAMBURG, LOS STRAIGHTJACKETS, THE WEIRDIES featuring MR. GASSER, THE SAUCERS, THE POINTED STICKS, THE CLONES, THE NEW FIDELITY, CRIPPLE CREEK FARIES, B-LINES, 84 ROOMS,and THE BELADEANS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090225-145900-to-20090225-170500.mp3" length="120459752" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090225-145900-to-20090225-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>18  February  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 15:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Today it's a Mod, Mod, Mod World with a feature and interview with The New Fidelity plus the mod-garage invasion with:
DIGGER AND THE PUSSYCATS, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE EASYBEATS, THE ROCKIN' RAMRODS, THE GREEN HORNETS, THE AARDVARKS, THE TRANZMITORS, THE DATSONS, THE PRISONERS, HEADQUARTERS, THE EMBROOKS, JOHN'S CHILDREN, THEE WAISTCOATS, THE SIR FINKS, THE LOLLIPOP SHOPPE, THE CHAINS, THE TVEES, THE GET QUICK, THE INSOMNIACS, THE NEW FIDELITY, FIRE, THE PARALLELS, THE MIDWAYS, THEE MANIPULATORS, MONSTERS FROM MARS!, THE GRUESOMES, THE TVEES....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090218-150200-to-20090218-170200.mp3" length="114672626" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090218-150200-to-20090218-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>11  February  2009</title><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Thee Rock and thee Roll with thee Reverb, thee Fuzz, thee Snarl and often thee Swirling-Organ courtesy of:
THE GREEN HORNETS, THE GRUESOMES, FLIPPER, THEE OH NO'S, THE MYSTIC EYES, THE COME-ONS, THE MOTHBALLS, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE EXOTICS, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, THE STRANGLERS, THE TRANZMITORS, THEE VICARS, THE GO-NUTS, THE CRUSADERS, THE B-LINES, THE EMERALDS, THEE ULTRA BIMBOS, THE TVEES, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, GIRL TROUBLE, CHARIOTS OF EGGS, THE NEW FIDELITY, THEE CELLAR DWELLERS, THE MAGGOTS, JACKSON PHIBES, THE FORBIDEN DIMENSION, THE UPSIDE DOWN, THE EXECUTIONERS, THE TONICS, THE JOLTS, THE OMENS, and THE SIR-FINKS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090211-150000-to-20090211-170000.mp3" length="114668039" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20090211-150000-to-20090211-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10  December  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2008 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Light shatterin' &amp; Tree tippin' 60's fuzz'n'growls and psych-quirk-pop! Plus an interview with Matt of Chariots of Eggs along with tunes by:
MR. GASSER AND THE WEIRDOS, THE WEIRDIES, THE BEEKEEPERS, SHUTDOWN 66, THE MAKERS, THE EMERALDS, THE FUZZTONES, THE HENCHMEN, THE SIR FINKS, THE CRUSADERS, GREAT SOCIETY, WE THE PEOPLE, THE MOCK TURTLES, YESTERDAY'S THOUGHTS, THE JURY, THE WILDEBEESTS, THE DELVETTES, THE MODELOS, NO FUN, CHARIOTS OF EGGS, POINTED STICKS, SQUIDDO, THE SHIMMYS, THE HOLOGRAMS, THE ZIP GUNS, THE BOOBY TRAPS, THE TVEES, THE NEW FIDELITY...

See you in the New Year!!!!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081210-150100-to-20081210-170400.mp3" length="117552428" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081210-150100-to-20081210-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>3  December  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Garage dwellin', Beer guzzlin' 6Ts R'n'R plus interviews with Chris of The TVees and Angela of Eldorado!!! with tunes by:
THE IRVING CLAWS, THE PERSIAN RUGS, THEE SNUFF PROJECT, THE DEAD GHOSTS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE ULTRA BIMBOS, BILLY CHILDISH, LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE VICIOUS CYCLES,  THE DUBLINS, THE TVees, POSITIVELY 13 O'CLOCK, THE SANDPIPERS, ROCKIN' RYAN AND THE REAL GONERS, THE ORANGU-TONES, SWANK, ELDORADO, THE EVAPORATORS, THE TVees, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE TOP DRAWERS, VANCOUGAR, THE WEIRDIES, THE NEW FIDELITY, THE TVees....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081203-150000-to-20081203-170400.mp3" length="118486508" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081203-150000-to-20081203-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>12  November  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 15:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>6Ts Fuzz-blasters from the Land of Shrew featuring:
THE BUG NASTIES, MUCK AND THE MIRES, THE EMERALDS, THE PLAYMATES, THE HEARTACHES, THE NUTHIN'S, THE TOP DRAWERS,  HUNG JURY,  THE GREENHORNES, THE DEAD GHOSTS, THE BOMBORAS, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE SATISFACTION, THE SURF TRIO, ASTROID #4, THE STAIRS, THE GURUS, THE DRIVING STUPID, THE EVAPORATORS, THE MONKS, THE QUID, BENDERS, TELL-TALE HEARTS, CHESTERFIELD KINGS, THEE MANIPULATORS, THE TIKI TINES, THE APEMEN, GREEN ON RED, THE MODELOS, THE WEIRDIES, NOT SENSIBLES, THE PARALLELS.. . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081112-150200-to-20081112-170100.mp3" length="113720198" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081112-150200-to-20081112-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>05 November  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 15:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Hip Shakin', Bed Thumpin', Garagedoor Slammin' R'n'R with:
THE SATELLITERS, THE EMERALDS, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE SPECTORS, THE MIDWAYS, THE YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE GRUESOMES, THE FUNSEEKERS, THE DEAD GHOSTS, THE VOODUO, THE STINKIES, THE WEIRDIES, JACKSON PHIBES, COLOR ME PSYCHO, GIRL TROUBLE, THE REAL KIDS, THE FAST, INTOXICA, THE BARRACUDAS, THE MISSING LINKS, THE BOOBY TRAPS, THE MANSFIELDS, THE KAISERS, THE PAYBACKS, THE YO-YO'S, LOS HORRIES, THE LURKERS, THE KING KHAN AND BBQ SHOW, THE FE FI FO FUMS, THE STOLEN MINKS, THE STRIKE, THE TRANZMITORS..... .. . . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081105-150200-to-20081105-170200.mp3" length="114679298" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081105-150200-to-20081105-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>29 October  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Outta the haunted garage comes &quot;Spook Spook a Goo-Goo&quot; with:
THE SURF COASTERS, KING DAPPER COMBO, THE CRAMPS, GOOGLE A, THE 3-D INVISIBLES, GROOVIE GHOULIES, THE SUBSONICS, THE FAMOUS MONSTERS, THE HOODS, ROCKIN' RYAN AND THE REAL GONNERS,  MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, THE HEXXERS, THE CREEPY CREEPS, THE SWING RAYS, THE BEGILED, THE INVISIBLE EYES, GRAVEDIGGER V, THE ZOMBIE IV, LORDS OF ALTAMONT, DIG MA'S GRAVE, DEAD BOLT, THE SEEDS, THE EVAPORATORS, CASPER THE FRIENDLY GHOST, THE VICIOUS CYCLES, COUNT BARCULA AND THE EAST VANPIRES, THE FIENDS, LADY DOTTIE AND THE DIAMONDS...</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go's &quot;Spook Spook a Goo-Goo&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081029-150000-to-20081029-170100.mp3" length="115612544" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081029-150000-to-20081029-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>22 October  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tripping outta the garage thru Psychesville into the western plains of THE MODELOS!
TOMORROW, THE GREEN HOUR, THE LA DE DA'S, LORDS OF GRAVITY, THE BLUES MAGOOS, THE CRUSADERS, THE MESS MAKERS, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE DOWN'N'OUTS,THE OKMONIKS, THE STOLEN MINKS, THE GREEN TELESCOPES, THE SPACESHITS, STEREOPHONIC SPACE SOUND UNLIMITED, THE WIERDIES, THE PUSSYCATS, THE WIGS, EUX AUTRES, THE DREAM SYNDICATE, THE BOSS MARTIANS, THE FIENDS, THE FLAKES, THE PANDORAS, THE MODELOS, BEN VAUGHN, DYLAN THOMAS AND THE VANCOUVER VIPERS, THE WILDEBEESTS, GROOP, ALTERNATE ACTION, THE ONE NIGHT BAND.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081022-150000-to-20081022-170000.mp3" length="114655112" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081022-150000-to-20081022-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>15 October  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Out-a-control, flypped-out, tripped-out garage pounders by:
THE LYRES, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE CHIMPS, ? AND THE MYSTERIANS, THE SEEDS, THEE OH NO'S, THE CAVEMANISH BOYS, THE HANGEE V, THE SHAMS, COLOR ME PSYCHO, WAU Y LOS ARRRGHS!!!, THE MIDWAYS, PUSSY GALORE, THE WEIRDIES, LOS PLANTRONICS, TEENAGE HEAD, THE JOLTS, MOTORAMA, THE RAMBLIN' AMBASSADORS, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, THE LEATHER UPPERS, THE EXPLOSIVES, TEE AND THE CRUMPETS, THE LIME SPIDERS, THE FIENDS, THE STOLEN MINKS, MEN FROM S.P.E.C.T.R.E., THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE TELEPATHIC BUTTERFLIES, THE ORCHID HIGHWAY, THE TRANZMITORS, THE HEADLESS HORSEMEN, THE HITS, QUINTRON...</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081015-150000-to-20081015-170100.mp3" length="115612961" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081015-150000-to-20081015-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>1  October  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shakin' the 6Ts Action with the likes of:
THE LORDS OF ALTAMONT, THE UPPERCRUST, THE EVAPORATORS, THE WOOLLY BANDITS, THE TOP DRAWERS, THE WIPEOUTERS, FUN 100, THE BOLIDES, THE MINDS, INTERNATIONAL NOISE CONSPIRACY, 101 STRINGS, CHRISTINA AND THE BIPPIES, LORDS OF GRAVITY, THE MOJOMATICS, THE CREEPS, THE NELSONICS, THE SHAMBLES, YOUNG RIVAL, LOS CAMINOS, THE WILDE MANIACS, THE WEIRDIES, THE FLESHTONES, BOBBY J &amp; THE GENERATIONS, THE BIRDS, THE CYNICS, THE STOLEN MINKS, FUAD AND THE FEZZTONES, THE SCOUTS, THE KLEPSTONES, THE GREEN HOUR, JERSEY THURSDAY, THE HIGH DIALS !!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081001-150300-to-20081001-170100.mp3" length="112762766" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20081001-150300-to-20081001-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>24  September  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Ripping Garage Rock the 1st hour and Gripping Mod-Pop the 2nd hour plus an interview with Rod of Novillero.
Hour #1:
THE GHASTLY ONES, MONDO TOPLESS, THE GONADS, THE ALOHAS, THE WIERDIES, THE RIDE THEORY, THE BLACK LIPS, THE MORLOCKS, THE HEARTACHES, THE WORST, THE BOGEYMEN, THE TREE, THE MOJOMATICS, THE LAUNDRONAUTS, THE JIGSAW SEEN, THE GREEN HOUR, SPODGENBESS ABOUNDS.
Hour #2:
THE DATSONS, THE JESSICA FLETCHERS, THE SUGARPLASTIC, THE SPRING COLLECTION, ---NOVILLERO---, THE TELEPATHIC BUTTERFLIES, THE HIGH DIALS, THE DEAD GHOSTS, LOS CAMINOS, THE B-LINES, SUBCITY DWELLERS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go !!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080924-150200-to-20080924-170200.mp3" length="114679298" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080924-150200-to-20080924-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>17  September  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Lid Flippin' Garage Greatness and the world premier of the new James T. Kirks record! (plus interview with Ted of the James T. Kirks)
with Roughneck Rompers by:
THE MIRICLE WORKERS, THE GOLDSTARS, CINECYDE, THE LOVE ME NOTS, MR. AIRPLANE MAN, THE GRUESOMES, THE MIDWAYS, THE OPTIC NERVE, THE BUG NASTIES, THE ULTRA 5, THE SMUGGLERS, THE DRAGS, THE FINE LINES, THE REAL PILLS, THE NEINS,  THE TOP DRAWERS, THE EXOTICS, NOVILLERO, FRANK VENTURA &amp; THE CRESENTS, THE JAMES T. KIRKS, YOUNG RIVAL, THE GREEN HOUR BAND, THE HIGH DIALS... . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080917-150100-to-20080917-170400.mp3" length="117553262" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080917-150100-to-20080917-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10  September  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2008 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzed-up garage numbers by the following r'n'r bumblers:
THE HATE BOMBS, BATTERSHELL, THE OMENS, THE WILDEBEESTS, BLOODY HOLLIES, THE TREBELS, PRIMORDIALS, SATURN V featuring ORBIT, SADDLESORES, LOS CAMINOS, THE AMAZING SPIDER MEN, DUCHESS AND THE DUKE, THE ALOHAS, THE SUNSETS, BARRACUDA'S, THE GROUPIES, THE DISHRAGS, THE WORRYIN' KIND, NOVILLERO,  HUSKER DU, EXPLODERS, THE SPARKLES, THE TVees, ROYAL NONESUCH, CHESTERFIELD KINGS, TOP DRAWERS, THE WEIRDIES, SUBSONICS, PARALLELS, YOUNG RIVAL, DEFEKTORS, THE GET QUICK, THE BEEKEEPERS, WEATHERED PINES, PEP TORES, THE HIGH DIALS..</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080910-150200-to-20080910-170400.mp3" length="116593745" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080910-150200-to-20080910-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>27  August  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Organ-poundin', ass-shakin', fuzz-pumpin' garage thumpers from
THE PRIESTS, THE MANFIELDS, PLAYTHINGS, GODDAMNED GENTLEMEN, LOS CAMINOS, THE RAPIERS, RON DRAND ORCH, ELDORADO, THE THANES, LIVE WIRES, THE LEN PRICE 3, SWEET BABY, UNTOLD FABLES, LUNA, GREEN HOUR, DWARVES, TOP DRAWERS, S.C.O.T.S., LES LUTINS, THE CREEPERS, THE CREEPY CREEPS, THE CREEPSHOW, THE BRAINS, THE SURF MESSIAHS, WOOLLY BANDITS, THE SEEDS, B-LINES, WALL OF VOODOO, TEEN APPEAL, THE EVAPORATORS, JIGSAW SEEN, VANCOUVER NIGHTS...</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080827-150200-to-20080827-170200.mp3" length="114690140" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080827-150200-to-20080827-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>20  August  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzz-packed Garage Sex-plosions with:
THE SUPERBEES, THEE FOURGIVEN, RIFF RANDELS, THE DEL MONAS, FUAD AND THE FEZZTONES, INVISIBLE EYES, GREEN HOUR,
THE ORANGE ALIBASTOR MUSHROOM, THE FIENDS, THE BUG NASTIES, THE PRIMORDIALS, THE SIN-TONES, THE MILKEES, ROCKET K,
HOT SHOTS, GOOGLE A, SLOWPOKE AND THE SMOKE, THE SHITBIRDS, RAIN PARADE, THE FOUR CORNERS, THE GRUESOMES, PEABODY HERMITAGE, CABARET VOLTAIRE, THE SICK ROSE, THEE MYSPELLED, YOUNG RIVAL, THE BOBBYTEENS, THE ZEROS, THE WAX MUSEUMS,
NO BUNNY, DEAD GHOSTS, HIGH DIALS......</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080820-150100-to-20080820-170500.mp3" length="118508609" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080820-150100-to-20080820-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>13  August  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Hip shakin', groove makin' ditties and an interview with Tony Bardack of The Pointed Sticks!     ---plus tunes from
THE MIDWAYS, IRVING KLAWS, BREADMAKERS, BOOBY TRAPS, Q65, DOCTOR EXPLOSION, MOTARDS, HEFNERS, UGLY BEATS, 5 CANADIANS, OLD HAUNTS, YOUNG RIVAL, 3 O'CLOCK, THREE 4 TENS, GREEN HOUR, LAUGHING SKY, SLOWPOKE &amp; THE SMOKE, BOMBORAS, ULTRASONICAS, LAUNDRONAUTS, CYNICS, EVAPORATORS, POINTED STICKS, GABRIEL &amp; HIS ANGELS, HIGH BIRDS, DEAD GHOSTS, PARALLELS, BOB LOG III, ELDORADO, SWANK.........</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080813-150200-to-20080813-170300.mp3" length="115632143" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080813-150200-to-20080813-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>06  August  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Spazzin' out with THE LYRES, PRIMORDIALS, FORTUNE &amp; MALTESE, MAGGOTS, POINTED STICKS, INVISIBLE EYES, SEX MUSEUM, JAP KAT, BLACK LIPS, PANDORAS, NIGHT MIST, PURE COUNTRY GOLD,
YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, DEKES OF HAZZARD, THE 4 INSTANTS,
THE CAKE PEOPLE, ZEROS, GO-BETWEENS, GRUESOMES,
MORNING SHAKES, GIRL TROUBLE, HYPSTERZ, GREEN HOUR,
DEAD GHOSTS, PARALLELS, UNCALLED FOR, GRAVEDIGGER V, STRANGLERS, THE DADDS, THE MOXIES, OKMONIKS, GONN,
GIRL TROUBLE, ORCHID HIGHWAY.....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080806-150100-to-20080806-170200.mp3" length="115648406" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080806-150100-to-20080806-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>30 July  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzy numbers, drunkin' bumblers and wobbily drummers demonstrated by: THE STAGGERS, THE CANNIBALS, MARKED MEN, SADIES, THE NUTHIN'S, FUAD &amp; THE FEZZTONES, JAYBEES,
DEAD GHOSTS, FRUZZLE &amp; THE FAZZLETONES,PURPLE MERKINS,
ZOLAR X, DUKES OF HAMBURG, SLOWPOKE &amp; THE SMOKE, JOLTS
STEREO SHOESTRING, EVAPORATORS, MUCK &amp; THE MIRES, GRUESOMES, Y'ALLS, CHILLS, THE BUG NASTIES, TELEPATHIC BUTTERFLIES, GREEN HOUR, CREEPY CREEPS, BOSS MONSTERS, VICEROYS, TVEES, RIDE THEORY, TRAP DOORS, LES LUTINS, POINTED STICKS......</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080730-150000-to-20080730-170200.mp3" length="116569142" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080730-150000-to-20080730-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25 July  08</title><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>POP**POWER-POP**INDIE-POP --&gt; IT'S POP-A-MATIC!!!
with your host Frank Rumbletone, featuring:
THE CHILLS, TELEVISION PERSONALITIES, JASIMINE MINKS, GO-BETWEENS, VASILINES, THE EMBARRASSMENT, FAT TUPIPS, WOLFHOUNDS, CHAMELEONS, HALF MAN HALF BISCUIT, CHRIS KNOX,
POP WILL EAT ITSELF, DOUBLEHAPPYS, AMERICAN FLAG, BREAKAWAYS,
JIGSAW SEEN, MATT BRUNO, NEGRO PROBLEM, THE GROOVE FARM,
THE BATS, POI DOG PONDERING, RED GUITARS, THE FLATMATES,
RIC MENCK, LOOK BLUE GO PURPLE, BIG BANG POW, HOODOO GURUS...</description><itunes:subtitle>POP-A-MATIC</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080725-180000-to-20080725-193700.mp3" length="92707568" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080725-180000-to-20080725-193700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>23 July 2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 15:05:15 -0700</pubDate><description></description><itunes:subtitle>Ska-T hosts  Rumbletone Radio A Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080723-150515-to-20080723-170011.mp3" length="109825835" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080723-150515-to-20080723-170011.mp3</guid></item><item><title>16 July  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Simply put: AN ABSOLULTELY KICKASS SHOW OF TRIPPED-OUT GARAGE AND WYLDE PSYCH!!! From the likes of KING KHAN &amp; THE SHRINES, THE MUMMIES, SPOILED BRATS, THE HOODS, TNT, THE SHAMBLES,
VICIOUS CYCLES, YO-YO'S, PARALLELS, TVEES, LOOKING GLASSES,
THINGS TO COME, GREEN HOUR BAND, THE UNRELATED SEGMENTS,
JOLTS, BOURBONS, LARRY AND THE BLUENOTES, FUZZTONES, ZIP GUNS,
LAUNDONAUTS, THE JOLT, ROCKIN' RYAN AND THE REAL GONERS, HILLBILLY SOUL SURFERS, RAMBLIN' AMBASSADORS, MONOCHROME SET,
OKMONICS, CHAD ALLEN AND THE REFLECTIONS, PUSSY CATS,
THE SHADOWS, DICKIES, BOONARAAS, MURDER CITY DEVELS.. .. .. .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080716-150100-to-20080716-170500.mp3" length="118510277" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080716-150100-to-20080716-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>09 July  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Mind-melting summer-sweltering garage-slop with
FUAD &amp; THE FEZZTONES, THE YOUNG PLAYTHINGS, PANDORAS,
SAHARA HOTNIGHTS, MACH III, FLESHTONES, THE HEARD, MIDWAYS, CAVEMANISH BOYS, JOLTS, RAMONETURES, REAL LOSERS, SAINTS, JESSICA FLETCHERS, ADVERTS, ARMATAGE SHANKS, PRIESTS, PRIMATES, WORST, MASHED POTATOES, FASTBACKS, CREEPY CREEPS, CHARMING SNAKES, TRANZMITORS, ORANGES, POINTED STICKS, HYPSTERZ, STEMS, LORDS OF GRAVITY, LOVE ME NOTS, BAD BEER ..</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080709-150100-to-20080709-170100.mp3" length="114677630" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080709-150100-to-20080709-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>02  July  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Sun-soaked, mind-rotted, fuzz pleasures from the likes of LARRY AND THE LOAFERS,  GRUESOMES, WILDEBEESTS, RENEGADES, FLAKES, PROSTITUTES, KING KHAN AND THE SHRINES, SURFADELICS, OMENS, HIGH TENSIONS, SHIMMYS, VENDETTAS, ACTIVE DOG, APES, COSMIC DROPOUTS, VANCOUGAR,, VICIOUS CYCLES, UGLY BEATS,  VOODUO, ROYAL CHAINS, WAX MUSEUMS,  KURLINGS, VAPID, GREEN HORNETS, MAOW, PRIMORDIALS... .. . . . . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080702-150300-to-20080702-170200.mp3" length="113719781" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080702-150300-to-20080702-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25  June  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A Beeramid of staggering Rock'n'Roll stacked with
THE TEENAGE HARLOTS, MORLOCKS, BOARS, HOLLYWOOD SINNERS, SURFADELICS, PRIMORDIALS, MINSTRELS, SIGHTS, EVAPORATORS, HARA KEE REES, DIK VAN DYKES, EXPLODING WHITE MICE, SEEDS, CANADIAN SQUIRES, SIGHTS, THEE SNUFF PROJECTS, JOLTS,
POINTED STICKS, LEGENDARY INVISIBLE MEN, GOLDEN LEMONS, WILLOWZ, FUAD AND THE FEZZTONES, BLUESTARS, YOUNG RIVAL,
PRISONERS, TREMBLES, OKMONIKS, RAMBLIN' AMBASSADORS,
RED HEARTS, SIMPLY SAUCER, LOYALTIES, GREEN PAJAMAS, JOLTS,
GREEN HOUR BAND, CELIBATE RIFLES, MOUNT McKINLEYS .. .. . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080625-150100-to-20080625-170400.mp3" length="117554096" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080625-150100-to-20080625-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>18  June  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>All the FUZZ and twice the ACTION!!! with THE WOOLY BANDITS, LOST SOUNDS, LOS PEYOTES, OKMONIKS, PRIMORDIALS, TRAP DOORS, KRAVIN' &quot;A&quot;s, MIDWAYS, REZILLOS, BOLIDES, GRISWALDS, MANIPULATORS, MISSING LINKS, FALLOUTS, CHILLS, MOPS,
MORNING SHAKES, BEGILED, PARALLELS, TVees, CREEPY CREEPS, YOUNG PENNSYLVANIANS, COCONUT COOLOUTS, OUTSIDERS, VANCOUGAR, DOW JONES AND THE INDUSTRIALS, DEVO, EPOXIES, LOS CHICOS .... ... . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080618-150200-to-20080618-170800.mp3" length="120427226" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080618-150200-to-20080618-170800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>11  June  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>We spazzed to the fuzzy, frantic, flip-out sounds of
The Executioners, Eyes, Midways, Hunchedback Men, TVees, Los Chicos, ? &amp; The Mysterians, Frantic V, Fumestones, Spectors, Shams, Pebbles and Bam Bam, Frigg a-Go-Go,
Tell-Tale Hearts, Rusty Springfield, Muffs, Jolts, Trazmitors, Dead Ghosts, Primordials, Bug Nasties,
Los Imbasils, Fuad &amp; The Fezztones, Laundanauts .. .. .. .  .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080611-150300-to-20080611-170400.mp3" length="115637147" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080611-150300-to-20080611-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>04  June  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2008 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Strumin' Fuzzamentals with THE LOONS, COOCONUT COOLOUTS, SATELLITERS, WINDOW PAYNES, HEARTACHES, ORCHID HIGHWAY,
COCTAILS, SCREAMIN' RAYS, HORROR POPS, LOS EXPLOSIVOS,
THE SLURPS, LOS TWANGERS, THE TVees, ROYAL CHAINS,
BUG NASTIES, THE CAVERNARIOS, MANSFIELDS, SWANK, SUPERNOVA, SPRING COLLECTION, REAL PILLS, JERSEY THURSDAY, TELKRIMEN, IMMEDIATES, FUZZTONES...... .. . . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080604-150000-to-20080604-170100.mp3" length="115614629" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080604-150000-to-20080604-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>28  May  2008]</title><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzadelic Freakout with THE DUKES OF HAMBURG,
CRAWLING WALLS, CURSE OF THE HORSEFLESH, BLUES MAGOOS,
DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, CHESTERFIELD KINGS, AARDVARKS, SHAMBLES, PRETTY THINGS, ROUTE 66, BARRACUDAS, TVEES,
MAN OR ASTROMAN, CREEPY CREEPS, SPACE SHITS, UNTAMED YOUTH,
B-GIRLS, YOUNG SAVAGES, ROCKIN' RYAN &amp; THE REAL GONNERS,
ZIPGUNS, HITS, DOWN'N'OUTS, SPITS, PLEASURE SUIT, OKMONIKS,
TEENAGE HEAD, CPC GANGBANGS, LIME SPIDERS, GREEN HOUR BAND,
UNCLAIMED.... .. . . . . . . . . .   .    .        .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080528-150300-to-20080528-170400.mp3" length="115637981" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080528-150300-to-20080528-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>21  May  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 15:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>If the Garage is Rockin' don't come a Knockin'! Shakin' it with NO BUNNY, THE EVAPORATORS, LES SEXAREENOS, OKMONIKS, LOVE ME NOTS, CLONES, DECEIVERS, SUBSONICS, MOXIES, VIVIAN GIRLS, SICK ROSE, GREEN HOUR BAND, WARLOCKS, THREE O'CLOCK, GHASTLEY ONES, CUTE LEPERS, POWER CHORDS, RACHAEL GORDEN, 5 AMERICANS, LES FLANEURS, THE EVENT,
SURF MESIAHS, VICIOUS CYCLES, VANCOUGAR, DEAD GHOSTS,
B-LINES, TRANZMITORS, LAST OF THE BAD MEN, MUDHONEY,
BOSS MONSTERS, LAUNDRONAUTS, SPRING COLLECTION, STINKIES ......... ....  .. .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080521-150500-to-20080521-170000.mp3" length="109887134" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080521-150500-to-20080521-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>14  May  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>INSTRO au GO-GO with THE RAMBLIN' AMBASSADORS' Brent Cooper (ex-Huevos Rancheros)Interview &amp; Feature along with
THE MAGGOTS, STAGGERS, MIDWAYS, MAGIC SWIRLING SHIP, OKMONIKS,
TRIO, SMUGGLERS, BREADMAKERS, NELSONICS, CYNICS, PEACOCKS, HARA-KEE-REES, NO FUN, TEENGENERATE, SATISFACTION, MUSSIES, SPLODGINESSABOUNDS, CRYIN' OUTLOUDS, LAUNDRONAUTS,
WE THE PEOPLE, GREEN HOUR BAND, HUEVOS RANCHEROS .. .. . . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080514-150200-to-20080514-170600.mp3" length="118522787" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080514-150200-to-20080514-170600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>07 May  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 15:09:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Sliding down the slimey slope of rock'n'roll with:
THE FORBIDDEN TIGERS, CREEPY CREEPS, THE BRISTOLS,
FLAT DUO JETS, PUSSY GALORE, LAUNDRONAUTS, GROOP,
ROYAL PENDLETONS, BURPS, RAIN PARADE, HEADQUARTERS,
GREEN HOUR BAND, URBAN SURF KINGS, VANCOUGAR, BARRIER,
THE TVEES, U-J3RK5, PLIMSOULS, TRAP DOORS, DEAD GHOSTS,
MIRICLE WORKERS, THE NECESSARIES, TRAP DOORS, THE WIGS,
THE WALL, LOS PLANTRONICS, GOLDSTARS, FABIENNE DELSOL .....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080507-150900-to-20080507-170400.mp3" length="109889636" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080507-150900-to-20080507-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>30  April  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>THE LAUNDRONAUTS invade with their swirling, garage-cleaning action! Also, thunderin' sounds by THE MIDWAYS, HEARTACHES, GRAVEDIGGER V, WILD WEEKEND, TEENAGE HEAD, SCISSORS, SQUIDDO, TEDDY &amp; HIS PATCHES, RAY BRANDES, CHAINS, MONSTERS FROM MARS, UNKNOWNS, MYSTERY MACHINE, OKMONIKS, FLESHTONES, THE WORST, UPPER CRUST, GREEN HOUR BAND, HOODS, VAPID, ZIPGUNS, FIENDS, DOCTORS EXPLOSION, IRVING CLAWS, DEADCATS, NEW FUGITIVES
.... .. . .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080430-150300-to-20080430-170400.mp3" length="115636730" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080430-150300-to-20080430-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>23  April  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 15:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Interviews with Ian Tiles of THE POINTED STICKS and
Rob Thompson of The HARD ROCK MINERS / THE HIGHBALLS
plus goin' zonkers with:
THE PHANTOM JETS, WOOLLY BANDITS, BOSS MARTIANS, HI-RISERS, FLESHTONES, GREEN ON RED, POWER CHORDS, ZEROS, BARRACUDAS,
OKMONIKS, DRAGS, TEENAGE HEAD, HITS, VICIOUS CYCLES, BIZ, LAUNDRONAUTS, CRUSADERS, ELDORADO, RAMBLIN' AMBASSADORS,
ROYAL GRAND PRIX ...  ..  .. .  .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080423-150400-to-20080423-170800.mp3" length="118510277" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080423-150400-to-20080423-170800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>16  April  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzy numbers from drunkin' bumblers by the likes of
THE OKMONIKS, THURSTON HOWLERS, GIRL TROUBLE, FLESHTONES, FLAKES, THEE CRUCIALS, MARSHMALLOW OVERCOAT, MODELOS,  COCONUT COOLOUTS, PURE COUNTRY GOLD, ROCKETFINS, EXOTICS SALVATION ARMY, SHAMS, SOUTHERN CULTURE ON THE SKIDS, 
VAPID, THE HEELS, NOMADS, LAUNDRONAUTS, SOUND EXPLOSION, HIGHBALLS, HARD ROCK MINERS, BUGHOUSE 5, TRANZMITORS, 
LES HELL ON HEELS, CHAD ALLAN A &amp; THE REFLECTIONS...  .. .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080416-150200-to-20080416-170500.mp3" length="117552011" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080416-150200-to-20080416-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>9  April  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 15:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzy Mammaries from Back in the Daze by THE WILDEBEESTS, THE TRAP DOORS, ORANGU-TONES, LITTLE BITS, TREBLEMAKERS, BOARS, UNTAMED YOUTH, THEE MANIPULATORS, EUX AUTRES, GRUESOMES, TONICS, MEAN THINGS, TONICS, FRIARS OF YOUTH, VOLUME OUT, INTOXICA, DEAD BOLT, MAOW, THAT'S A NO NO!, PAWNEE DRIVE, SWANK, LOS MENTAS, VIPERS, THEE MAKEOUT PARTY, CREEPY CREEPS, HIGHBALLS, SHEETAH ET LES WEISSMULLER, ROCKIN' ROADRUNNERS...
.........  ..... ... .. .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080409-150500-to-20080409-170500.mp3" length="114678881" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080409-150500-to-20080409-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>2  April  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A Fuzzy Afternoon Delight with the raw, wilde and primitive sounds of The SWAMP RATS, COCONUT COOLOUTS, EARACHES, OPTIC NERVE, FORGOTTEN REBELS, RESONAIRES, SMUGGLERS, LES ARTYFACTS, CHRISTINA &amp; THE BIPPIES, SHE CREATURES, THE FAST, STIV BATORS, RAISED BY WOLVES, BAD APPLES, POINTED STICKS, OSCILLATORS, OMENS, MOUSE &amp; THE TRAPS, CYNICS, HOODOO GURUS, ELOIS, STAIRS, CREEPY CREEPS, VAPID, I GANZI, TRANZMITORS, GIANT LEECHES..............</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080402-150000-to-20080402-170600.mp3" length="120401789" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080402-150000-to-20080402-170600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>26  March  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Primitive, Raw, Garage A.C.T.I.O.N dished-up by:
THE FAB FEZMEN V, MUCK &amp; THE MIRES, URGES, SPITFIRES, REBERBERATORS, DEVO,  STEREOPHONIC SPACE SOUND UNLIMITED, THEE TUMBITAS, DEAD GHOSTS, DWARVES, 64 FUNNYCARS, EVAPORATORS, FLESHTONES, GROOVIES, LORD HIGH FIXERS, FREAKOUTS, INVISIBLE EYES, HEFNERS, GENTLEMEN CALLERS, CREEPS, UNTOLD FABLES, X-RAYS, HITS, BRANDED.........</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080326-145900-to-20080326-170400.mp3" length="119443940" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080326-145900-to-20080326-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>19  March  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Special feature on German Garage with THE SATELLITERS, GOLDEN LEMONS, TORPEDO MONKEYS, BATS, DIABOLIKS, KENTUCKYS, HARA-KEE-REES, SLAVES, CURLEE WURLEE  plus fuzzy delights by the LOST SOUNDS, UGLY BEATS, MASONICS, FLESHTONES, VON ZIPPERS, REAL KIDS, STEREOSCOPE JERK EXPLOSION, VULCANEERS, THEE OH SEES, ZIP GUNS, GROOVIE GHOULIES, DIRTBOMBS........</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080319-150000-to-20080319-170400.mp3" length="118487759" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080319-150000-to-20080319-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>12  March  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>We tripped down the time-tunnel into the land of BARACUDAS, URGES, GREEN HORNES, BOOZE, MAGIC PLANTS, TELL-TALE HEARTS, TIJUANA BIBLES, MISSUNDERSTOOD, MORLOCKS, ETTES, DAVIE ALLEN, VOODUO, GREEN HOUR, RIPPERS, TRAP DOORS, ATLANTICS, DEAD GHOSTS, CHESTERFIELD KINGS .......   ...   ....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080312-150300-to-20080312-170400.mp3" length="115636730" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080312-150300-to-20080312-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>5  March  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Springtime Garage-Cleaning with fuzz-scrubbing power
provided by:  THE FLAKES, BOOBY TRAPS, CREEPY CREEPS, HATE BOMBS, DEMON'S CLAWS, THREE FOR TENS, EVAPORATORS, ZOLAR X, POINTED STICKS, FONDAS, WEIRDOS, RIPPERS, MAKERS, SHAMS, TRANZMITORS, THE PRICE OF DRUGS THESE DAYS IS THROUGH THE ROOF, FREDDY AND THE FOURGONE CONCLUSIONS, CLONES, MONSTERS FROM MARS!...........</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080305-150100-to-20080305-170400.mp3" length="117552428" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080305-150100-to-20080305-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>27  FEB  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 15:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>RARE PSYCH and GARAGE from the vaults of Vancouver's Dandelion Records. Jems from the likes of THE SOUND SANDWICH, AMON DUUL 2, MORGAN, FAINE JADE, SILVER APPLES, SHADOWS OF KNIGHT, CLEAR LIGHT, FEVER TREE, MOTIONS, SATINS, PIERRE HENRI, DRAGON FLY, CREEPY JOHN THOMAS,   MISSING LINKS, THE WEEDS............</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go's Dandelion Special</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080227-150300-to-20080227-171000.mp3" length="121361306" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080227-150300-to-20080227-171000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>13 February  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 15:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>TRIP THE FUZZ FANTASTIC with the likes of THE APE SHITS, DOLLY ROCKER MOVEMENT, BLACK LIPS, CREEPY CREEPS, EVAPORATORS, LOVE, URGES, MACH V, BOARS, MEMPHIS MORTICIANS, A-BONES, VANCOUGAR, TRANZMITORS, HARA-KEE-REES, FUZZTONES, PAINTED SHIP..................</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080213-150200-to-20080213-170300.mp3" length="115647572" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080213-150200-to-20080213-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>6  February  2008</title><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 15:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Back from So. Cal. with a slew of new freakin' garage ditties!
....including the Miscreants, Creepy Creeps, Rockin' Ryan &amp; the Real Gonners, the Drags, thee Fine Lines, Real Pills, Chesterfield Kings, Roy Loney, Lords of Gravity, Meteors, Volcanos, Frantic V, Things to Come, Quarter After, Armitage Shanks, The Evaporators.....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080206-150100-to-20080206-170100.mp3" length="114678881" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20080206-150100-to-20080206-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>12 December  2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2007 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>X-mas a go-go!!! Primative, fuzzed-out garage mayhem with Christmas tunes tossed throughout. Today we celebrated with the Urges, the Strangemen, Del Monas, Marked Men, Jessica Fletchers, Gruesomes, We The People, Shutdown 66, Kon Tikis, Triple Doubles, Doctor's Explosion, Crusaders, Dead Cats, Ladies Night, Modelos, and the Stomach Mouths................</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071212-150000-to-20071212-170200.mp3" length="116572061" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071212-150000-to-20071212-170200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>5  December  2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2007 15:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Wailin' fuzz buzzin' numbers from the likes of the Nackers, Orangu-tones, Night Crawlers, Del-vetts, Elastic Band, Ultra-twist, Shades, Roc LaRue &amp; the 3 Pals, Zolar X, Tranzmitors, Girl Trouble, Leather Uppers,  and LIVE INTERVIEW
with LITTLE HAMM (Rob Dayton) of CANNED HAMM!!!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071205-150200-to-20071205-170000.mp3" length="112766936" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071205-150200-to-20071205-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>28  November 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2007 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Fuzzy-freak-outs &amp; slippery-slime by the Fe Fi Fo Fums, the La Dee Das, the Bad Apples, the Purple Merkins, the Shambles, the Midways, Miricle Workers, Frantic V, Meanie Geanies, Parallels, Sadies, Mummies, Jersey Thursday, and the Diplomats of Solid Sound.........................</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071128-150000-to-20071128-170500.mp3" length="119445608" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071128-150000-to-20071128-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>21  November 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2007 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>From the vaults in the Rumbletone Lab came the oozing sounds and fuzz-driping sludge of the Invisible Eyes, The Urges,  Thurston Howlers, Green on Red, Epoxies, Klaus Wunderlich, Meteors, Hits, Jolts, Hard-ons, Pointed Sticks, Inca Babies, Les Garcons, and the Tiki Tones....... along with other dangerous toxins!!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071121-150000-to-20071121-170400.mp3" length="118487759" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071121-150000-to-20071121-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>14  November 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Outta-the-garage came the greasy, grimmy and gritty sounds
of the Urges, the Dorktones, Magic Plants, Yard Trauma, Sick Rose, BBQ, Ray Condo, Fatal Flying Guilloteens, Chesterfield Kings, Swell Maps, Beat By Five, Spitfires, Mach V, We The People, Ultra V, District Six, Slumberjack and the Jaybees... ....... plus a 'hole lotta mo'e!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071114-150000-to-20071114-170500.mp3" length="119456867" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071114-150000-to-20071114-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>7 November 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2007 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Action packed fuzzadelic-freakout with DMZ, Intoxica, Phantom Rockers, Love, Men from S.P.E.C.T.R.E., Boss Martians, Morlocks, Riff Randells, Painted Ship, Misunderstood, Creepy Creeps, Flying Dutchmen.............</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071107-150000-to-20071107-170300.mp3" length="117542837" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071107-150000-to-20071107-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>31 October 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Gore Gore a Go-Go- Halloween Spook-tacular! with scary tunes by The Fiends, Deadcats, Famous Monsters, 1313 Mockingbird Lane, Groovie Ghoulies, Ghastly Ones, Mr. Gasser &amp; the Weirdos, Honeymoon Killers, Witchdoctors, Cramps, Evaporators, Deadbolt and The Jolts......

Special call-ins by Flying Saucer Mike of the Deadcats/ Kon Tikis and Joey Jolt of the Jolts/ Remores!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio's Gore Gore a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071031-150100-to-20071031-170400.mp3" length="117563270" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071031-150100-to-20071031-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>24 October 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2007 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Caveman grunts, guitars that thump, sleazy tunes by skin pounding baboons brought to you by Los Peyotes, the Pills, Curlee Wurlee, Meteors, Cool Jerks, Blood Shot Bill, 3:00, Freakouts, Murphy &amp; the Mob, Vooduo, and Doctor's Explosion!!! .... ... .. .</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071024-150200-to-20071024-170700.mp3" length="119480636" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071024-150200-to-20071024-170700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>17 October 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2007 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Shakin' crazy bones and spinnin' wyld tones with the Spaceshits, Evaporators, Nightstalkers, Man or Astroman, Resonaires, Thanes, Paybacks, Woolly Bandits, Bluestars, and the Mongols......!!!!......................!!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071017-150300-to-20071017-170500.mp3" length="116605421" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071017-150300-to-20071017-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>10 October 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A funtime frolic through fuzzland with the Satelliters, Cynics, Black Lips, Woggles, Les Baroques, 45s, the Craig, Apes, Highballs...... and an interview with Swank!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071010-150300-to-20071010-170600.mp3" length="117563687" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071010-150300-to-20071010-170600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>3 October  2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2007 15:06:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Back from So Cal with a slew of brand new rippin' garage recordz! Today we rocked out to The Creepy Creeps, Black Lips, The Love Me Nots, Pure Country Gold, The Monsters, Kon Tikis, and ? and the Mysterians.......!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071003-150600-to-20071003-170500.mp3" length="113732291" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20071003-150600-to-20071003-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>26 September 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2007 14:59:02 -0700</pubDate><description></description><itunes:subtitle>Julie Matson fill in for Frankie!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070926-145902-to-20070926-170235.mp3" length="118067840" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070926-145902-to-20070926-170235.mp3</guid></item><item><title>29 August 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2007 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Primitive Garage Mania with the Goldstars, Boonaraas, Thingz, Pills, Woggles, Breadmakers, Chains, Hex Dispensers, Mojomatics...... and other fuzzy creatures that thump-thump in the night!!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070829-150100-to-20070829-170300.mp3" length="116605838" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070829-150100-to-20070829-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>22  August  07</title><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2007 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Fuzzy summertime fun with the Pointed Sticks, Baracudas, Ettes, Heartaches, A-Bones, Zombie Ghost Train, and the Headless Hearsemen!!!  ...and a whole lot more....</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070822-150100-to-20070822-170300.mp3" length="116605838" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070822-150100-to-20070822-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>15  August 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2007 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Time trippin' with the Satelliters, Kaisers, Ugly Beats, Fiends, Staggers, Q65, Dishrags, and the Stereoscope Jerk Explosion!!!!!      .......to name a few.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070815-150000-to-20070815-170400.mp3" length="118499435" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070815-150000-to-20070815-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>8  August 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2007 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Kranked-up Garage Mayhem with the likes of the Treblemakers, Ghastly Ones, Shimmys, Pointed Sticks, Brimstones, Ultra-twist, and Marked Men!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070808-150000-to-20070808-170300.mp3" length="117541586" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070808-150000-to-20070808-170300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>1 August  2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2007 15:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Rippin' Garage Action &amp; Power-Pop! ...a brief interview with Billy Bones of Raised By Wolves/ Lizard People... and ended with a bit of psychedelic soup.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070801-150200-to-20070801-170000.mp3" length="112774859" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070801-150200-to-20070801-170000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>25 July 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2007 14:59:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Today's menu featured roasted Mod-kebab with a side of mixed Texan-garage and chilled Japanese rock'n'saki.</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070725-145900-to-20070725-170100.mp3" length="116583320" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070725-145900-to-20070725-170100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>18 July  2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2007 15:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Wiggin' out with the Shimmys, the Nackers, Dr. Explosion, Dick Hyman, Sky Saxon, the Fuckidies, the Freakouts  and many other far-out garage maniacs!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070718-150300-to-20070718-170400.mp3" length="115647989" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070718-150300-to-20070718-170400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>11 July 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2007 15:00:08 -0700</pubDate><description>Bryce (Third Time's The Charm) filled in today!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio A-Go Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070711-150008-to-20070711-165923.mp3" length="113994167" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070711-150008-to-20070711-165923.mp3</guid></item><item><title>04 July 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2007 15:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A fun-time rockin' garage show with mini-features on The Omens and The Tell-Tale Hearts!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070704-150000-to-20070704-170500.mp3" length="119456450" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070704-150000-to-20070704-170500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>27 June 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 15:00:05 -0700</pubDate><description>a  rockin' good time with a feature on scandanavian garage!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio a Go-Go</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070627-150005-to-20070627-170039.mp3" length="115233074" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070627-150005-to-20070627-170039.mp3</guid></item><item><title>20 June 2007</title><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 15:00:46 -0700</pubDate><description>talked to Nikki Corvette today on the heels of her first ever show in Vancouver Monday June 25 @ Pub 340!</description><itunes:subtitle>Rumbletone Radio A-Go Go!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070620-150046-to-20070620-170100.mp3" length="114914486" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20070620-150046-to-20070620-170100.mp3</guid></item></channel></rss>