<?xml version="1.0"  ?>

	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" ><channel><title>CiTR -- The Copyright Experiment</title><description></description><itunes:summary></itunes:summary><itunes:author>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>The Copyright Experiment</itunes:subtitle><itunes:owner> <itunes:name>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:name><itunes:email>technicalservices@citr.ca</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href=""/><itunes:link rel="image" type="video/jpeg" href="">CiTR -- The Copyright Experiment</itunes:link><image><link></link><url></url><title>CiTR -- The Copyright Experiment</title></image><link></link><generator> podcast mate 2000</generator><item><title>copy/paste #3: Ringin in the Halloween</title><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 23:03:13 -0700</pubDate><description>I bring us into Halloween with a spooky Halloween dance mix.</description><itunes:subtitle>30 October 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141030-230313-to-20141031-000540.mp3" length="59704520" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141030-230313-to-20141031-000540.mp3</guid></item><item><title>copy/paste #2: Turn up</title><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 23:03:19 -0700</pubDate><description>all hip hop show!</description><itunes:subtitle>23 October 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141023-230319-to-20141024-000014.mp3" length="54404867" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141023-230319-to-20141024-000014.mp3</guid></item><item><title>copy/paste #1: Dive In</title><pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 23:03:09 -0700</pubDate><description>The show is now called copy/paste. On the first episode with the new name, I follow up a live broadcast from Sonic Topographies with an entire set of ambient and experimental electronic music. Brand new tunes from Andy Stott, Arca, Flying Lotus, and more. Press play and dive into your mind.</description><itunes:subtitle>16 October 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141016-230309-to-20141017-000616.mp3" length="60344198" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141016-230309-to-20141017-000616.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Mixed Bag</title><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 23:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Music I like, mixed for you. Includes brand new tunes from Caribou, SBTRKT, Anna Lunoe, Rae Sremmurd, and more.</description><itunes:subtitle>2 October 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141002-230100-to-20141003-000400.mp3" length="60230774" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141002-230100-to-20141003-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>More music from the electronic underground</title><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 23:02:33 -0700</pubDate><description>More music from the underground, including music from Sinoia Caves, Aphex Twin, and a bunch of other far-out artists.</description><itunes:subtitle>11 September 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140911-230233-to-20140912-000418.mp3" length="59034401" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140911-230233-to-20140912-000418.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Some tunes from the underground</title><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2014 23:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Some tunes I've been diggin' lately. Nothing free here unfortunately. Enjoy the mix.</description><itunes:subtitle>6 September 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140904-230100-to-20140905-000146.mp3" length="58089896" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140904-230100-to-20140905-000146.mp3</guid></item><item><title>50 - The Pirate Joe's Story (Final Episode)</title><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 23:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>In the final episode of the Copyright Experiment, Tim sits down with local businessman and dedicated disruptor Mike Hallat, who owns and operates Pirate Joe's. Recently his business was taken to court by Trader Joe's, but in true underdog fashion he prevailed. In our interview, we chat about the origins of Pirate Joe's, the importance of questioning rules, what it's like being labeled a pirate, how he beat a national grocery empire in court, and how it all can empower musicians to stick up for their their work as well. A fitting end to a show dedicated to questioning the rules and assumptions of the music industry.

Plus, we have time for a few more free tracks for you, with download links on the blog!</description><itunes:subtitle>28 August 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140828-230000-to-20140829-000400.mp3" length="61166522" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140828-230000-to-20140829-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>49 - We Write The Rules</title><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 23:00:59 -0700</pubDate><description>As The Copyright Experiment comes to a close at the end of this month, Tim reflects back on some of the lessons learned this past year about how the music industry ought to be. He also comes to the conclusion that there is a lot that we as music consumers and fans can do right now to taylor the music industry to our tastes. During this time of massive disruption and upheaval, we can write the rules of the new music industry. But, we do have to be conscious of how we are doing so. Listen in to find out how you can shape the music industry you want!</description><itunes:subtitle>21 August 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140821-230059-to-20140822-000529.mp3" length="61666505" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140821-230059-to-20140822-000529.mp3</guid></item><item><title>48 - Like This Post To Download</title><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 23:15:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Facebook made an announcement last week that is sure to rock the promotional abilities of independent musicians on Facebook. Using their omniscient benevolence, Facebook has decided that developers and page owners must not incentivise users to like their page, and instead have users like a page simply because they want to. The biggest consequence this will have in the independent music world is the death of Like To Download, a mechanism that allows users to like a page in order to download music for free. Tim explains how exactly this could hurt independent musicians specifically, and places it on the map of other tactics Facebook is using to drive up revenue at all costs.</description><itunes:subtitle>14 August 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140814-231500-to-20140815-000400.mp3" length="47752883" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140814-231500-to-20140815-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>47 - Return of the Patent Trolls</title><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 23:01:45 -0700</pubDate><description>Another patent troll is creeping its head up in the news recently, this time it's the patent holder for podcasting technology, shell company Personal Audio. Who is this vague sounding company? Why are they in the news now?? Can they really patent all podcasts??? Find the answer to these questions and more on this week's episode of, The Copyright Experiment!

Also another batch  of free tunes, cause  I know you like them so much. Enjoy.</description><itunes:subtitle>7 August 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140807-230145-to-20140808-000409.mp3" length="59656982" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140807-230145-to-20140808-000409.mp3</guid></item><item><title>46 - eBooks and a whole lotta music</title><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 23:01:43 -0700</pubDate><description>There's a class action lawsuit settlement that will soon be doling out $3.175M to ebook purchasers of the last four years, which means Canadian publishers could be giving you back some money! Tim uses this as an opportunity to reflect once more on the publishing industry's digital disruption, and how it is similar to the new digital music industry. This week there's also an extra long, extra good mix of all free music, so listen in to hear some nice tunes too.</description><itunes:subtitle>24 July 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140724-230143-to-20140725-000109.mp3" length="56815127" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140724-230143-to-20140725-000109.mp3</guid></item><item><title>45 - .GIF2</title><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 23:06:29 -0700</pubDate><description>The Copyright Experiment gets out in the wild to check out .GIF2, a gallery event and concert displaying a curated selection of animated GIFs!</description><itunes:subtitle>17 July 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140717-230629-to-20140718-000204.mp3" length="54066680" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140717-230629-to-20140718-000204.mp3</guid></item><item><title>44 - SCOTUS Shoots Down Aereo</title><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 23:02:03 -0700</pubDate><description>Hey, remember that US Supreme Court case we talked about some weeks back between the network television broadcasters and TV web streaming company Aereo? No? Well, that's okay. SCOTUS laid down their decision last week, so we thought it was about time for a revisit. We'll go over why this case is important to copyright on the web, and what the decision could mean for other cloud-based web services. Listen up!</description><itunes:subtitle>3 July 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140703-230203-to-20140704-000310.mp3" length="58313825" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140703-230203-to-20140704-000310.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #43 - YouTube vs. The World of Independent Music</title><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 23:02:43 -0700</pubDate><description>YouTube has been in the spotlight this week after news that they are launching a premium music streaming service, to compete with the likes of Spotify, Rdio, Beats Music, and all the rest!  But with this news comes controversy: Independent labels are claiming that the contract being handed to them is full of unscrupulous terms and undesirable conditions.  What are they? Are labels justified in their vexation? Find all of it out by listening in now!</description><itunes:subtitle>26 June 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140626-230243-to-20140627-000300.mp3" length="57626192" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140626-230243-to-20140627-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #42 - Radio On The Internet (Interview with Freya Zaltz)</title><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 22:58:00 -0700</pubDate><description>NOTE: This episode was pre-recorded. Head over to the blog to hear the best version of this episode: http://copyrightepxeriment.tumblr.com/

This week on The Copyright Experiment, Tim sits down with special guest Freya Zaltz to talk about Re:Sound (a copyright collective), The Copyright Board of Canada, and online web tariffs.  Freya successfully argued to the Copyright Board, on behalf of campus and community radio stations across Canada (such as CiTR!), for a tariff ruling that would be fair for these not-for-profit radio stations. Curios to hear the results? Dive into the episode!</description><itunes:subtitle>19 June 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140619-225800-to-20140620-000200.mp3" length="61982174" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140619-225800-to-20140620-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #41 - Tesla Motors loses its rotors</title><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2014 23:09:30 -0700</pubDate><description>Following in the footsteps of its patent-averse inventor's namesake, Tesla Motors has declared that they will not persue legal action against anyone who uses their patents.  As far as the automobile industry goes, this is certainly an unexpected move. But what exactly does it mean? Why is Tesla doing this? What aren't they mentioning? Tim aka Autonomy discusses all these questions and more, along with drop-in guest Brad aka DJB!</description><itunes:subtitle>12 June 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140612-230930-to-20140613-000815.mp3" length="56033252" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140612-230930-to-20140613-000815.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #40 - UK's groove</title><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 23:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Last week we hopped over the Pacific to learn about China's copyright laws. This week, we're jumping the Atlantic over to the home of western imperialism, the United Kingdom! A recent article in The Guardian on BBC Radio 1's playlisting policies prompted us to give you the low down on the UK's public broadcaster, and draw comparisons to the CBC over here, and also our fair radio station, CiTR.</description><itunes:subtitle>29 May 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140529-230300-to-20140530-000500.mp3" length="60221183" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140529-230300-to-20140530-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #39</title><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 23:01:27 -0700</pubDate><description></description><itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140522-230127-to-20140523-000504.mp3" length="60706571" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140522-230127-to-20140523-000504.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #38 - Net Neutrality Redux</title><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 23:02:41 -0700</pubDate><description>The Internet's afire with concern these days, over the fate of that lofty concept of Net Neutrality. Everyone is talking about it, everyone thinks they know the answer, but does anyone actually know what they are talking about? There's a lot of sensationalism in the media, and buzzwords being tossed around like nickels (we don't have pennies in Canada). We separate the wheat from the chaff and bring the latest analysis in the ongoing fight for Net Neutrality, straight from the typewriter of Tom Wheeler and the FCC.</description><itunes:subtitle>15 May 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140515-230241-to-20140515-235957.mp3" length="54807272" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140515-230241-to-20140515-235957.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #37 - Ephemeral Exhibits</title><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 22:57:52 -0700</pubDate><description>Do you know where your data will be in 20 years? That's what we're asking this week on The Copyright Experiment, in light of the recent recovery of Andy Warhol's Amiga PC paintings. In just 30 years, Warhol's computer data went from easily accessible and reproducible to nearly impossible to access. And it's not just Warhol's computer, it's all digital technology. We take a look at why digital obsolescence occurs, what it means for the future of artistic culture, and how copyright can play an unlikely role in all of this. Dig in!</description><itunes:subtitle>8 May 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140508-225752-to-20140509-000400.mp3" length="63208988" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140508-225752-to-20140509-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #35 - Clouds and Waves</title><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 23:04:34 -0700</pubDate><description>This week on The Copyright Experiment, we discuss a hearing that the US Supreme Court held on Tuesday, between national broadcasters and a tech startup Aereo. Aereo is a service that utilizes thousands of tiny antennae to pull over-the-air, freely available TV signals in local markets and sends them over the Internet to paying subscribers. ABC spearheads this lawsuit, and claims that Aereo should be paying royalties and licensing fees for its service as a content provider, but Aereo says that they are not a content provider, just an equipment provider and should therefore be in the clear. A decision in this case for either side could have far-reaching implications to the future of broadcast television, as well as cloud-based Internet services. We dive into the details and give you the scoop!</description><itunes:subtitle>24 April 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140424-230434-to-20140425-000128.mp3" length="54368171" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140424-230434-to-20140425-000128.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #34 - Canada's Digital Futures</title><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 23:04:30 -0700</pubDate><description>Autonomy flies solo on this episode of the Copyright Experiment, and gives a summary of recent news regarding the future of Canada's digital information infrastructure. 3 key events have happened that do not bode well for the future of Canadian Internet users: The lackluster Digital Canada 150 plan, the deceivingly-named Digital Privacy Act (Bill S-4), and the recent funding cuts to the CBC. Altogether, these 3 acts showcase a government that is ill-informed on the issues surrounding digital information access, and unwilling to pay attention to those who are informed. Listen in to learn the grim details of each event.</description><itunes:subtitle>17 April 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140417-230430-to-20140418-000815.mp3" length="60953852" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140417-230430-to-20140418-000815.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #33 - Robots Make Music, Too</title><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 23:01:23 -0700</pubDate><description>A special guest drops by this week on The Copyright Experiment! The one and only Djb joins Tim to talk AI in the music industry. We tackle everything from remix robots to intelligent music selection. AI IS EVERYWHERE!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>10 April 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140410-230123-to-20140411-000015.mp3" length="56276363" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140410-230123-to-20140411-000015.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #32 - Release Relief</title><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 23:03:43 -0700</pubDate><description>We here at the Copyright Experiment answer a lot of questions, but sometimes it's helpful to pose questions too. On this episode, we pose the question, &quot;What does it mean to release music?&quot;. Sounds straight forward enough, but in today's modern music industry, releases take on forms limited only by imagination. What counts as a release? An LP? An online purchase? A digital download? Ability to stream? We take to the streets and ask typical music consumers to share what they think constitutes a music release, and we hear a couple interesting stories to boot!</description><itunes:subtitle>4 April 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140403-230343-to-20140404-000423.mp3" length="57968966" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140403-230343-to-20140404-000423.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #31 - Shaolin Shadowboxing: TCE vs. Wu-Tang Clan</title><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 23:01:12 -0700</pubDate><description>Ring the match bell, this week we're shadowboxing with the Wu. The recent news that Wu-Tang Clan will be releasing just a single copy of their next album has locked the attention fans and journalists everywhere. The Wu claims to be making music more like fine art, but is it a smart move? We break down the strategy against the backdrop of the modern music world and see if it's more than just a publicity stunt.</description><itunes:subtitle>27 March 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140327-230112-to-20140328-000400.mp3" length="60041039" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140327-230112-to-20140328-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #30 - Copyright: Live and Direct!</title><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 23:01:44 -0700</pubDate><description>This week we're tackling the wild west in the copyright game -- performance rights, public showing royalties, and how mobile technology is changing the ways in which we think about performance. So if you've ever wondered how it's legal for your buddy to throw on Public Enemy at the hip coffee shop, or for your local DJ to play the latest Duke Dumont single at your favourite night club, or even if you're curious about the legality of recording live shows, listen in!</description><itunes:subtitle>20 March 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140320-230144-to-20140321-000126.mp3" length="57070331" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140320-230144-to-20140321-000126.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #29 -  Run DMCA</title><pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 23:07:19 -0700</pubDate><description>Here's some news that's flying under the radar: The US Congress is considering amending the Copyright Act, which has us over at the Copyright Experiment pretty excited. First order of business: The House Judiciary Committee on Courts, Intellectual Property, and the Internet held a hearing to evaluate the effectiveness of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. The DMCA is the last revision to the Copyright Act, and has profoundly shaped the Internet's development in the last 15 years. There has been very little coverage of this debate, so we are doing our own hard-hitting coverage of the hearing. Hear our thoughts on the future of the Internet!</description><itunes:subtitle>13 March 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140313-230719-to-20140314-000329.mp3" length="53687210" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140313-230719-to-20140314-000329.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #28 - Giddy for Getty Images</title><pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 23:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>We're back to our regularly scheduled programming, and this week we're talking about the big news this week: Getty Images, the top stock &amp; editorial photography service, is releasing the majority of its collection for free use online. The service now allows anyone to embed their images into blog posts, tweets, websites, and more. Why the sudden news? What is Getty planning? Is this ultimately good for them? How about users? We tackle all these questions and more, bringing you our expert analysis. Jump in!</description><itunes:subtitle>6 March 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140306-230300-to-20140307-000200.mp3" length="56399795" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140306-230300-to-20140307-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #27 - FUNDRIVE!</title><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 23:03:23 -0800</pubDate><description>It's CiTR's annual fundraiser week, Fundrive! Held in the oldschool telethon format, Fundrive is CiTR's way of raising money for the station. We only ask this of our listeners once a year, so support quality independent radio by donating today! You can support our show by donating online at: http://bit.ly/tcefundrive . No dollar amount is too small! But if you're feeling particularly generous, $100 will get you a special TCE prize: We will come DJ your next party, everything included! Or, if you're not a party type, we will remix a song of your choice in the style of your choice! COOL. Hurry, you only have until March 7!</description><itunes:subtitle>27 February 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140227-230323-to-20140228-000921.mp3" length="63073463" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140227-230323-to-20140228-000921.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #26 - Music Versus... part 4: Books!</title><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 23:23:00 -0800</pubDate><description>We wrap up our multi-part series on copyright in other creative disciplines with the one that started Copyright way back in the 18th Century: Book publishing. We start with a primer on the origins of copyright and book publishing, how the American book publishing industry grew from piracy, how it became the behemoth of an industry it is today, and now more recently, how eBooks and digital distribution are transforming the publishing industry again!</description><itunes:subtitle>20 February 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140220-232300-to-20140221-000644.mp3" length="41796872" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140220-232300-to-20140221-000644.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #25 - Music Versus... part 3: Science!</title><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 23:03:59 -0800</pubDate><description>Part 3 of our multi-part series takes us to how intellectual property is treated in scientific disciplines, particularly chemistry (pharmaceuticals) and biology (biotech). He take a look at the high-stakes business of drug development, weigh the ethical considerations of patenting biotechnology, and more. Plus we also talk discuss Trademark Law, in light of the recent &quot;Dumb Starbucks&quot; controversy that has swept up Twitter.</description><itunes:subtitle>13 February 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140213-230359-to-20140214-000739.mp3" length="60816242" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140213-230359-to-20140214-000739.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #24 - Music Versus... part 2: Film</title><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 23:03:44 -0800</pubDate><description>In Part 2 of our multi-part series on copyright in other disciplines, we tackle the film industry! We draw comparisons between Canadian and American takes on film, how copyright is legislated, how infringement is enforced, and how it's aallll changing, just like music. Cop it!</description><itunes:subtitle>6 February 2014</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140206-230344-to-20140207-000251.mp3" length="56449418" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140206-230344-to-20140207-000251.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #23 - Music Versus... part 1: Software</title><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2014 22:59:56 -0800</pubDate><description>This week we kick off a multi-part series that compares intellectual property rights in music against other intellectual industries and trades. This week, we talk software. Everything from patent law to end user license agreements are covered, and we compare these components to analogous structures in the music industry.  How is a EULA similar to DRM protection? How is the software patent debate similar to the limits of fair use? Find all your answers inside!</description><itunes:subtitle>30 January 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140130-225956-to-20140131-000130.mp3" length="58835492" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140130-225956-to-20140131-000130.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #22 - Goldieblox and The Three Boys</title><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 22:58:52 -0800</pubDate><description>This week on The Copyright Experiment, we discuss a strange recent controversy over the limits of Fair Use and its protection of Parody. Specifically, we chronicle the rise and eventual back down by the producers of a delightfully empowering online video produced by girls toy maker Goldieblox. In the video, we hear little girls singing a parody version of the Beastie Boys' &quot;Girls&quot;, with lyrics meant to inspire young girls to desire more than dolls and pink things. There has been lots of &quot;he-said she-said&quot; talk going on about this, so we get to the bottom of it and play judge and jury on the video's legality.</description><itunes:subtitle>24 January 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140123-225852-to-20140124-000042.mp3" length="59091530" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140123-225852-to-20140124-000042.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #21 - The Indie Musician's Guide To The Modern Music Industry</title><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 23:04:51 -0800</pubDate><description>Are you an aspiring musician? Well, this episode is for you! We give a solid overview of everything you need to know about how the modern music industry works, specifically for the indie musician. A lot has changed over the past 10 years, and to try to jump into things now can be a bit daunting. We go over what you need to know about your intellectual property rights, how to effectively distribute your music to fans, and how to market your music in this fast-moving, ever-changing modern music industry. Jump in!</description><itunes:subtitle>16 January 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140116-230451-to-20140117-001032.mp3" length="62676479" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140116-230451-to-20140117-001032.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #20 - File Sharing: The Hit Maker</title><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 23:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>**NOTE: Last week's &quot;best of 2013&quot; show is available via the blog only, at http://copyrightexperiment.tumblr.com **
On this week's episode of The Copyright Experiment, we discuss a recent academic article by Glynn S. Lunney Jr., who tried to empirically quantify file sharing's impact on the music industry. Specifically Lunney evaluates the possibility that file sharing actually increased the number of hit songs, as predicted by the microeconomic theory of income substitution.</description><itunes:subtitle>10 January 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140109-230200-to-20140110-000641.mp3" length="61843313" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140109-230200-to-20140110-000641.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #18 - Bey Bey's New Cey Dey</title><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 23:03:06 -0800</pubDate><description>It's been pretty hard to ignore this week: Beyonce just dropped her 5th album last Friday, with no notice, exclusively on iTunes, whole album only.  It's a bold move in today's music distribution climate, but the numbers don't lie: This album is huge. But, is this due to the novel release strategy, or are other factors at play here? We give out take on this strategy, including whether it will pay off for Beyonce, and what it means to her music fans.</description><itunes:subtitle>19 December 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131219-230306-to-20131220-000447.mp3" length="58923896" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131219-230306-to-20131220-000447.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #17 - The Value of Music -- Spotify's conundrum</title><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 22:59:48 -0800</pubDate><description>This week on the Copyright Experiment, we discuss a claim by Tim Quark, a music executive at Google Play, that it is impossible to devalue music. What does he mean by this, and do we think he's right? We also take a good hard look at Spotify, which takes a lot of the blame lately for what's been regarded as a devaluing of music. Coincidentally, Spotify has recently released more transparent information in the way it does business, and how money flows in and out of the company's pockets.  We take a good look at this newly public information, and find where the real problems lie.</description><itunes:subtitle>13 December 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131212-225948-to-20131213-000549.mp3" length="63097232" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131212-225948-to-20131213-000549.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #16 - SOCAN I kick it?</title><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 23:01:53 -0800</pubDate><description>YES YA CAN! This week on the Copyright Experiment, we give you the low-down on an organization called SOCAN, the SOCiety of composers, authors, and music publishers of CANada. They are a huge organization that collects licensing fees from over 100,000 business across Canada and distributes the money to its members (artists and labels) in the form of royalties. How does it all work? Does it work? Should it even exist? Is it relevant to an Internet Age? We tackle all these questions in this week's episode!</description><itunes:subtitle>6 December 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131205-230153-to-20131206-000609.mp3" length="61445912" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131205-230153-to-20131206-000609.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE # 15 - The Tee Pee Pee</title><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 23:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This week, we talk about the recently leaked section of the Trans-Pacific Partnership chapter on Intellectual Property.</description><itunes:subtitle>28 November 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131128-230100-to-20131129-001918.mp3" length="74862053" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131128-230100-to-20131129-001918.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #14 - BOOOKS!!!</title><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 23:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>On this episode of The Copyright Experiment, we discuss the recent ruling in the 8-year-long court battle between The Author's Guild and Google over the Google Books program, and its alleged copyright infringement. We also discuss how this relates to copyright infringement court cases in the music industry, and what implications it may mean for the future of digital distribution.</description><itunes:subtitle>21 November 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131121-230200-to-20131122-000310.mp3" length="58476038" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131121-230200-to-20131122-000310.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #13 - Lies, Damn Lies, and Tunes</title><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 22:59:08 -0800</pubDate><description>This week we discuss a controversial article that claims to expose the 13 worst lies about the modern music industry. We tackle them one by one, and give our on thoughts on each issue.</description><itunes:subtitle>14 November 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131114-225908-to-20131115-000131.mp3" length="59617367" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131114-225908-to-20131115-000131.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #12 - Media Democracy Days 2013</title><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 23:02:29 -0800</pubDate><description>In this special episode of The Copyright Experiment, we interview Dr. Kathleen Cross, SFU professor and Chair of the Media Democracy Project. She gives us a great interview that spans modern music distribution, privacy and data collection, technological innovation, and the future of the Internet. If you are interested in any of this, make sure you check out Media Democracy Days 2013, the yearly conference that MDP puts on, happening Nov 8+9 at VPL downtown.</description><itunes:subtitle>7 November 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131107-230229-to-20131108-000506.mp3" length="59864648" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131107-230229-to-20131108-000506.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #11 - A Remix Spooktacular</title><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 23:01:49 -0700</pubDate><description>It's Halloween! Ever notice how Halloween always tends to bring out the themed remixes in dance music? Well we sure did, and decided to talk everything remix on this week's scaaary episode of The Copyright Experiment!</description><itunes:subtitle>31 October 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131031-230149-to-20131101-000107.mp3" length="56687108" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131031-230149-to-20131101-000107.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #10  - With Special Guest The Passenger</title><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 23:04:09 -0700</pubDate><description>This week, we bring in local electronic musician The Passenger to talk about his abundance of free music, what makes vinyl special, and a project he undertook to get people to listen to his music. Then we are treated to a 40 minute DJ set featuring a selection ambient and beat driven Passenger tracks, including a couple soon-to-be-released. Listen in!</description><itunes:subtitle>24 October 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131024-230409-to-20131025-000449.mp3" length="57905165" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131024-230409-to-20131025-000449.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #9 - Just A Sample</title><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 23:05:28 -0700</pubDate><description>This week on The Copyright Experiment, DJ Mochi and Autonomy recount their chance meeting with house music staple Todd Edwards before his show at The Biltmore over the weekend. The discussion invariably leads to his signature style of vocal sampling, and how he deals with copyright. Then we discuss the legality of sampling in general, and how specific court cases have shaped the way people view sampling in modern times. Then, of course, Autonomy steps up to the decks and spins another set full of free tunes, including a few choice Todd Edwards tracks. Check it out!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>17 October 2013</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131017-230528-to-20131018-000500.mp3" length="56908952" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131017-230528-to-20131018-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #8 - Different Strokes for Different Beats</title><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 23:02:37 -0700</pubDate><description>On this episode of The Copyright Experiment, we discuss two recently filed copyright infringement lawsuits that both claim damages/royalties for works that were produced in the 1960s. The first is over the illegal sampling of an old funk song called &quot;Different Strokes&quot;, and the second over who holds the copyright on the screenplay for the film &quot;Raging Bull&quot;. How fair are their claims, given the enormous amount of time that has already passed? Is it fair to artists if these claims are valid? Do they even fall under the scope of Copyright Law? We discuss it all in this week's episode! Plus, as always, we serve a fresh new mix of free tunes to bring you through the rest of the hour.</description><itunes:subtitle>[%DATE]</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131010-230237-to-20131011-000122.mp3" length="56160020" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131010-230237-to-20131011-000122.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #7 - with special guest Vincent Parker</title><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 23:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This week, we bring Vincent Parker into the studio to give his perspective on copyright and the music industry. He also talks about his DIY approach to being a musician, his live performances, and other fun tangents! After the Interview he treats us to a 40-min live set, full of the bright synths, spastic percussion, and deep bass he is known for. Be sure to give it a listen!</description><itunes:subtitle>[%DATE]</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131003-230200-to-20131004-000225.mp3" length="57756713" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131003-230200-to-20131004-000225.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #6 - The Cost of Free</title><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 23:07:08 -0700</pubDate><description>Today's artists give away a lot of music free of monetary cost, but may have other costs associated with them, usually in the form of personal information. Is this trade justified to the consumer? We tackle this question and more in this week's episode.</description><itunes:subtitle>[%DATE]</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130926-230708-to-20130927-000248.mp3" length="53158037" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130926-230708-to-20130927-000248.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #5 - Newforms Festival Wrap-up</title><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 23:04:21 -0700</pubDate><description>First we talked about the new forms festival and some DJ licensing information.

TRACKLIST
Tutsbutta - Ous Chop (Kline's Wonton Soup remix)-Ous Chop-Taylor Kline
Dream Dior - Arrow-Bermuda-Baback Kashani
Vincent Parker - Hypo-Hypo-Vincent Parker
Laura Mvula - She (Shlohmo Remix)-She-Laura Mvula &amp; Henry Laufer
Frank Grimes - Be Your Love-Be Your Love-Frank Grimes
Calamalka - Bad Scene-Bad Scene-Michael Campitelli
Starkey - Fade-Fade EP-PJ Geissinger
Husky - Geeked-Geeked-Husky
Mariah Carey - Touch My Body (Cyril Hahn Remix)-Touch My Body-Cyril Hahn
Ryan Hemsworth - Empty Thoughts Over A Shallow Ocean-Still Awake-Ryan Hemsworth
Sheila D Yeah - Da Shrug-The Kamikaze Comeup-Sheila D Yeah
Azelia Banks - ATM Jam ft. Pharrell (Kaytranada edition)-ATM Jam-Kevin Celestin
Masia One - Warrior's Tongue (ill.Gates Remix)-Warrior's Tongue-Maysian Lim &amp; Dylan Lane
Destiny's Child - Bug A Boo (Ganz Flip)-Bug A Boo-Beyoncé Knowles, Kandi, Kelendria Rowland, Kevin Briggs, LaTavia Roberson, LeToya Luckett, &amp; Ganz</description><itunes:subtitle>(19-Sep-2013)</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130919-230421-to-20130920-000635.mp3" length="59496854" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130919-230421-to-20130920-000635.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #4 - Mixing into the 13th</title><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 23:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This week we provided a little mix, with only a very short talk segment introducing the topic of next week: the real cost of free!

TRACKLIST:
Al'tarba - Petite Maline (Compilation Banzai Labs 5)
Dazastah - The Pump feat. Arnie (The Pump)
J Dilla with Frank N Dank - Anthem (Monolithium Recrunk) (Anthem)
Major Lazer feat. Bruno Mars, 2 Chainz, Tyga &amp; Mystic - Bubble Butt (Neo Fresco Remix) (Bubble Butt)
Kelis - Bossy feat. Too $hort (HxdB &amp; Subcorr Refix) (Bossy)
Zebra Katz - Sex Sellz (Cabo Blanco Booty) (The Grand Opening Compilation)
Karma Kid, Friend Within, Yasmin - Feeling (So Special) (Monki &amp; Friends)
The Passenger - Keep Finding Eachother (Keep Finding Eachother)
Keys N Krates - Dreamyness (Lucid Dreams)
Falcons - Vroom (advance) (Remixes vol. 2)
Nightwave - Night Heat (160 Mix) (Night Heat)
JMJ &amp; Richie - Universal Horn (Mat the Alien Remix) (Universal Horn)
Lea Lea - Black Or White (Goth Trad Remix) (Black Or White)</description><itunes:subtitle>(12-Sep-13)</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130912-230500-to-20130913-000600.mp3" length="58315493" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130912-230500-to-20130913-000600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #3 - Harlem Shakin'</title><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 23:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Harlem Shake Copyright Discussion followed by a mix...

TRACKLIST:
plastic little - miller time (thug paradise 2.1)
hector el father - los terroristas (the bad boy)
baauer - yaow (harlem shake)
abel - girls (baauer remix) (girls ep)
young braised - opacity (f. ammit) (Japanese Tendencies)
iggy azelea - work (dj uniique remix) (work)
beyonce - naughty girl (brenmar and fiinesse remix) (naughty girl)
clicks and whistles - best buy love (best buy love)
dj sega - biggie theme (biggie theme)
ekho - falsetto. (falsetto)
hxdb vs subcorr - no hats land (no hats land)
laura mvula - she (hissy fit remix) (she)
stwo - liz (arnold x lil texas remix) (liz)
amerie - why don't we fall in love (kaytranada version) (kaytranada versions)
dj snake, yellow claw, spanker - slow down (slow down)
outkast - ms. jackson ft kendrick lamar (potatohead people remix) (ms jackson)</description><itunes:subtitle>(05-Sep-2013)</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130905-230500-to-20130906-002500.mp3" length="76463333" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130905-230500-to-20130906-002500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #2 - Creative Commons</title><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 23:02:13 -0700</pubDate><description>In this show, Jeff and Tim discuss Creative Commons - What it is, why it exists, how it works, and if it works. Then we dive in with a 45 minute DJ mix of new free music!</description><itunes:subtitle>(29-Aug-2013)</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130829-230213-to-20130830-000411.mp3" length="59240816" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130829-230213-to-20130830-000411.mp3</guid></item><item><title>TCE #1 - A Brief History of Copyright</title><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 23:05:14 -0700</pubDate><description>Inaugural show! Tim talks about the history of copyright, and how it informs our current discussions of copyright. Followed by a 45 minute DJ mix featuring all free music, including plenty of locals.</description><itunes:subtitle>(22-Aug-2013)</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130822-230514-to-20130823-000425.mp3" length="56576186" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130822-230514-to-20130823-000425.mp3</guid></item></channel></rss>