<?xml version="1.0"  ?>

	<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" ><channel><title>CiTR -- The Jazz Show</title><description>CiTR is proud to present one of the best jazz shows in Vancouver. It has been hosted by notable jazz musician Gavin Walker since 1984. He features Jazz music that is respectful of its tradition and influential to the future. Every 11 o clock an album or an artist is featured and explored in depth. Walker's extensive knowledge and 'hands-on' experience as a jazz player has made this show one of the most listened to in its genre.</description><itunes:summary>CiTR is proud to present one of the best jazz shows in Vancouver. It has been hosted by notable jazz musician Gavin Walker since 1984. He features Jazz music that is respectful of its tradition and influential to the future. Every 11 o clock an album or an artist is featured and explored in depth. Walker's extensive knowledge and 'hands-on' experience as a jazz player has made this show one of the most listened to in its genre.</itunes:summary><itunes:author>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:author><itunes:subtitle>CiTR is proud to present one of the best jazz shows in Vancouver.</itunes:subtitle><itunes:owner> <itunes:name>CiTR 101.9 Vancouver</itunes:name><itunes:email>technicalservices@citr.ca</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="http://www.citr.ca/podcast_photos/jazzshow.jpg"/><itunes:link rel="image" type="video/jpeg" href="http://www.citr.ca/podcast_photos/jazzshow.jpg">CiTR -- The Jazz Show</itunes:link><image><link>http://www.citr.ca</link><url>http://www.citr.ca/podcast_photos/jazzshow.jpg</url><title>CiTR -- The Jazz Show</title></image><link>http://www.citr.ca</link><generator> podcast mate 2000</generator><item><title>Broadcast on 24-Nov-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This is one of the most overlooked albums in the Mingus legacy. It is from a relatively stable period musically and personally in Mingus' volatile life. The band is one of the longest he was able to keep together and lasted from 1956 through the latter part of 1958 with basically the same personnel  except for the revolving door of pianists. Pianist were hard to keep in those days as they were always busy with backing singers of playing lucrative solo gigs. The personnel her is Clarence Shaw on trumpet, Shafi Hadi on alto and tenor saxophones, Jimmy Knepper on trombone and of course Dannie Richmond on drums. A last minute cancellation by Mingus' semi-regular pianist caused Mr. Mingus to call the then up and coming Bill Evans to play piano and he came in and sight-read the parts and  nailed every tune. Bill is really the co-star on this date. Only one non-Mingus tune is featured and that is the beautiful Eubie Blake/Andy Razaf tune called &quot;Memories of You&quot; the rest of the six tunes are by Mingus. This is an album that should not be overloo0ked and is an important piece of Minugs' musical history. &quot;East Coasting&quot; is a wonderful musical experience.</description><itunes:subtitle>Bassist and composer Charles Mingus: &quot;East Coasting&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141124-210100-to-20141125-004600.mp3" length="214866884" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141124-210100-to-20141125-004600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 17-Nov-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This great band played only in the Los Angeles area yet it gained international fame because vibist/leader Terry Gibbs was astute enough to record the band's infrequent gigs and record them well with the genius engineer Wally Heider. The band consisted of the cream of the crop of Jazz playing Hollywood musicians. These were men who loved playing Jazz but also made a great living doing studio/movie/TV work. Players like alto saxophonists Joe Maini and Charlie Kennedy and tenorists Richie Kamuca and Bill Perkins. Trumpeters Al Porcino in the lead and soloists Conte Candoli and Stu Williamson. Trombone masters, Frank Rosolino and Vern Friley and the great Mel Lewis on drums to name just a few. Terry Gibbs is the perfect bandleader...outgoing and ebullient. Gibbs on vibes is the real link between Lionel Hampton and Milt Jackson and his fine solos are heard throughout the set. The band's arrangers are Shorty Rogers, Al Cohn, Manny Albam and Bill Holman. &quot;Main Stem&quot; is the name of the album and the band is the one and only Terry Gibbs Dream Band recorded at &quot;The Summit&quot; in January of 1961. Terry just celebrated his 90th birthday on October 13, 2014!</description><itunes:subtitle>Vibist and bandleader Terry Gibbs: &quot;The Terry Gibbs Dream Band- Main Stem&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141117-210100-to-20141118-000400.mp3" length="174761492" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141117-210100-to-20141118-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 10-Nov-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This album is one of the most iconic Blue Note releases in that it represents four young men who are advancing the Jazz Tradition by not abandoning that tradition. Most prominent is the leader, Hammond organist Larry Young who is taking the instrument beyond blues and greasy funk and into other musical realms.The two horns are representative of modern thinking and both are innovators and important stylists, trumpeter Woody Shaw and on tenor saxophone, Joe Henderson.These two blend so well and seem to breathe together. On drums is the always powerful yet tasteful Elvin Jones who works so well with Larry Young's bass lines. Three great Woody Shaw tunes are featured plus a swinging blues by Henderson and a great standard, &quot;Softly As In A Morning Sunrise&quot;. One bonus is the duo track with Young and Jones doing Thelonious Monk's &quot;Monk's Dream&quot;. A classic and innovative date unlike any other session that featured the Hammond organ.&quot;Unity&quot; is an important milestone.</description><itunes:subtitle>Organ innovator Larry Young with Woody Shaw,Joe Henderson and Elvin Jones: &quot;Unity&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141110-210300-to-20141111-000400.mp3" length="172983404" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141110-210300-to-20141111-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 03-Nov-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Richard Williams (1931-1985) was an incredible trumpeter and a powerful voice in his chosen horn. Richard recorded with John Handy, Booker Ervin, Yusef Lateef, Oliver Nelson and was a member of the hottest Jazz cauldron of the time: The Charles Mingus Jazz Workshop. He played in numerous big bands, symphony orchestras and Broadway pit bands and did studio work but he only made one album under his name and it's tonight's Jazz Feature. It was done in November of 1960 and called &quot;New Horn In Town&quot;. It features Richard with alto saxophonist/flutist Leo Wright (who didn't record enough for me taste), pianist Richard Wyands, bassist Reginald Workman and a young drummer who had played with Wes Montgomery and his brothers named Bobby Thomas. The album is well planned and well-rehearsed and contains two fine old standards plus Benny Golson's &quot;I Remember Clifford&quot;.  Richard Wyands contributes one composition to the set and Richard Williams does three. Although this album is hardly ground breaking or revolutionary it is fine solid Modern Jazz. The album is well paced and the band is tight. &quot;New Horn In Town&quot; is well worth hearing so check it out!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trumpeter Richard Williams: &quot;New Horn In Town&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141103-210200-to-20141104-000400.mp3" length="173941670" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141103-210200-to-20141104-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 27-Oct-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>William &quot;Sonny&quot; Criss had a career that seemed to go in fits and starts. Sonny emerged early on the 1940's L.A. Jazz scene with his full-bodied sound and passionate approach and played  with all the important players then went on to play with Norman Granz' Jazz At The Philharmonic travelling jam session and shared the stage with Charlie Parker, Fats Navarro, Hank Jones, Shelley Manne and others. He made his first recordings under his name for Granz in 1950. His career was stifled by changing styles in L.A. and Criss was brushed aside by the West Coast Jazz cool players. Sonny was a hot, passionate player with a sweeping sound all his own. We turn to one of his 3 albums he made for the small Imperial label in 1956. The title tells it all &quot;Sonny Criss Plays Cole Porter&quot;. Ten great Porter songs played with beauty and originality with Sonny's alto in the lead and backed by Larry Bunker on vibes, Sonny Clark on piano, Buddy Clark (no relation) on bass, and Lawrence (aka Larence) Marable on drums. Criss was born in Memphis on October 23, 1927 and died by his own hand in Los Angeles on on Nov. 19,1977 at age 50 after a diagnosis of terminal cancer of the stomach. A great voice was lost and Sonny still seems under appreciated and we hope tonight's Jazz Feature rectifies this a bit. Sonny was a great player and always delivered!</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto Saxophone Master Sonny Criss: &quot;Plays Cole Porter&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141027-210200-to-20141028-000100.mp3" length="171113576" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141027-210200-to-20141028-000100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 20-Oct-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This five movement creation by composer extraordinaire George Russell is his tribute to New York City. It was written and recorded in late 1958 and 1959 and played by an all-star orchestra with many many great Jazz stars as soloists. People such as John Coltrane, Benny Golson, Bob Brookmeyer, Phil Woods, Art Farmer, Bill Evans, Max Roach are all heard extensively. Mr, Russell incorporates several &quot;standard&quot; tunes into his composition here and you'll hear references to &quot;Manhattan&quot;, &quot;Autumn In New York&quot;, &quot;How About You&quot; and other melodies but it's all George Russell. This historic record is a tribute to one of the greatest cities in the world. Each movement is introduced by poet/writer Jon Hendricks and provides a wonderful set-up to the music. New York, New York....a town so nice, they named it twice!</description><itunes:subtitle>Composer George Russell: &quot;New York, New York&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141020-210200-to-20141021-000400.mp3" length="173942504" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141020-210200-to-20141021-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 13-Oct-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is an historic record date with Thelonious Monk joining Art Blakey's 1957 edition of The Jazz Messengers. Monk had one important request when he agreed to do this date and that was it must include mostly Monk tunes. Monk and Blakey were best of friends and their Birthdays were one day apart Oct.10(Monk) and Oct 11(Blakey) so it was a fun date for all concerned. Blakey's Messengers included Cleveland-born trumpeter Bill Hardman and Chicago-born Johnny Griffin (&quot;The Little Giant&quot;), bassist James &quot;Spanky&quot; DeBrest and Blakey on drums and Monk on piano. All the tunes are Monk's except for the last tune which was written by Johnny Griffin and called &quot;Purple Shades&quot;. This is an iconic and classic album which is our way of saying Happy Birthday to two men who shaped Jazz music forever.</description><itunes:subtitle>Thelonious Monk with Art Blakey's Jazz Messengers (1957).</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141013-210100-to-20141014-000000.mp3" length="171115244" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141013-210100-to-20141014-000000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 06-Oct-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Elvin Jones was one of the most compelling and inventive drummers in the history of Jazz. In 1965 he left the John Coltrane &quot;Classic Quartet&quot; and struck out on his own leading his bands that he dubbed &quot;The Elvin Jones Jazz Machine&quot;. These were groups of various sizes that he led until his passing in May of 2004.This was one of his first records post-Coltrane and Elvin put together a fine band for this Atlantic date done in March of 1966.Elvin's older brother is here on cornet and it's the magnificent Thad Jones. Hank Mobley is on tenor saxophone and he lives up to his name as &quot;the welterweight champion of the tenor saxophone&quot;. On piano is the South African guru of Jazz, Dollar Brand aka Abdullah Ibrahim. This is an early recording by Dollar as he had just moved to New York from Europe via South Africa. On bass is the lesser known but strong Don Moore, On one tune Elvin and Thad's cousin takes over the piano chores on electric piano and his name is Steven James. A varied program of originals by Brand, Mobley, Thad Jones and Elvin and electric pianist Steven James make up this fine and often overlooked record. Midnight Walk is a fine documentation of the beginning of Elvin Jones' career as a bandleader.</description><itunes:subtitle>Drummer Elvin Jones: &quot;Midnight Walk&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141006-210200-to-20141007-000200.mp3" length="172030976" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20141006-210200-to-20141007-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 29-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Phillip Wells Woods is still to this day one of the foremost exponents of the alto saxophone and a Jazz Master. Woods was born in Springfield Mass. on November 2,1931 and moved to New York to attend The Julliard School of Music in 1948. By 1954 he had began recording for Prestige/New Jazz under his own name and he also made sideman appearances but tonight's Jazz Feature recording made in November of 1955 put Phil Woods in the front rank of alto saxophonists. The album is a quartet date with Woods as the only horn. He is accompanied by the unsung John Williams on piano who had just left the Stan Getz group. Teddy Kotick is a tower of strength on bass and Phil's long standing running buddy Nick Stablulas on drums. The program is a mix of lesser known standards (4) and Woods' originals (2). Woods has recorded literally hundreds of dates since then as a leader and sideman but tonight's Jazz Feature is a true classic and one that Woods' is still proud of......and rightly so!</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Phil Woods: &quot;Woodlore&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140929-210200-to-20140930-000300.mp3" length="172983821" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140929-210200-to-20140930-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 22-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>William &quot;Red&quot; Garland was one of the finest and most distinctive pianists of his generation. He rose to fame  with Miles Davis from 1955 through 1958 with a few short layoffs. Garland through being employed by Davis got a recording contract with Prestige Records and made a whole series of good selling trio albums that established his sound away from Davis. Garland was also a frequent sideman on many dates with John Coltrane, Jackie McLean, Phil Woods and others. Red went on his own after his tenure with Davis and worked mostly trio gigs and recorded for Prestige and later Riverside records. Tonight's Jazz Feature is an album called &quot;Red Garland At The Prelude&quot; which was recorded at a small high-end club in Harlem where people actually listened! Garland chose two Philadelphia musicians to accompany him: fine bassist Jimmy Rowser and an unsung great on drums, Charles &quot;Specs&quot; Wright. The set consists of some great standards and blues performed by one of the all time great pianists, Red Garland!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist Red Garland: &quot;Red Garland At The Prelude&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140922-210300-to-20140923-000200.mp3" length="171068957" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140922-210300-to-20140923-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 15-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Leonard Bernstein was a musician, composer, conductor and a world ambassador for quality music and understood Jazz music. He understood it's inner workings and respected Jazz players as much as his fellow classical players. In this recording that was done in 1956, Bernstein explains what Jazz is and what it isn't. He plays examples himself and uses many great players such as Duke Ellington, Louis Armstrong, Bessie Smith, Miles Davis and many many others.Bernstein explains many of the technical terms of Jazz and music in simple layman-like terms. This was his forte. Maestro Bernstein is educational and entertaining, There is too the odd unintentional humerous moment when Bernstein states something that is of the time because don't forget, this recording was done in 1956. It is of course still a very relevant document and hopefully will enlighten you to some of the mysteries of Jazz and music in general.This is Part 2 of our &quot;back to school&quot; series in The Jazz Show. Leonard Bernstein and &quot;What Is Jazz&quot;.</description><itunes:subtitle>Maestro Leonard Bernstein narrates &quot;What Is Jazz&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140915-210200-to-20140916-000200.mp3" length="172026389" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140915-210200-to-20140916-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 08-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This capsule history of Jazz with recorded examples is narrated by the erudite and lucid alto saxophone master Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley. It was recorded in 1960 but is still entertaining and relevant as a historical document.It is Part 1 of our &quot;back to school&quot; idea that we do on The Jazz Show every September. Mr Adderley was well qualified to do a recording like this as he was not only a good speaker but was a former high school teacher before he became famous as a master saxophonist and bandleader. Sit back and enjoy this recording even if you heard it before as it is always worth revisiting. Next week will be another historic educational recording with Maestro Leonard Bernstein called &quot;What Is Jazz&quot;.</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley narrates &quot;A History of Jazz&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140908-210200-to-20140909-000200.mp3" length="172002203" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140908-210200-to-20140909-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 01-Sep-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Master tenor saxophonist Stan Getz in one of his great artistic and innovative triumphs. Seven compositions for strings were written by the great Eddie Sauter and Mr. Getz improvises over them. Seems simple doesn't it? However when you combine the genius of Getz with the fine craftsmanship of Mr.Sauter then you have an unbeatable combination. This album has entered the realm of &quot;Jazz classics&quot; and is an essential item in anyone's collection and a complete triumph for Getz and Sauter. It was recorded in 1961 and remains fresh to this day. Focus is a masterpiece and tonight's Jazz Feature!</description><itunes:subtitle>Stan Getz and Eddie Sauter: &quot;Focus&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140901-210100-to-20140902-000200.mp3" length="172982570" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140901-210100-to-20140902-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 25-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is a rather rare Prestige album recorded in January of 1966. Bobby Timmons was a very distinctive pianist who had many sides, one being that he could generate a lot of heat and exciteement with some very bluesy gospel flavoured playing but he also could be just as distinctive playing in a more straight ahead Bud Powell oriented style and yet preserving his identity. It's the latter style and mood that Bobby chooses to explore on this set. He hand-picked the band with Ron Carter on bass and Jimmy Cobb on drums and the great Wayne Shorter as the sole horn. Carter contributed three tunes to the set and Shorter wrote one...an affectionate tribute to Bobby Timmons called &quot;Tom Thumb&quot;. Timmons wrote two originals for the date as well. This is not an innovative or revolutionary date but good solid Modern Jazz played with soul and swing....check out &quot;The Soul Man&quot;.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Bobby Timmons with Wayne Shorter:&quot;The Soul Man&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140825-210200-to-20140826-000100.mp3" length="171068123" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140825-210200-to-20140826-000100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 18-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This was the first album under his name of composer/arranger/tenor saxophonist Bill Holman. He first got recognition as a saxophonist and arranger/composer for Stan Kenton then went on to occasionally form his own big band for a few dates and a possible recording session. By dint of his residence in Los Angeles, Holman was able to recruit many of the finest studio/Jazz players in L.A.This he did on this his debut record. &quot;The Fabulous Bill Holman&quot; lives up to it's name and marks it as a classic of big-band Jazz and sets a very high standard for others to follow. The playing of all involved is superb both in ensemble work and solos. You will hear over the six selections, solos by Charlie Mariano and Herb Geller on altos,Holman and Richie Kamuca on tenors, Conte Candoli and Stu Williamson on trumpets and others plus a great rhythm section of Lou Levy on piano, Max Bennett on bass and the great Mel Lewis on drums. All in all great writing by Holman covering four of his own tunes and one by Sonny Rollins...Airegin and a great Harold Arlen, Johnny Mercer standard called Come Rain or Come Shine. It was all recorded in April of 1957 and remains one of the finest examples of big-band Jazz!</description><itunes:subtitle>Composer/arranger Bill Holman: &quot;The Fabulous Bill Holman&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140818-210200-to-20140819-000000.mp3" length="170111108" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140818-210200-to-20140819-000000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 11-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This album was the first domestically released album by Miles Davis' &quot;Second Great Quintet&quot; which included tenor saxophonist/composer Wayne Shorter, pianist Herbie Hancock, bassist Ron Carter and drummer Tony Williams. This album indicated a new change for Miles Davis in that a lot of his old standard repertoire was being replaced by compositions by himself and the band including works by Shorter, Hancock, and Carter. This album represents that change and it was recorded over a three day period in Los Angeles in January of 1965. It is a milestone album not only because of the new repertoire but of the inspired and fresh playing of the group. Seven new compositions are featured by everyone in the band save for Williams and it represents a step forward by one of Jazz music's great innovators....Miles Dewey Davis.</description><itunes:subtitle>Miles Davis and &quot;The Second Great Quintet&quot;: &quot;E.S.P.&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140811-210200-to-20140812-000200.mp3" length="172027223" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140811-210200-to-20140812-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 04-Aug-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This marvelous album is tonight's Jazz Feature and as it is the first night of The Jazz Show's new policy, The Jazz Feature will be heard right after our theme and initial intro....right after 9pm instead of the old time of after 11pm.The Jazz feature is Montreal based Christine Jensen and her Jazz Orchestra. This album called &quot;Habitat&quot; won the 2014 Juno Award for Best Large Jazz Ensemble. The band consists of the cream of the crop of Montreal based players and is a very large group of over 20 pieces. Christine's compositions reflect her studies and influences of Maria Schneider, Gil Evans and Bob Brookmeyer. The music is six compositions that can be listened to as a continuous suite or as individual moods. All in all a deep and wonderful sonic pleasure.</description><itunes:subtitle>Composer/bandleader Christine Jensen: The Christine Jensen Jazz Orchestra: &quot;Habitat&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140804-210200-to-20140805-001400.mp3" length="183062294" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140804-210200-to-20140805-001400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 28-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2014 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This album which is one of Lee Morgan's finest ironically was recorded in 1964 and never released until 1981 when the Blue Note vaults were researched.It was more than a pleasant surprise when it was finally put out. Lee Morgan had made an astonishing comeback with his recording &quot;The Sidewinder&quot; and had overcome his personal problems to emerge a greater more mature musician. He was still only 26 years old! He assembled a great band here with alto saxophonist Jackie McLean, trombone master Curtis Fuller, pianist McCoy Tyner, bassist Bob Cranshaw and as a special favour, Art Blakey on drums. Blakey had stopped doing sideman dates in 1962 but appeared here as a special favor to his favourite trumpeter...Lee Morgan. Morgan wrote four out of the five tunes and McCoy Tyner penned the ballad feature called &quot;Twilight Mist&quot;, Morgan's compositions are among his best and they display another side to his immense talent. &quot;Tom Cat&quot; is the name of the album and is the appealing title track. Lee Morgan indeed!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trumpeter/composer Lee Morgan: &quot;Tom Cat&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140728-210100-to-20140729-000300.mp3" length="173950844" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140728-210100-to-20140729-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 21-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This album is a creative step-up for pianist McCoy Tyner who had signed with Blue Note Records after his tenure with John Coltrane. McCoy chose an all-star group for this date that took place in 1968.Woody Shaw is on trumpet, Gary Bartz on alto saxophone and the great Wayne Shorter is on tenor saxophone. Ron Carter who is best known as a bassist plays his first instrument here: the cello. He is heard enhancing the ensemble. Herbie Lewis is on bass and the late Freddie Waits is on drums. Mr Tyner is on piano and the album features four of his ground breaking compositions plus his arrangement of one by the under-rated Cal Massey. This album represents an important creative step for Tyner and one that he is rightly proud of. It is a favourite and may become yours too!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer McCoy Tyner: &quot;Expansions&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140721-210100-to-20140722-000300.mp3" length="173646017" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140721-210100-to-20140722-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 14-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Stan Kenton's Orchestra over the years covered just about every style of music imaginable. From simple dance music to the most complex semi-classical scores. This album called &quot;Contemporary Concepts&quot; is Kenton at his most swinging. It is serious Jazz and features a range of exciting soloists like alto saxophonists Lennie Niehaus and Charlie Mariano, to tenor saxophonist Bill Perkins, trombonists Carl Fontana and Kent Larsen to trumpeters Sam Noto and Stu Williamson and others. Stan's rhythm section couldn't help but swing hard....Ralph Blaze on guitar. Max Bennett on bass and Mel Lewis on drums plus the maestro Stan Kenton on piano. Bill Holman wrote the arrangements of six standards and turned each of them into mini symphonies. The seventh tune is the exciting Gerry Mulligan original based on &quot;I've Got Rhythm&quot; that he called &quot;Limelight&quot;. This album is a favourite among Kenton fans and non-fans too. &quot;Contemporaty Concepts&quot; is a classic.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Stan Kenton Orchestra: &quot;Contemporary Concepts&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140714-210400-to-20140715-000000.mp3" length="168194576" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140714-210400-to-20140715-000000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 07-Jul-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This date was recorded live at a small club in Watts called the Black Orchid on August 15,1961. It is a recording of a one-night stand by the great voice of the tenor saxophone: Gene Ammons..... backed by the the club's house band led by organ master Richard &quot;Groove&quot; Holmes with guitarist Gene Edwards and drummer Leroy Henderson. These small neighborhood clubs dotted the Afican-American inner-cities back in the day and they mostly featured Jazz music and the Hammond organ trios were predominant in these places. Gene Ammons was a favorite of most African-American Jazz fans and the crowd here eats up his every, riff and note. These audiences were favored by Jazz players from the most cerebral to the most earthy and the folks in the chairs missed nothing! &quot;Groovin' With Jug&quot; is a great look back when Jazz was an important part of Inner-City life. Enjoy the great sounds.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone giant Gene Ammons with organist Richard &quot;Groove&quot; Holmes and his Trio.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140707-210100-to-20140707-235900.mp3" length="170204516" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140707-210100-to-20140707-235900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 30-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This legendary date by a legendary pianist/composer is considered by many to be his masterpiece. Elmo Hope was a friend and contemporary of Bud Powell and Thelonious Monk and grew up with them. Hope's career was spotty and his recordings few and his life was blighted by drug addiction and ill health but his musical legacy is firm. During his four years in Los Angeles from 1956 to 1959 he had a few triumphs and this Jazz Feature recording was one of them. Mr Hope is accompanied by bassist Jimmy Bond and the great Frank Butler on drums. Of the eight tunes, seven are Hope compositions and one favored standard is played...a ballad version of &quot;Like Someone in Love&quot;. &quot;The Elmo Hope Trio&quot; is one of the highlights on Hope's often erratic career and enhances his deep musical legacy.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Elmo Hope: &quot;The Elmo Hope Trio&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140630-210000-to-20140701-002700.mp3" length="197812418" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140630-210000-to-20140701-002700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 23-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Dexter Gordon was a pioneer of Modern Jazz and influenced a whole school of saxophone players including John Coltrane and Sonny Rollins. This live set recorded in Copenhagen at that city's most famous Jazz club The Montmartre during Gordon's happy and  productive European sojourn. Dexter is accompanied by the finest rhythm section  in Europe with two American  ex-pats: pianist  Kenny Drew and  drummer Albert Heath plus the young Danish  genius  of the bass  Nils Henning Orsted-Pederson (NHOP. Dexter delivers the goods on this date done in 1967.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone master Dexter Gordon;&quot;Live in  Copenhagen'</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140623-210000-to-20140623-235959.mp3" length="172389596" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140623-210000-to-20140623-235959.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 16-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A most unique ensemble...a real &quot;living room band&quot;. The Jimmy Giuffre 3. Mr Giuffre on clarinet and tenor and baritone saxophones, Bob Brookmeyer on valve trombone and Jim Hall on guitar. This unit only made one recording and this is it. Giuffre was a wonderful musician/composer/arranger who explored every type of music from straight-ahead Jazz to the outer reaches of the avant-guard and free-form music. He wrote for large and small ensembles. This band explores Giuffre's &quot;folk/pastoral/blues&quot; stage and the music this little group makes is complete in itself. Four Giuffre compositions are featured
plus some unlikely &quot;standards&quot;. The title track is perhaps the closest tune to a pop standard and it was written by Johnny Mercer. The other tunes are a couple of campfire tunes....&quot;Show Me The Way to Go Home&quot; and &quot;California, Here I Come&quot;. This is a lovely band and the music could only be played by people deep into the Jazz language. &quot;Trav'lin' Light with the Jimmy Giuffre 3 is a refreshing experience.</description><itunes:subtitle>Multi-instrumentalist Jimmy Giuffre and his 3: (with Jim Hall and Bob Brookmeyer):&quot;Trav'lin' Light&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140616-210500-to-20140617-002600.mp3" length="191697530" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140616-210500-to-20140617-002600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 09-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>One of the finest recordings by one of the most popular and critically overlooked tenor saxophonists in Jazz: Illinois Jacquet. Often dismissed as a screamer and a showboater, Jacquet remains a misunderstood major voice of the tenor saxophone. The truth is Mr. Jacquet was an outgoing player and was always out to please his audience but was always musical and harmonically sophisticated. Possessing a huge, deep and sensuous tone, he could turn up the excitement meter but could also move you to tears with a heartfelt ballad. He had one foot in the swing era and one foot in Modern Jazz. It is this transitional concept that's evident on tonight's Jazz Feature. &quot;Swing's The Thing!&quot; puts Jacquet in the company of his peers including Roy Eldridge (&quot;Little Jazz&quot;), Herb Ellis on guitar, Jimmy Jones on piano, Ray brown on bass and Jo (&quot;Papa Jo&quot;)Jones on drums. Six fine tunes plays with soul and taste by all and one of the finest albums by this great tenor saxophonist. &quot;Swing's The Thing&quot; Indeed Mr. Jacquet.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone master Illinois Jacquet: &quot;Swing's The Thing!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140609-210400-to-20140610-003700.mp3" length="203045351" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140609-210400-to-20140610-003700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 02-Jun-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The whole show tonight is dedicated to the 2014 edition of the T.D. Vancouver International Jazz Festival. Guest host and one of the founding fathers of the Jazz Festival is John Orysik, the festival's Media Director. John will discuss the festival and pick the music to be heard while Gavin Walker will be here to interject a few words as well. The Jazz Show's annual tribute to Vancouver's most recognised and popular cultural event. Check out this show!</description><itunes:subtitle>A Very Special Edition of The Jazz Show dedicated to the TD International Jazz Festival with Gavin Walker and Jazz Festival Media Director John Orysik.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140602-210300-to-20140603-000400.mp3" length="172525538" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140602-210300-to-20140603-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 26-May-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Andrew Hill was a unique and wonderful composer/pianist. Andrew attracted the ear of Blue Note head honcho, Alfred Lion when Hill moved to New York in 1963. Hill appeared as a sideman on Hank Mobley's classic &quot;No Room For Squares&quot; date and Mr. Lion immediately signed Andrew to a contract and produced Andrew's first album for Blue Note the now classic &quot;Black Fire&quot;. Hill made many records for the label but many were not released as Lion didn't wish to flood the small market. Hill's music is sometimes difficult, quirky and not in the mainstream...in other words, an acquired taste. However when you &quot;get&quot; Andrew's music....one will never forget it! This date was discovered in the vaults of Blue Note and at first deemed unreleaseable but soon after a second listening, Mr. Hill okayed it's release. It became one of the most discussed albums of 2003 and praised by all quarters...fans and critics. The band consists of trumpeters Woody Shaw and Dizzy Reece. Trombonist Julian Priester and French horn virtuoso, Robert Northern plus Howard Johnson on tuba and bass clarinet.The single reed performer is the great Joe Farrell who is heard on tenor and soprano saxophone, alto flute, bass clarinet and English horn. The bassist is Ron Carter and the drummer is the young Lenny White. All the compositions are by Andrew Hill and the date was done in November 1969. Profound and moving music.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Andrew Hill: &quot;Passing Ships&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140526-210300-to-20140527-003000.mp3" length="198379538" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140526-210300-to-20140527-003000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 19-May-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Guitarist Grant Green seemed to suddenly appear on the national Jazz scene from out of nowhere appearing on Blue Note Records as a leader and as a sideman in the early 60s. He had honed his skills in his hometown of St. Louis MO and was asked to come to New York by alto saxophone master Lou Donaldson who recommended him to Blue Note's honcho Alfred Lion. Green became a favourite and recorded frequently in the years 1961-65 and those recordings contain his most lasting work. Many of Green's sessions were never issued until after his death in 1979. This one that we're featuring tonight was one of those.It's a very high level session with Mr. Green in the company of two members of John Coltrane's &quot;classic quartet&quot; in the persons of pianist McCoy Tyner and drummer Elvin Jones. The bassist is the ubiquitous Bob Cranshaw. With this powerful rhythm section Green is at his best. Two Green originals (including the title track) are heard plus a delightful version of &quot;My Favourite Things&quot; with the Coltrane arrangement. Pianist Duke Pearson's exotic original called &quot;Bedouin&quot; is heard. Completing the set is the Bacharach/David tune called &quot;Wives and Lovers&quot; done in &quot;sprung waltz&quot; style. Mr. Green was one of the giants of the guitar and this date proves it!</description><itunes:subtitle>Guitar great Grant Geen: &quot;Matador&quot; with McCoy Tyner, Bob Cranshaw and Elvin Jones.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140519-210200-to-20140520-002500.mp3" length="194011880" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140519-210200-to-20140520-002500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 12-May-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Miles Davis and his band which he called &quot;Directions&quot; was at this time playing music alongside some of the great rock stars of the day. Davis' music had changed and he was using electric instruments and some rock elements as well and had dropped the standards and tunes like &quot;Walkin'&quot; and &quot;So What&quot; from his repertoire. The music here is an extension of the concepts found on &quot;Bitches Brew&quot; (his best selling album). The band includes Mr. Davis on trumpet(open and unenhanced by electronics), Steve Grossman on soprano and tenor saxophone, Keith Jarrett on electric organ, Chick Corea on electic piano,Dave Holland on electric bass, Jack DeJohnette on drums and Airto Moreira on percussion, flute and voice. The music is intense and powerful and although this music has been issued before this new reissue removes the edits and we get the full evening's performance. Hence the full evening of music as performed at Fillmore East in New York on June 19,1970. A powerhouse band!</description><itunes:subtitle>Miles Davis At Fillmore-Friday June 19,1970.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140512-210200-to-20140513-003400.mp3" length="202615007" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140512-210200-to-20140513-003400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 05-May-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Bob Belden wrote this music for a 69 piece orchestra to portray the life of Elizabeth Short aka &quot;The Black Dahlia&quot;. Her full story is on the web but the music can stand on it's own. Moody, introspective and sometimes dream, exotic and exciting. This huge project features work by trumpeters Tim Hagans and Lew Soloff, saxophonists Lawrence Feldman, Mike Migliore, Joe Lovano and Bob Belden and trombonist Conrad Herwig and contributions by several pianists, Kevin Hays, Marc Copeland and many more. A great piece of orchestral mood music at it's best tracing this story. A masterpiece of orchestration and writing. Kudos to Bob Belden!</description><itunes:subtitle>Bob Belden: &quot;Black Dahlia&quot; (A Suite in 12 Movements).</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140505-210400-to-20140506-003000.mp3" length="197325779" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140505-210400-to-20140506-003000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 28-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This album recorded in August of 1957 is an important milestone in the recorded legacy of John Coltrane. By the time of this recording he had broken his drug habit and kept a heavy practice schedule plus he had joined one of the most important and ground breaking bands in Jazz music....the Thelonious Monk Quartet.With this date even the critics who had been very harsh to Coltrane (with the exception of Ira Gitler) were coming around to recognise Mr. Coltrane as one of the important new voices on the tenor saxophone. Coltrane is heard here with The Red Garland Trio, a band that he made many of his Prestige recordings with. Garland is a wonderful lyrical contrast to Coltrane's intensity. Paul Chambers is the anchor and drive and Arthur Taylor's drums kick butt in the best possible way. Two great blues are featured, the title track (Tranein' In) and Bass Blues and a mood piece written by Alonzo Levister called &quot;Slow Dance&quot; and the beautiful standard &quot;You Leave Me Breathless&quot; and the barn burning up tempo version of Irving Berlin's &quot;Soft Lights and Sweet Music&quot;. This album was a giant step by a Jazz giant.</description><itunes:subtitle>&quot;John Coltrane With The Red Garland Trio-Tranein' In&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140428-210200-to-20140429-000200.mp3" length="172029308" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140428-210200-to-20140429-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 21-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Today (April 21) is the 82nd Birthday of one of the world's great Jazz trombonists and an incredible composer/arranger Lockesly Wellington Hampton....better known as &quot;Slide&quot;. He became a competent trombonist when he was young and soon graduated to playing with known bands led by Lionel Hampton (no relation) and Maynard Ferguson. He also wrote arrangements and compositions for those bands and others and developed that skill until it was as important as his playing. He formed The Slide Hampton Octet in 1960 and began touring both the USA and Europe with that band as well as recording for several major labels. The Slide Hampton Octet was sometimes increased to a tentet or 11 pieces. Tonights' Jazz Feature is the Octet with 9 pieces! Alumnus, Freddie Hubbard (trumpet)is back on this date and guests,Yusef Lateef on tenor saxophone and flute is a worthy addition but the star is the guest appearance of Max Roach. Roach's drums light a fire under the band and made this recording a very special one. Regulars George Coleman on tenor saxophone and Richard Williams on trumpet are heard plus some solos by Slide himself and Tommy Flanagan on piano. The tunes are a mix of Hampton originals and Hampton re-interpretation of some good standards. The centerpiece is really dedicated to Mr. Roach and is called &quot;Drum Suite&quot;. Happy Birthday Slide Hampton!  The album &quot;Drum Suite&quot; is a classic!</description><itunes:subtitle>The Slide Hampton Octet with guests Max Roach, Freddie Hubbard and Max Roach:&quot;Drum Suite&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140421-210200-to-20140422-000100.mp3" length="171061868" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140421-210200-to-20140422-000100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 14-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This Jazz Feature is a short concert performed in Sweden at the Ahus Jazz Festival in July of 1973 with the great tenor saxophonist playing with pick-up rhythm section of US ex-pats.The people involved with Mr. Ammons are Horace Parlan on piano, Red Mitchell on bass and a fairly unknown drummer named Ed Jones. They provide Gene Ammons with the right backing and although he had about a year to live (he died at age 49 of bone cancer)one would never suspect he was gravely ill. The tunes are all familiar to the band and there was obviously no rehearsal but it wouldn't matter with musicians of this calibre. This is a rare recording and gives one to hear one of the all-time greats on the tenor saxophone....Happy Birthday Gene &quot;Jug&quot; Ammons. Ammons was born in Chicago on April 14, 1925.Dig Jug!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone giant Gene Ammons: &quot;Gene Ammons In Sweden&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140414-210300-to-20140415-000300.mp3" length="172065587" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140414-210300-to-20140415-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 07-Apr-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The recordings are considered some of the finest of Billie Holiday's long career. They are three recording dates done for a small independent label called Commodore Records run by a musically sensitive producer named Milton Gabler. Gabler loved and respected Miss Holiday and wished to present her with HER choice of material in the best possible setting. These recordings were done firstly in April of 1939 and then a bit later in April of 1944 for two sessions.Many people consider these recordings to be Billie's finest. The 16 tracks made up of mostly standards plus a couple of originals by Miss Holiday make up the bulk of the set and these are the master takes chosen by Mr. Gabler and Miss Holiday. We hope you agree with assessment that these tracks a re perhaps the finest of her long career. Sit back and enjoy a lady who was called without reservation &quot;the voice of Jazz&quot;. Happy 99th Birthday to Billie Holiday aka Lady Day.</description><itunes:subtitle>Celebratimg the 99th Birthday of Billie Holiday: &quot;The Commodore Master Takes&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140407-210200-to-20140408-000400.mp3" length="173923322" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140407-210200-to-20140408-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 31-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This wonderful recording that seems to be overlooked was Monk's penultimate recording for Columbia Records and the final official documentation of his Quartet with the great tenor saxophonist Charlie Rouse. They do three new Monk compositions on this disc. The rest were performed at a later date with Rouse absent due to a death in his family so it is Monk with his regular accompanists, Larry Gales on bass and Ben Riley on drums. The bonus is a tune (a Monk classic: &quot;In Walked Bud&quot;)with a vocal by Jon Hendricks, who was visiting the session. This was only the third time Monk had ever recorded with a vocalist. This album won a Grammy for it's unique cover but although it's near the end of Monk's career the music is superb. The title &quot;Underground&quot; refers more to the album's cover rather than to Monk himself who by this time was recognized as one of the most important figures in Jazz music both as a composer and pianist. Check Monk out always!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer/icon Thelonious Monk: &quot;Underground&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140331-210100-to-20140401-000200.mp3" length="172984655" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140331-210100-to-20140401-000200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 24-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This rather informal jam-type date was done just before Miles Davis formed his &quot;first great quintet&quot; and it features a newly healthy and strong Miles Davis just at the beginning of rise to Jazz stardom. It's an ad-hoc date with vibist Milt Jackson as the co-star. Miles had recorded with Milt on the legendary &quot;Bags' Groove&quot; date on Christmas Eve in 1954 and wanted to do more with Milt. Jackie McLean on alto was a Miles Davis protege and Miles opted to record two of McLean's compositions as well as present him on the front line. The second two pieces are without McLean who left the studio. The others involved along with Davis, Jackson and McLean are pianist Ray Bryant (a newcomer to New York at that time), bassist Percy Heath (a Davis favou
rite) and drummer Arthur Taylor. The date for all it's informalness is a perfect date with no gratuitous or uninspired playing and is a tribute to Miles, Milt, Jackie, Ray, Percy and Art.</description><itunes:subtitle>Miles Davis and Vibist Milt Jackson in Sextet/Quintet: August 5,1955</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140324-210200-to-20140325-000100.mp3" length="171068123" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140324-210200-to-20140325-000100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 17-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>There are really few words to describe the musical genius of Phineas Newborn Jr. He was born in Memphis on December 14, 1931 and died at age 57 in 1989. He could play a variety of instruments besides the piano....bass, drums, trumpet, tenor saxophone but it is genius at the piano that will give Mr. Newborn his place in Jazz History. Newborn had it all, touch, he made the piano ring with beauty, he used space and yet could make blindingly fast double octave runs and had a knack for re-harminizing tunes instantly like Art Tatum. Newborn's idols were, Tatum, Peterson and Bud Powell but he forged his own way and his own distinctive style. Intermittent mental illness forced him many times during his career to enter hospitals to recover so he was off and on the scene. This was a detriment to his fame, career and recognition and ultimately his early 
demise. Newborn deserves a place of honour like his idols because he was on their level. Tonight's Feature is a productive recording session from 1961 with top-grade Newborn and a deluxe rhythm section with Sam Jones on bass and Louis Hayes on drums. 6 Jazz standards are explored plus 2 Newborn originals.This will give anyone an idea of the scope and majesty of his playing. Long live Phineas (&quot;Finus&quot;) Newborn!</description><itunes:subtitle>&quot;The Great Jazz Piano of Phineas Newborn Jr&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140317-210200-to-20140318-000300.mp3" length="172984238" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140317-210200-to-20140318-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 10-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>&quot;Screamin' The Blues&quot; is really a classic album that doesn't enjoy the same fame as Mr. Nelson's &quot;The Blues And The Abstract Truth&quot;. It was recorded by similiar personnel but for a smaller label (Prestige/New Jazz) and about 8 months before the &quot;Abstract Truth&quot; date. Make no mistake the level of music is just as high as it the creativity. The people involved on this session are Richard &quot;Notes&quot; Williams on powerhouse trumpet and the wonderful Eric Dolphy on alto saxophone and bass clarinet.Mr. Nelson plays both alto and tenor saxophones. Pianist Richard Wyands is tasteful and swinging, the great George Duvivier is on bass and Mr.&quot;Snap Crackle&quot; aka Roy Haynes is on drums. Well thought out and organized as most Nelson recordings are...this sounds like a working band and it's close because everyone's head is in the same place. It's a great listen!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor and alto saxophonist/composer Oliver Nelson: &quot;Screamin' The Blues&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140310-210200-to-20140311-000300.mp3" length="172982987" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140310-210200-to-20140311-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 03-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>The great producer Norman Granz was responsible for bringing the jam session which he felt was the core of Jazz music, to the stage. He also recorded many studio produced jams with some of the greatest musicians in the world. Charlie Parker, Oscar Peterson, Illinois Jacquet, Count Basie, Buddy Rich and literally hundreds of others. Many of these recordings are now considered classic and essential in anyone's record collection. We will play a variety of them tonight on our special Fun Drive Show.</description><itunes:subtitle>Jam Session performances produced by Norman Granz with Stan Getz, Charlie Parker, Count Basie etc.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140303-210300-to-20140303-235800.mp3" length="167115797" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140303-210300-to-20140303-235800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 03-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>The great producer Norman Granz was responsible for bringing the jam session which he felt was the core of Jazz music, to the stage. He also recorded many studio produced jams with some of the greatest musicians in the world. Charlie Parker, Oscar Peterson, Illinois Jacquet, Count Basie, Buddy Rich and literally hundreds of others. Many of these recordings are now considered classic and essential in anyone's record collection. We will play a variety of them tonight on our special Fun Drive Show.</description><itunes:subtitle>Jam Session performances produced by Norman Granz with Stan Getz, Charlie Parker, Count Basie etc.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140303-210300-to-20140303-235800.mp3" length="167115797" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140303-210300-to-20140303-235800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 03-Mar-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>The great producer Norman Granz was responsible for bringing the jam session which he felt was the core of Jazz music, to the stage. He also recorded many studio produced jams with some of the greatest musicians in the world. Charlie Parker, Oscar Peterson, Illinois Jacquet, Count Basie, Buddy Rich and literally hundreds of others. Many of these recordings are now considered classic and essential in anyone's record collection. We will play a variety of them tonight on our special Fun Drive Show.</description><itunes:subtitle>Jam Session performances produced by Norman Granz with Stan Getz, Charlie Parker, Count Basie etc.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140303-210300-to-20140303-235800.mp3" length="167115797" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140303-210300-to-20140303-235800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 24-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This feature has a large orchestra playing music composed and arranged by Oliver Nelson who not only conducts the orchestra but is heard with others on alto and tenor saxophones. The 7 part suite is a depiction of the history of African/American people from their origin in Africa to their arrival in the USA as slaves, their emancipation and all the triumphs and tribulations ending in the optimistic part 7 called &quot;Freedom Dance&quot;. Nelson put together the cream of the crop of New York Jazz players for this project in September and November 1961.It is a credit to producer Esmond Edwards and Prestige Records that this huge project was realised. The music tells a great story but is also great Jazz and it is a tribute to Oliver Nelson who was able to tell this musical story. Afro/American Sketches is a quite masterpiece.</description><itunes:subtitle>Oliver Nelson/saxophonist/composer/arranger: &quot;Afro/American Sketches&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140224-210200-to-20140225-001300.mp3" length="182539376" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140224-210200-to-20140225-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 17-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This album was Herbie Hancock's last for Blue Note Records. He was a rising star as he had been part of Miles Davis' ground breaking &quot;second great quintet&quot; for 7 years and had just formed his own sextet. He had just signed a very lucrative contract with Warner Bros.Records but owed Blue Note one more and Blue Note went out of their way to provide Herbie with everything he needed. His new sextet consisted of Johnny Coles on trumpet and flugelhorn, Garnett Brown on trombone, Joe Henderson on tenor saxophone, Buster Williams on bass and Albert &quot;Tootie&quot; Heath on drums. The band was augmented by three more horns for a larger ensemble sound....bass trombone, bass clarinet and flute and alto flute....Tony Studd, Jerome Richardson and Hubert Laws were the extras. All of the compositions were in honour of the African-American people and the civil rights movement but the music is not overtly militant. It was recorded in 1969 during a turbulent time in US History. Four of the five pieces are by Hancock and one by bassist Williams. &quot;The Prisoner&quot; stands on it's own and has never been revisited by Herbie Hancock yet it is one of his finest and most eloquent musical statements. You are in for a treat!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Herbie Hancock: &quot;The Prisoner&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140217-210300-to-20140218-002900.mp3" length="196711538" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140217-210300-to-20140218-002900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 10-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This album is not as overt a protest or as political as last week's Jazz feature by Max Roach but has political overtones, a reflection the time it was recorded in 1961. This was the time of The Freedom Riders, young people both black and caucasian from the North who headed down to the militant Southern States to fight the segregation laws that were illegal but still practised. The members of this important edition of Art Blakey's Jazz Messengers were all African- Americans who were politically aware. The music reflects this awareness as to the civil rights movement that was taking place in the USA. The title track is a drum solo by Art Blakey dedicated to the young Freedom Riders and called &quot;The Freedom Rider&quot;. The rest of the tunes by this great Messenger edition which consisted of Wayne Shorter on tenor saxophone who was also musical director of the band. Lee Morgan on trumpet, Bobby Timmons on piano, Jymie Merritt on bass and Blakey. The compositions are two by Shorter and four by Morgan showing how creative this band was. The music is intense and swinging and the chemistry of this band is something to behold. Check out &quot;The Freedom Rider&quot;!</description><itunes:subtitle>Master drummer Art Blakey and The Jazz Messengers: &quot;The Freedom Rider&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140210-210100-to-20140211-003700.mp3" length="206235401" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140210-210100-to-20140211-003700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 03-Feb-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>By 1960 drummer Max Roach had been for years a keen student of politics and civil rights and as a black American he realized that his mission was to combine politics and his music. He would do this without compromising the quality of his music in any way. Roach was one of the music's greatest drummers and a pioneer of Modern Jazz.The Freedom Now Suite was his first fully political statement and it features his ensemble and his vocalist Abbey Lincoln. Roach wrote the music and Oscar Brown Jr. wrote the words. The band includes Mr.Roach on drums with Booker Little on trumpet, Julian Priester on trombone, Walter Benton on tenor saxophone and James Schenck on bass.The first three compositions deal with the USA and opens with &quot;Driva' Man&quot; and the guest soloist on this track is the great Coleman Hawkins. &quot;Freedom Day&quot; is by the band. Track three is Mr. Roach and Miss Lincoln only in a three part suite. Part 2 moves to Africa and Michael Olatunji is added on drums and vocal plus two other percussionists in &quot;All Africa&quot; and the final selection is in memory of the notorious Shapeville Massacre and called &quot;Tears For Johannesburg&quot;. All of this was recorded in August and Seoptember 1960. It remains a pivotal recording in the long career of Mr. Max Roach and to this day is a powerful statement.</description><itunes:subtitle>Drummer/composer Max Roach: &quot;We Insist! The Freedom Now Suite&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140203-210300-to-20140204-002600.mp3" length="194009795" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140203-210300-to-20140204-002600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 27-Jan-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Lee Konitz is one of the foremost voices of the alto saxophone. He was one of the first to emerge in the late 1940s and NOT play like Charlie Parker. He hooked up with pianist/teacher/guru Lennie Tristano and became one of his leading disciples. Konitz went on to play with Miles Davis and tour with Stan Kenton and then formed his own ensembles. Konitz has never been an &quot;in your face&quot; kind of player but always exhibited a warm woody sound coupled with a melodic concept that never relied on cliches and &quot;hot licks&quot;. Konitz was an influence on Paul Desmond and Art Pepper. Lee is also Anthony Braxton's favourite saxophonist! This album called &quot;Motion&quot; was recorded in one day and night on August 29,1961 and puts Lee with just bass and drums. The great and unheralded Sonny Dallas is on bass and the amazing Elvin Jones is on drums. Jones was with John Coltrane at the time and retains his identity but plays very differently with Konitz. These three men had never played together before and Lee just picked a group of great standard tunes to improvise on with rather amazing results. The very self-critical Mr. Konitz actually liked this record! I'm certain you will too. Konitz is still alive and well at age 86 and this album is a Konitz landmark.</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Lee Konitz: &quot;Motion&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140127-210100-to-20140128-003600.mp3" length="205481882" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140127-210100-to-20140128-003600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 20-Jan-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Bob Florence was born and raised in Los Angeles on May 20 1932 and passed away on May 15,2008 at age 75. He began his career as a concert pianist but was converted to Jazz at the Los Angeles City College. He began playing every variety of gig on piano, movie soundtracks, TV shows,backing singers of every variety but continued to compose and arrange. He wrote for Kenton, Basie, Ellington, Herman,Buddy Rich and also at times led his own bands which he called &quot;The Limited Edition&quot;. He was able to pick the virtual cream of the crop of L.A. based players who were able to reach his very high demands. His writing always emphasised the soloist and he never over-wrote. His music preserved the freedom and swing of small group Jazz. This album called &quot;Serendipity 18&quot; is one of Florence's masterpieces. 18 great musicians playing his arrangements and his compositions. Viva Bob Florence!</description><itunes:subtitle>Composer/arranger Bob Florence: &quot;Serendipity 18&quot; The Bob Florence Limited Edition Orchestra</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140120-210100-to-20140121-003400.mp3" length="203258021" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140120-210100-to-20140121-003400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 13-Jan-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Billed at &quot;The Last Concert&quot; and performed by the longest permanent group in Jazz music the Modern Jazz Quartet was going to disband. John Lewis, piano and musical director, vibist Milt Jackson, the group's major solo voice, bassist Percy Heath and drummer Connie Kay were going to go their separate ways. This great &quot;last concert&quot; took place at Avery Fisher Hall in New York on November 25,1974 and even the MJQ did some very special things with their music that night.It was recorded and occupies a special place in the MJQ's vast legacy of recordings. There is a special feel to this concert as on can imagine. As a postscript the MJQ reformed in 1981 and they continued to record and play engagements until the death in 1999 of vibist Milt Jackson. Jackson could never be replaced and that was the true end of the Quartet. Listen to these recordings to hear the MJQ at their best.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Modern Jazz Quartet: &quot;The Last Concert&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140113-210200-to-20140114-003000.mp3" length="198546755" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140113-210200-to-20140114-003000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 06-Jan-2014</title><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>&quot;Mingus Dynasty&quot; was bassist/composer Charles Mingus' second album for Columbia Records. His first &quot;Mingus Ah Um&quot; was his best selling album and it elevated Mingus out of the Jazz underground. Mingus was on his way. This second album was even more varied and much better programmed. It featured Mingus' working group with John Handy (alto), Booker Ervin (tenor) Jimmy Knepper (trombone) and Dannie Richmond(drums) as hold overs from the first album. The newcomers were Richard Williams (trumpet) and Roland Hanna (piano). That was the working group and on this date Mingus added some non-soloing horns to the mix on several tunes expanding the sound. The compositions are a mix of moods from loose jams to formal compositions and the moods vary from gentle and reflective to boiling and angry and everything in between. One of Mingus' finest recordings! Mingus Dynasty indeed!</description><itunes:subtitle>Bassist/composer Charles Mingus: &quot;Mingus Dynasty&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140106-210200-to-20140107-003700.mp3" length="205480214" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20140106-210200-to-20140107-003700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 30-Dec-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This is an often overlooked album recorded over two days on Nov.24 and Dec. 2,1959. It was done after his milestone recording &quot;Giant Steps&quot; and his great classic &quot;My Favourite Things&quot;. It is a relaxed date with Mr. Coltrane and his partners from Miles Davis' band. In fact they were all in the employ of Davis at this time. We hear Coltrane with Wynton Kelly on piano, Paul Chambers on bass and Jimmy Cobb on drums. The tunes are a mix....three underplayed standards and five originals by Mr. Coltrane. All the tunes are short and concise and reflect Mr. Coltrane in a lyrical and happy mood throughout. We also hear the first documented version of his classic composition for his first wife...&quot;Naima&quot;. &quot;Coltrane Jazz&quot; is just that.....fine music in the great tradition by the formost voice of the tenor saxophone. 
We all wish everyone out there a very HAPPY NEW YEAR from myself, Gavin Walker and The Jazz Show.</description><itunes:subtitle>John Coltrane: &quot;Coltrane Jazz&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131230-210300-to-20131231-000500.mp3" length="173854517" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131230-210300-to-20131231-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 23-Dec-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This famous (sometimes infamous) recording date that took place on Christmas Eve of 1954 has gone down in Jazz History as a milestone session which influenced generations of Jazz players.This date is a tradition on The Jazz Show and we hear it every year on the last show before Christmas. Somehow, although there is nothing obvious about Christmas in this music, nevertheless there IS a definite Christmas feeling about this music. It is by the Miles Davis All-Stars and features Mr. Davis with vibraphone master Milt Jackson, piano genius Thelonious Monk, bassist Percy Heath and drummer Kenny Clarke. Four tunes were done and two alternate takes for a total of six selections on the afternoon and evening of Dec. 24,1954.The tunes were issued on a couple of LPs...one called &quot;Bags' Groove&quot; and the other called &quot;Miles Davis and The Modern Jazz Giants&quot; and later on a variety of CDs. Tonight we wish you all a very Merry Christmas.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Miles Davis All-Stars with Milt Jackson and Thelonious Monk on Dec.24,1954: &quot;Bags' Groove&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131223-210100-to-20131224-000100.mp3" length="171762011" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131223-210100-to-20131224-000100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 16-Dec-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This was Mal Waldron's second trio date for Prestige/New Jazz Records. it was done in March of 1959 after a tour of Europe with Billie Holiday. Mal was Billie's arranger and pianist from 1957 to 1959. He was also in the 50's, house pianist/arranger/composer for Prestige Records and recorded with John Coltrane, Gene Ammons, Jackie McLean and many others. Mal had gained a great experience working with Charles Mingus and others as well. His piano style combines his major influences, Ellington, Monk and Powell all rolled into Mal Waldron. This album is a fine portrait of Mal as a composer and an interpreter of great standards. He's accompanied by Addison Farmer on bass and a young Albert &quot;Tootie&quot; Heath on drums.The first track is inspired by Mal's first trip to Europe with Miss Holiday and it's the 20 minute &quot;Overseas Suite&quot;. Three standards follow and a final Waldron opus dedicated to his family called &quot;All Of Us&quot;. This is a wonderfully refreshing date despite being done in 1959. &quot;Impressions&quot; will impress!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Mal Waldron: &quot;Impressions&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131216-210200-to-20131217-003300.mp3" length="202276403" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131216-210200-to-20131217-003300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 09-Dec-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 21:04:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Gerry Mulligan was one of the most distinctive of all the exponents of the modern baritone saxophone but that wasn't all there was to Mulligan. He was an ace arranger, composer, band leader and a more than competent pianist. Among his many bands it's his pianoless quartet that stands out in people's minds. The first one was put together in Los Angeles with trumpeter Chet Baker and was in many ways the most magical. The second was a while later with valve trombone master Bob Brookmeyer and the third is the subject of tonight's Jazz Feature and it has Mulligan with trumpet giant Art Farmer, bassist Bill Crow and drummer Dave Bailey. This definitive album was made for Columbia Records in late 1958 and early 1959. It's called &quot;What Is There To Say?&quot; after on of the songs. Two other standards are heard as well as several Mulligan compositions. It captures the best of this group and makes this version of The Mulligan Quartet arguably his finest Quartet. I leave it to you, the listener to decide.</description><itunes:subtitle>Baritone saxophone master Gerry Mulligan and his Quartet: &quot;What Is There To Say?&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131209-210400-to-20131210-003600.mp3" length="202591655" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131209-210400-to-20131210-003600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 25-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Roland Kirk was a musical phenomena and someone that we may never see the like of again. Mr. Kirk who later adopted the name &quot;Rahsaan&quot; Roland Kirk discovered his talents in his dreams. He lost his sight at a very early age but fell in love with the sound of music. He taught himself to play three horns at once making him a one-man band and later added the clarinet, flute, and trumpet plus other sound producing devices to his arsenal. He was a bizarre sight and initially to fans and especially to critics who thought he was merely an eccentric gimmick but Mr. Kirk proved them wrong. His music has depth, soul, swing and passion and tonight's Jazz Feature was the first recording to give him international prominence. It was issued and widely distributed on Mercury Records and signaled to the world that Kirk had arrived. The album is called &quot;We Free Kings&quot; and features Kirk on all his horns in the company of two stellar rhythm sections. He delivers some standards that are not overdone and mostly his own compositions. His accompanists are Richard Wyands and Hank Jones on piano, Wendell Marshall and Art Davis on bass and Charlie Persip on drums with both rhythm sections.&quot;We Free Kings&quot; is one of Roland Kirk's early masterpieces...check it out right here.</description><itunes:subtitle>Multi instrumentalist and genius Rahsaan Roland Kirk: &quot;We Free Kings&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131125-210200-to-20131126-002600.mp3" length="195646937" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131125-210200-to-20131126-002600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 18-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Wynton Kelly was one of the finest piano players on the planet during his short life (he died at age 39). His highest prominence was when he was a member of Miles Davis' Quintet from 1959 to 1963. This fine album was recorded in 1960 when he was a member of the Davis band with Kelly's hand picked trio with Paul Chambers on bass and the always dynamic Philly Joe Jones on drums.Kelly was taken for granted in his lifetime because he was not a Jazz revolutionary and because he was so consistent. He never made a performance that was less than excellent.This album entitled &quot;Kelly At Midnight&quot; preserves the essence of his playing. There are two Kelly originals and two by his friend Rudy Stevenson and the ballad feature called Weird Lullaby by Jazz character/singer Babs Gonsales. Kelly At Midnight preserves the legacy of all that is great about Wynton Kelly.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist Wynton Kelly: &quot;Kelly At Midnight&quot; with Paul Chambers(bass) and Philly Joe Jones(drums).</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131118-210300-to-20131119-003900.mp3" length="206483516" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131118-210300-to-20131119-003900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 11-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Recorded at the end of 1976 at New York's Village Vanguard. Dexter Gordon, who had been absent for many years from the American Jazz scene returns at the height of his powers and teams up with the great young trumpeter Woody Shaw and his band. The band aside from Shaw and Gordon has Ronnie Matthews on piano, Stafford James on bass and Louis Hayes on drums,.Gordon who had been in Europe for many years is welcomed back by packed houses, honours and praise. The elder statesman returns and makes music with the youngsters,as it were. The performances are all full length and unedited and were issued by Columbia on a double disc set called &quot;Homecoming&quot;. The music is energetic and creative and swings like mad! Long Tall Dexter at his best!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone giant Dexter Gordon: &quot;Homecoming&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131111-210300-to-20131112-000400.mp3" length="172969226" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131111-210300-to-20131112-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 04-Nov-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This date which took place in New York in September of 1953 was really a Jazz summit meeting. The quartet had never played together before and these four great musicians just came together like fish to water. Nominally led by the pioneer of the vibes, the great Lionel Hampton at his musical best, devoid of all his usual showbiz trappings and just displaying his musical genius. Hampton is joined by Oscar Peterson on piano and both these virtuosos challenge and spar and parry with one another with incredible musicality. Ray Brown on bass provided the underpinning with his great sound and swing. Buddy Rich, who plays only brushes throughout provides the pulse and fire underneath the to main soloists. It is a true meeting of musical giants and the repertoire was simply chosen as they went along. Standards and a few Jazz favourites are there and all the tunes are familiar. What is done to these tunes is what makes the date so exceptional. Hamp, Oscar, Ray and Buddy at their inspired best!</description><itunes:subtitle>Vibraphone master Lionel Hampton: &quot;The Lionel Hampton Quartet&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131104-210200-to-20131105-000500.mp3" length="174899102" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131104-210200-to-20131105-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 28-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Grachan Moncur 111 is one of the lesser known but important figures on the New York Jazz scene in the mid-60's when new ideas and concepts were emerging and musicians were finding new ways to create and improvise. Moncur was an educated young man and experienced playing for four years with Ray Charles and a year with The Jazztet led by Art Farmer and Benny Golson and touring also with Sonny Rollins. Moncur's skills as a trombonist with his own concept emerged on this recording and he definitely was NOT a J.J.Johnson clone. His writing skills are evident on the four selections that make up this date. The personnel here include four people who recorded and worked gigs together under the leadership of alto saxophone master Jackie McLean. Along with McLean and Moncur are two emerging stars in the persons of vibist Bobby Hutcherson and drum genius Tony Williams who was 18 years old at the time. Bob Cranshaw is on bass and he is great in any context.However the real star here is trumpeter Lee Morgan who is not ever thought of in a context such as this but proves himself to be open-minded and totally responsive to the music and shows his great range of expression. The four compositions heard here are all Moncur's and they reflect different moods and show his range of expression. Everybody here is on top of things and inspired by Moncur's music and exhibiting fresh musical ideas. &quot;Evolution&quot; was Moncur's recording debut and it was issued on Blue Note and is a modern classic in every sense of the word.</description><itunes:subtitle>Trombonist/composer Grachan Moncur 111: &quot;Evolution&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131028-210200-to-20131029-004500.mp3" length="213120071" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131028-210200-to-20131029-004500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 21-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight we celebrate what would have been the 96th Birthday of one of the great innovators of 20th Century music....John Birks &quot;Dizzy&quot; Gillespie. This recording is one of Dizzy's finest and it features an all-star band. Gillespie is the catalyst here and he even pushes his own limitless boundries in an incredibly inspired performance. Sonny Stitt is heard on alto saxophone only and like Gillespie is in intense and inspired form. John Lewis like Stitt had worked with Gillespie in their formative years in the 1940's and Lewis' playing is more outgoing than his performances with his Modern Jazz Quartet. The underrated Clifton &quot;Skeeter&quot; Best is on guitar in a tasteful role with a few fine solos and mostly rhythm playing. Percy Heath is a tower of strength on bass and like Lewis was a member of The Modern Jazz Quartet. Charlie Persip was Dizzy's favourite drummer at this time (1956). He drives the band with intelligence and taste. Only five tunes make up this date including a ballad medley that features Stitt, Dizzy and Lewis. 42' and 48&quot; of classic Jazz played by six giants and innovators. The Modern Jazz Sextet lives up to it's name in every way.  Happy Birthday Mr. Gillespie!</description><itunes:subtitle>Dizzy Gillespie and Co: &quot;The Modern Jazz Sextet&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131021-210300-to-20131022-004800.mp3" length="214730525" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131021-210300-to-20131022-004800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 14-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Organ master James Oscar Smith must be considered one of the pioneers of Jazz music as he almost single-handedly brought the Hammond organ into Jazz music. Jimmy Smith wasn't the first one to ever use the instrument in Jazz but he developed a concept on the organ that was copied by just about every practitioner who followed. Smith, after a period of learning the instrument, emerged and began to work around his hometown of Philadelphia. He was heard by Blue Note Record's Alfred Lion and signed to the label. He became Blue Note's biggest seller. This session features the Smith working trio with Quentin Warren on guitar and Donald Bailey on drums plus three magnificent horns in the person of tenor saxophonist Ike Quebec, alto saxophone master Jackie McLean and trumpeter Blue Mitchell. Each gets a ballad feature but the bulk of the other selections are great informal jams on various blues in major and minor keys. It's an inspired date and allows us to hear all these great players at their unfettered best. The album is called &quot;Open House&quot; and it has just that feeling of a group of friends gathering for some stimulating conversation and you the listener is invited.</description><itunes:subtitle>Hammond organ master Jimmy Smith: &quot;Open House&quot; with Blue Mitchell, Ike Quebec and Jackie McLean.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131014-210300-to-20131015-003500.mp3" length="202262642" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131014-210300-to-20131015-003500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 07-Oct-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Even though he had been first and foremost as one of the world's finest Jazz drummers since 1934, Jo Jones didn't make his first recording under his own name until this date in August 1955. Tonight The Jazz Show celebrates what would have been Jo's 102nd Birthday. Jo or as he was known later in life as &quot;Papa Jo&quot; died at age 73 on September 3,1985. He was really the forerunner of Modern Jazz drumming.He did away with the &quot;four on the floor&quot; reliance on the bass drum and used the hi-hat cymbal (operated with the foot) to keep time and also the large &quot;ride&quot; cymbal and it gave the rhythm section room to breathe and be dynamic rather than just pound out a beat. This is a fine date with all of Jo's favorites including the great Lucky Thompson on tenor saxophone, trombonist Bennie Green...both modernists rooted in deep swing. Underrated trumpeter Emmett Berry is on board. The rhythm section is unbeatable...Freddie Green on guitar, Walter Page on bass, Nat Pierce on piano and of course Jo Jones on drums. Count Basie replaces Nat Pierce on the two wonderful takes of the old standard &quot;Shoe Shine Boy&quot;. The Jo Jones Special Septet garnered some of the highest ratings when it was released in 1955 and it is still a classic today. Happy 102nd Birthday Papa Jo!</description><itunes:subtitle>Jonathan &quot;Jo&quot; Jones:&quot;The Jo Jones Special Septet&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131007-210200-to-20131008-003800.mp3" length="206986418" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20131007-210200-to-20131008-003800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 30-Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>We go from one of the most famous saxophonists featured last week....John Coltrane to one of the least known greats....his name Rudolph Johnson. Little is known about Mr. Johnson except that he is from Columbus, Ohio and first was heard touring with organist Jimmy McGriff. He headed west and was based in Los Angeles and spent a lot of time in San Francisco as well. A serious musician and a non-drinker and smoker he spent his time practising (8 hours a day!) and meditating. Johnson toured with Ray Charles for a few years as well He made two great recordings for the small Black Jazz label in the early 70's and tonight's Feature is his first. Done in 1971, it's called &quot;Spring Rain&quot;. Rudolph shows his range on the horn with seven of his compositions. All different moods. His accompanists are John Barnes on piano, and Reggie Johnson(no relation) on bass and a wonderful drummer named Ray Pounds. Mr. Johnson passed away in 2002 with virtually no notice by the Jazz press and to this day few people have heard this great musician. Tonight and on The Jazz Show you will!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophonist Rudolph Johnson:&quot;Spring Rain&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130930-210300-to-20131001-003800.mp3" length="205127015" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130930-210300-to-20131001-003800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 23-Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This feature is to honour the 87th Birthday of one of the most exciting, creative and influential musicians of the 20th Century namely John William Coltrane. Coltrane was under an exclusive recording contract with Prestige Records from 1957 to the end of 1958 however he was allowed to record this one date for Blue Note Records and the label's owner Alfred Lion made the most out of it by giving Coltrane a chance to not only record his own composition but write them for a three horn front line and of course pick the men to do this. Lion also paid for two days of rehearsal to get the music together. This was unheard of at the other label.The date was one of Coltrane's personal favourites and is considered a classic.

The people involved are Coltrane on tenor saxophone, Curtis Fuller on trombone, the teenage trumpet sensation, Lee Morgan, Kenny Drew on piano, Paul Chambers on bass and Philly Joe Jones on drums. The tunes are all by Coltrane (Blue Train, Moment's Notice, Locomotion, Lazy Bird) and the ballad of the set written by Kern and Mercer: &quot;I'm Old Fashioned&quot;. Blue Train stands out in the history of Coltrane's legacy and is clearly his best from his early period. Happy Birthday Mr. Coltrane.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophonist/composer John Coltrane: &quot;Blue Train&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130923-210200-to-20130924-003700.mp3" length="205481048" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130923-210200-to-20130924-003700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 16-Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2013 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The great maestro Leonard Bernstein narrates with many musical examples played by greats like Duke Ellington, Bessie Smith,Louis Armstrong, Buster Bailey, Buck Clayton, Phil Woods, Coleman Hawkins, Miles Davis, John Coltrane etc.what Jazz music is and what it isn't. This is a fun and educational look at what makes this form of music unique and valid as an art form. This disc is part of a The Jazz Show tradition in that we feature this album every year as our &quot;back to school&quot; project along with last week's Cannonball Adderley disc. This is less a Jazz history document but rather a demonstration of how this music is put together. Bernstein loved Jazz and it's obvious from this disc that he feels it's just as important as Bach, Brahms, Beethoven etc. Bernstein's lucidity and clear voice makes many of the so-called complexities of music very clear and simple. Even though this was recorded in the mid-50's it is still a valid and educational document. Leonard Bernstein adds his voice to What Is Jazz.</description><itunes:subtitle>Leonard Bernstein narrates with many musical examples:&quot;What Is Jazz&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130916-210100-to-20130917-003200.mp3" length="201650069" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130916-210100-to-20130917-003200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 09 Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The title says it all Mr. Adderley is the lucid narrator and with a series of recorded examples he takes you from the very beginnings of this great American art form up until he made this recording in 1960. This is The Jazz Show's annual &quot;back to school&quot; educational show. I hope that you find this entertaining and enlightening. Thank you Cannonball!</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley narrates &quot;An Introduction To Jazz&quot; with musical examples.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130909-210200-to-20130910-003000.mp3" length="198776105" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130909-210200-to-20130910-003000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 02-Sep-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight marks the 86th Birthday of one of the great movers and shakers of post-war Jazz, pianist/composer Horace Silver. Silver was brought to the national scene early in the 50's by none other than Stan Getz, who hired Silver's trio to back him in clubs and record dates.Silver became a charter member of Art Blakey's Jazz Messengers when it was a co-operative band.After Blakey, Silver formed his own quintet in the summer of 1956 and began his career as a bandleader.He recorded for Blue Note Records from 1956 to 1980 and left a legacy of recordings and compositions that changed the face of Jazz music. His piano styling pares down the essence of Bud Powell to it's essentials and Silver's piano stylings have influenced several generations of players. It is simple, bluesy and deeply swinging. Tonight's Feature is his first album with his own band . The band includes three former Jazz Messengers, Donald Byrd on trumpet, Hank Mobley on tenor saxophone and Doug Watkins on bass and of course, Mr Silver on piano. The drummer is a discovery of Horace's....18 year old Louis Hayes! The album is called &quot;6 Pieces of Silver&quot; and actually has 7 tunes as one standard is played called &quot;For Heaven's Sake&quot;. The album also contained one of Silver's first big hits and that's &quot;Senor Blues&quot;. Happy Birthday to Horace Silver 86 years young today.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Horace Silver: &quot;Six Pieces of Silver&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130902-210200-to-20130903-003100.mp3" length="199661813" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130902-210200-to-20130903-003100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 26-Aug-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>These are some previously unreleased performances by the great Art Pepper on his last tour of Japan in November 1981 about 6 months before his death in June of 1982. Art was aware of his somewhat fragile health and at this time was literally playing for his life. This tour was with his favourite quartet which included pianist George Cables, bassist David Williams and drummer Carl Burnett. Four great performances are featured here the first being the long and intense &quot;Make A List, Make A Wish&quot; a Pepper opus. Next is his favourite balled &quot;Everything Happens To Me&quot; followed by the up tempo &quot;Allen's Alley&quot; (aka &quot;Wee&quot;) written by Allen Eager. The final piece is a blues created by Art appropriately called &quot;Arthur's Blues&quot;. All of these performances were recorded in various locations in Japan between November 13 and 24, 1981. Intense and beautiful...the one and only Art Pepper.</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Art Pepper:&quot;Art Pepper Quartet in Japan 1981&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130826-210100-to-20130827-000000.mp3" length="171013496" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130826-210100-to-20130827-000000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 26-Aug-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A series of great unreleased recordings from Pepper's final tour of Japan in November 1981 with Pepper on alto saxophone,George Cables on piano, David Williams on bass and Carl Burnett on drums.Art Pepper's favourite quartet.

THIS IS THE FULL SHOW! THE PREVIOUS ONE WAS CUT SHORT AT 3 HOURS.</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Art Pepper: &quot;The Art Pepper Quartet in Japan 1981&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130826-210100-to-20130827-003600.mp3" length="205423502" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130826-210100-to-20130827-003600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 19-Aug-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This was Lee Morgan's final recording date under his name and it was done in September of 1971. Lee was shot and killed by his estranged wife at age 33 on February 19, 1972. Morgan was identified by his relationship with hard bop but when this recording was done Morgan was looking at some new horizons. His working band consisting of tenor saxophonist/composer Billy Harper, pianist Harold Mabern, electric bassist Jymie Merritt and drummer Freddie Waits was augmented here by flutist Bobbi Humphrey,trombonist Grachan Moncur 111 and an addition acoustic bassist in the person of Reginald Workman, Of the four tunes presented here, two are by Harper...&quot;Capra Black&quot; and &quot;Croquet Ballet&quot; and one tune by bassist Jymie Merritt called &quot;Angela&quot; for Angela Davis and a fine tune by pianist Harold Mabern called &quot;In What Direction Are You Headed?&quot;. New music and a new sound from a great Jazz Master....Lee Morgan left us at 33 but his music lives forever!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trumpet great Lee Morgan: &quot;The Last Session&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130819-210300-to-20130820-003900.mp3" length="206213717" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130819-210300-to-20130820-003900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 12-Aug-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Yusef Lateef had been around the Jazz scene for quite a while playing and recording under his own name since 1957. He moved to New York with his family in 1960 and worked with Charles Mingus among others but it wasn't until the end of 1961 when he joined the group led by alto saxophonist Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley and made it a sextet that Lateef was really put on the Jazz map.He remained with the Adderley organization until 1964 when he formed this quintet heard tonight. It's a live recording from a Philadelphia Jazz club called &quot;Pep's Musical Bar&quot;. Lateef is featured on tenor saxophone, flute and oboe and a variety of exotic instruments like the bamboo flute, the shenai, and the argol. His cohorts are Richard Williams on trumpet, a young up and coming Mike Nock on piano, Ernie Farrow on bass and the legendary James Black on drums. A whole variety of tunes showing the range of this band are heard before an appreciative audience on the evening of June 29, 1964. Yusef Lateef is still going strong at 92, performing and lecturing throughout the world.Live at Pep's cooks!</description><itunes:subtitle>Multi-instrumentalist Yusef Lateef:&quot;Live At Pep's&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130812-210200-to-20130813-003500.mp3" length="203566184" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130812-210200-to-20130813-003500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 05-Aug-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is a recording which combines the incredible talents of J.J.Johnson, trombone master and his composing and arranging abilities. Mr. Johnson said at the time of this recording done in 1964 that it was his best and everything he wanted to do up to that time. He is in magnificent form on his trombone and he was able to assemble two orchestras for these dates. The first is a 17 piece band which performs three pieces and the rest is an 11 piece band doing the rest of the titles. Mr Johnson composed only one piece here called &quot;El Camino Real&quot; but he arranged 6 great Jazz standards. He generously gave Gary McFarland two compositions and arrangements. Johnson arranged Oliver Nelson's &quot;Stolen Moments&quot; and Tom McIntosh arranged and composed two selections. The orchestras contain the cream of the crop of New York based Jazz/studio players....names like Clark Terry and Thad Jones, Oliver Nelson and Jerry Dodgion and a great rhythm section with Hank Jones on piano, Bob Cranshaw on bass and Grady Tate on drums is hard to beat. J.J.! is a fine complete portrait of one of the premier Jazz musicians of the last century. J.J.....indeed!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trombonist/composer J.J. Johnson and his Orchestra: &quot;J.J.!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130805-210200-to-20130806-004000.mp3" length="208340000" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130805-210200-to-20130806-004000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 29-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Booker Telleferro Ervin was one of the most distinctive and easily identifiable voices of the tenor saxophone to emerge in the 1960's. After years of study (mostly self-study)and dues on the road with a variety of Jazz and R&amp;B bands, Booker arrived in New York at the end of 1958. He was heard and immediately hired by Charles Mingus. He became Mingus' favourite tenor player and Mingus also relied on Ervin's photographic memory for explaining various ensemble roles to different players in Mingus' Jazz Workshop. Booker remained with Mingus from 1958 to 1963. He also worked with pianist Randy Weston and recorded on his own as a sideman and as a leader. He signed with Prestige Records in 1963 and began a whole series of albums for which he is best known...The Book series...&quot;The Freedom Book&quot;, &quot;The Blues Book&quot; etc. This fine recording is his second to last and his second for Blue Note records. Ervin died of kidney failure in July of 1970 at age 39. After this date there was only one more recorded appearance and that was with alto saxophonist Eric Kloss on Prestige called &quot;In The Land Of The Giants&quot;. This date is important as it is so strong and the band sounds like a working band. Booker is heard with Woody Shaw on trumpet, Kenny Barron on piano, Jan Arnet (from the Czech Republic) on bass and the great Billy Higgins on drums. Barron and Shaw contribute a tune each and Ervin wrote the rest. There are five tunes in all. This is a fine date that should be better known in the small legacy that was left by Booker Ervin. Tex Book Tenor cooks!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophonist Booker Ervin:&quot;Tex Book Tenor&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130729-210200-to-20130730-003000.mp3" length="198776522" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130729-210200-to-20130730-003000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 22-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The Jazz Feature tonight is by a unique individual. A very accomplished human being by the name of Dr. Denny Zeitlin. Zeitlin is a practicing psychiatrist/author and teacher AND one of the most individual and accomplished pianists on the planet. He was able to pursue both careers with equal dedication. The Jazz Feature is by his working band that he put together when he moved from the east to the Bay Area. He had begun practicing and teaching in his field of psychiatry and working in festivals, clubs etc. with this working trio. The great Charlie Haden is here on bass and the innovative drummer, Jerry Granelli work hand in glove with Denny to provide a very different piano trio sound. The album consists of good quality standards interpreted with the Zeitlin style, and several wonderful original compositions created by Zeitlin. The album was issued in 1965 on Columbia Records and was the first documentation of the Denny Zeitlin Trio. The album was called &quot;Carnival&quot; and is a gem. Dr. Zeitlin is alive and well and living in the Bay Area and continues to pursue both of his professions. Long live Dr. Denny!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Dr. Denny Zeitlin: &quot;Carnival&quot; with Charlie Haden and Jerry Ganelli.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130722-210000-to-20130723-003100.mp3" length="201627551" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130722-210000-to-20130723-003100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 15-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight(July 15, 2013)would have been the 90th birthday of one of the greatest drummers in Modern Jazz. Joseph Rudolph Jones aka &quot;Philly Joe&quot; Jones, who earned his place in Jazz history from his time with Miles Davis from 1952 to 1958. He appeared on albums led by himself and is a sideman on some of the most influential recordings in this music. Philly Joe's long and varied career in Jazz took him all over the world and he is to this day one of the most influential drummers in Jazz. He died fairly young from cancer on August 30,1985 at age 62. Tonight's Jazz Feature is one of his finest albums under his name called &quot;Philly Joe's Beat&quot; It is by his working band that he put together in 1960. It includes one of the few recordings by a great trumpeter named Michael Downs. On tenor saxophone is fellow Philadelphian  Bill Barron. Walter Davis Jr. is on piano and the great Paul Chambers is on bass and of course Philly Joe on drums. The band is tight and well rehearsed and the tunes include 3 that Philly Joe played when he was with Miles Davis (Salt Peanuts, Dear Old Stockholm and Two Bass Hit) plus one by trumpeter John Hines called &quot;Muse Rapture&quot; and an original by bassist Jimmy Garrison called &quot;Lori&quot;, one by Philly Joe called &quot;Got To Take Another Chance&quot;  and finally a tune from early Modern Jazz by Dizzy Gillespie called &quot;That's Earl Brother&quot;. this operation.Happy Birthday Mr. Jones...your beat goes on!</description><itunes:subtitle>Drum master &quot;Philly Joe&quot; Jones: &quot;Philly Joe's Beat&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130715-210200-to-20130716-003000.mp3" length="198781526" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130715-210200-to-20130716-003000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 08-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Lou Donaldson is a Jazz Master of the first order and is still touring and playing at age 86. During the late 60's and early 70's he did a whole series of albums for Blue Note that were really a great combination of funk, Jazz and R&amp;B. Lou had established his credentials with Clifford Brown, Elmo Hope, Art Blakey as well a great straight-ahead dates under his own name so there was no argument as to his abilities. His R&amp;B flavoured albums were treated harshly by the critics but they sold well and preserved the essence of Jazz. Jazz and R&amp;B have always had a healthy relationship and this date proves it. Donaldson has trumpet on the front line with guitar, Hammond organ, the occasional electric bass and drums. The music here covers all the bases and can be listened to and danced to. There is something for everyone here....a couple of good funky tunes, a beautiful ballad (Over The Rainbow), a calypso flavoured tune and straight-ahead swinger. Lou Donaldson hits all the bases and as he states in the album's title &quot;Everything I Play is Funky&quot;. Long live Papa Lou!</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Lou Donaldson: &quot;Everything I Play Is Funky&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130708-210200-to-20130709-003400.mp3" length="202609169" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130708-210200-to-20130709-003400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 01-Jul-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is a classic album make no mistake about that fact. It was given a lukewarm treatment by the Jazz critics at the time because it was such a casual and easy-going affair. It was Coltrane's first appearance on his new label, Atlantic Records. He had been with Prestige for over two years and moved to the more upscale Atlantic. It was done in January of 1959. The great producer Nesuhi Ertegun suggested that Coltrane record with one of Atlantic's big stars,the vibe master, Milt &quot;Bags&quot; Jackson. Jackson and Coltrane knew each other and had played together before and were friends so the idea was readily accepted. Jackson and Coltrane put their heads together and chose the rhythm section Jackson chose pianist hank Jones and drummer Connie kay and Coltrane picked bassist Paul Chambers. Several good standards were chosen and one early modern Jazz classic....&quot;Bebop&quot; (by Dizzy Gillespie. Three blues tunes by Jackson are heard and they are all good as Coltrane and Jackson are magnificent blues players. Coltrane moves a little closer to Jackson's concept on this date but this is because he is such a master musician who can adapt to any context. Bags and Trane is a real classic so sit back and enjoy the work of five Jazz masters!</description><itunes:subtitle>Vibist Milt Jackson and tenor saxophonist John Coltrane: &quot;Bags and Trane&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130701-210200-to-20130702-003400.mp3" length="202608752" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130701-210200-to-20130702-003400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 24-Jun-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Eli &quot;Lucky&quot; Thompson had a long career in Jazz music but not all of it was lucky. He was very respected in the community for his great talent on the tenor(and later the soprano) saxophone. He was a proud and determined man who rankled at some of the unjust treatment of Jazz artists.The Jazz Feature is from one of the peaks in Lucky's career. He had returned from a long period in Europe and recorded a few very fine albums for Prestige and then began his own record label....it was short-lived but our Feature comes from this period. We hear Lucky on tenor and soprano saxophones with the great Tommy Flanagan on piano, Willie Ruff on bass and Walter Perkins on drums. He plays some of his intriguing originals and some very well chosen standards. The music is on a very high level and makes us wonder why Mr. Thompson chose to sell his horns and give up music entirely ten years after these recordings were done in 1965. Thompson died poor and ill in Seattle in 2005 but at least in his last years he was in a care home. Lucky was one of the true Jazz Masters and proof is here on this date originally called &quot;Lucky Is Back And So Is Love&quot;.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor and soprano saxophone master Lucky Thompson: &quot;Lucky is Back and So Is Love&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130624-210200-to-20130625-002500.mp3" length="194009378" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130624-210200-to-20130625-002500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 17-Jun-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 21:01:00 -0700</pubDate><description>The late Sonny Clark left us too soon at age 31 on January 13,1963 from an overdose of heroin. Sonny was not an originator or a Jazz pioneer but a wonderful stylist who reflected the history of Modern Jazz piano. His touch and flow of ideas were the center points of his style and his ability to accompany horns made him a favourite among all the major horn players such as Jackie McLean, John Coltrane, Donald Byrd, Art Farmer, Curtis Fuller and the list goes on. Sonny was a wonderful composer as well and tonight's Jazz Feature has six of his works. Sonny's angel was Blue Note Record's Alfred Lion who loved Sonny's playing and his serious dedication to his art despite his drug problem. Lion recorded Sonny a lot as a sideman and as a leader. Trios, quartets and quintets. This session ended Sonny's first tenure with Blue Note and was done in March of 1959. It was never issued until the early 80's. It is a gem and has Donald Byrd on trumpet, Hank Mobley on tenor saxophone, Paul Chambers on bass and the great Art Blakey on drums and of course Mr. Clark on piano. They tackle six of Sonny's tunes and smoke on all of them. &quot;My Conception&quot; is one of his finest outings and is a minor classic. Long live Sonny Clark and his music!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Sonny Clark: &quot;My Conception&quot; with Donald Byrd, Hank Mobley.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130617-210100-to-20130618-002100.mp3" length="191137916" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130617-210100-to-20130618-002100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 10-Jun-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight's show is a special treat as it is the annual Jazz festival edition. The Vancouver International Jazz Festival 2013 is in the spotlight with a three hour plus edition focusing on many of the artists appearing this year. I turn the selection of the music over to my good friend John Orysik, who is not only one of the founding fathers of the Jazz festival but is it's Media Director. That's the basis of tonight's show which like the up and coming Jazz festival will be rich and varied. John Orysik and host Gavin Walker.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Annual Jazz Festival (2013) Edition with John Orysik (Media Director for The Coastal Jazz and Blues Society and Host Gavin Walker.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130610-210400-to-20130611-000800.mp3" length="175857785" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130610-210400-to-20130611-000800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>&quot;The Swinging Guitar of Tal Farlow&quot;</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is quintessential Tal Farlow one of the masters of Jazz guitar with his trio including the fabulous Eddie Costa at the piano and Vinnie Burke on bass. The repertoire is mostly standards but done in the unique and wonderfully refreshing manner by one of the great masters of Jazz guitar Tal Farlow! This album was recorded in May of 1956 after Tal did his apprenticeship with Red Norvo and Artie Shaw and others. This band became the house band at The Composer, an upscale Jazz venue in New York until it's closing in 1958. Enjoy a guitarist who was not only swinging but creative and distinctive and whose technical facility was the envy of every other guitarist. Tal Farlow Jazz giant!</description><itunes:subtitle></itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130603-210200-to-20130604-003000.mp3" length="198779024" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130603-210200-to-20130604-003000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 27-May-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight's music is swinging, lyrical and elegant and played by a group of Jazz masters under the leadership of one of the pioneers of Modern Jazz, vibraphonist Milt Jackson. After Lionel Hampton and to a lesser extent, Red Norvo, it was Milt Jackson who brought the vibes into Modern Jazz. He predominated on that instrument throughout his lifetime. As the primary member of The Modern Jazz Quartet he was able to branch out into his own career in person and on records and this date is one of his finest.Done in January of 1956 it pairs Milt Jackson with one of the most authoritative voices of the tenor saxophone and sadly one of the most overlooked...Eli &quot;Lucky&quot; Thompson. His sound and concept is one of the most original. These two gentlemen are accompanied by an ideal rhythm section of Hank Jones, one of the piano masters, Wendell Marshall on bass and Kenny Clarke on drums. Standards and blues abound and played with the touch of five Jazz Masters.</description><itunes:subtitle>Vibraphone master Milt Jackson with tenor saxophonist Lucky Thompson: &quot;The Jazz Skyline&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130527-210300-to-20130528-003500.mp3" length="202608335" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130527-210300-to-20130528-003500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 20-May-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Pianist/composer Freddie Redd occupies a small but important place in Modern Jazz. A self-taught and resourceful musician, Freddie Redd worked hard throughout the 1950's to establish himself on the New York Jazz scene. His breakthrough came when he signed with Blue Note Records and recorded his &quot;Music For The Connection&quot; with his quartet. The Connection was an off-Broadway play put on by The Living Theatre that was about drug addicts and featured Freddie's band in playing and speaking roles. It had a long run. The recording was highly praised and sold very well. This record is for this writer Freddie Redd's masterpiece and was his second Blue Note date. It features his quintet playing all Freddie's great compositions. The playing is superb and the band is tight. All of Freddie's tunes have substance and it's a shame that Blue Note didn't promote this recording very well as it soon became a collector's item. The people involved are Jackie McLean on alto saxophone, Tina Brooks on tenor saxophone, Paul Chambers on bass, Louis Hayes on drums and of course Freddie Redd on piano. Mr. Redd told this writer that this was his favourite recording of his own wok and was very proud of this date. Check out &quot;Shades of Redd&quot;.....it reall is a masterpiece!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Freddie Redd: &quot;Shades of Redd&quot; with Jackie McLean and Tina Brooks.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130520-210200-to-20130521-002800.mp3" length="196884176" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130520-210200-to-20130521-002800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 13-May-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A &quot;desert island&quot; disc. This was a short-lived band that performed a few gigs in the New York area then for two afternoons in May of 1962 went into the studio to record this date. The leader was the redoubtable Roy Haynes with Henry Grimes on bass and Tommy Flanagan on piano. They are at their very best but what makes this date unique and special is the front man...Rahsaan Roland Kirk on tenor saxophone, manzello (a soprano saxophone), the stritch (an elongated alto saxophone) and his distinctive flute and other paraphernalia. The well chosen repertoire includes three Haynes originals and four standards that have never been overplayed. When you hear this date you will understand why it is on many people's &quot;desert island&quot; records.</description><itunes:subtitle>Drum Master Roy Haynes with Rahsaan Roland Kirk:&quot;Out Of The Afternoon&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130513-210200-to-20130514-003600.mp3" length="204522782" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130513-210200-to-20130514-003600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 06-May-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This intimate get together between two musically related people became an instant classic. It was a true meeting of minds by two of the most prominent Jazz players. Pianist Bill Evans and guitarist Jim Hall are not only known for their individuality but their musicality. They are both virtuosi who don't need to show off their chops on every tune. They are humble to the MUSIC, first and foremost. They met in 1959 at the Lenox School of Music where they were teaching and established a mutual admiration society. This came to fruition on this duet recording done in April and May of 1962 for United Artists Records called &quot;Undercurrent&quot; The two men explore a variety of great standard and non-standard tunes plus an original by Jim Hall and one by John Lewis. The result is one of the essential Jazz recordings. Undercurrent is an album of great creativity, intense introspection and wonderful lyricism by Evans and Hall.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist Bill Evans and guitarist Jim Hall:&quot;Undercurrent&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130506-210200-to-20130507-002800.mp3" length="196885427" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130506-210200-to-20130507-002800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 29-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>To celebrate the 114th Anniversary of Duke Ellington's birth, The Jazz Show presents one of his true musical masterpieces....The Far East Suite. The music was written by Ellington and his alter-ego Billy Strayhorn after two tours. The first was a tour of the Middle East (Lebanon, Syria, Jordan etc,) and India and Sri Lanka. There followed a second tour to the Far East: (Japan, South Korea, Hong Kong etc. Duke and Strayhorn wrote all the music after these tours and it culminated into a 9 part suite. It was recorded over a period 3 days in December,1966 and became one of Ellington's great recordings. The band was at it's peak and all of the great soloists and players were healthy and playing their best. Paul Gonsalves, Johnny Hodges, Jimmy Hamilton (on clarinet), Harry Carney, Lawrence Brown, Cootie Williams, Cat Anderson and all of the others. The new bassist was the young virtuoso, John Lamb and making his recording debut on this date was the incredible drummer Rufus &quot;Speedy&quot; Jones. There is some magnificent Ellington piano as a bonus as well. Happy Birthday Edward Kennedy Ellington, your music will live forever!</description><itunes:subtitle>Duke Ellington and His Orchestra:&quot;The Far East Suite&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130429-210200-to-20130430-002900.mp3" length="197885810" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130429-210200-to-20130430-002900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 22-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight The Jazz Show honours and celebrates the 91st Birthday of one of American's most individual and iconic geniuses of this music referred to as Jazz....the one and only Charles Mingus. Mingus was a wonderful pianist and a virtuoso bassist but one of this music's greatest composers. He ranks with Ellington and Monk at creating a huge body of work. Today Mingus' compositions are played by the Mingus Big Band and his legacy is in the hands of his widow, Susan Mingus. This album was recorded in early 1963 with an 11 piece orchestra that had played two long engagements at Bird and The Village Vanguard in New York. The music was the first album in Mingus' new contract with Impulse Records and the label spared no expense catering to Mingus' wishes in the production and most importantly in the post-production. Mingus had full control as to his musical vision and this album was one, at the time that Mingus felt was his best to date. It is a suite of 3 movements with the long 4th being an amalgam of the first three. It's called &quot;The Black Saint and The Sinner Lady&quot; and has some outstanding solos by Jerome richardson on soprano and baritone saxophone, Mingus on bass and piano, Jaki Byard on piano but most importantly Charlie Mariano on alto saxophone. Mariano tears and cries out with unbridled passion with some of his best playing ever. This is a challenging and dense work worthy of listening to and re-listening.Happy Birthday Charles Mingus!</description><itunes:subtitle>Bassist/composer Charles Mingus:&quot;The Black Saint and the Sinner Lady&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130422-210200-to-20130423-002400.mp3" length="193051946" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130422-210200-to-20130423-002400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 15-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This well organized session featured two great Chicago-born musicians who went to the famous DuSable High School and learned the nuts and bolts of music from the redoubtable Captain Walter Dyett. Green went onto play with the great Earl Hines' band in 1943 and Ammons became a star in the famous Billy Eckstine band in 1944-45. Ammons' birthday was April 14 (1925-1974) and Green's was April 16 (1923-1977. Tonight's program broadcast on April 15 honours their birthdays. Along with trombonist Green and tenor saxophonist Ammons....two of the most recognizable voices on their horns...are cornettist Nat Adderley and the &quot;two Franks&quot; from the Basie band Frank Foster and Frank Wess. Both are great tenor saxophonists and Wess is also heard on flute. The rhythm section is fine with Tommy Flanagan on piano, Eddie Jones (also from the Basie band) on bass and the youngest member of the musical Heath Family, drummer Albert &quot;Tootie&quot; Heath. Green penned two tunes and Ammons did one and Foster contributed the opener (&quot;Juggin' Around&quot;) and Wess contributed one plus there is a delightful version of Cannonball Adderley's tune called &quot;Sermonette&quot;. Foster and Wess helped arrange some of the tunes . This is a well run date that doesn't sprawl and is cohesive but leaves plenty of blowing room for everyone. So HAPPY BIRTHDAY Bennie Green and Gene Ammons. This date wasn't called &quot;The Swingin'est&quot; for nuthin'!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trombonist Bennie Green and tenor saxophonist Gene Ammons:&quot;The Swingin'est!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130415-210300-to-20130416-002300.mp3" length="191137082" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130415-210300-to-20130416-002300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 08-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This great band was based in San Francisco and was the brain child of tenor and soprano saxophonist Mel Martin who organized this band in the early 1980's. Mel is a well known teacher,lecturer,and a player who among others has worked with Dizzy Gillespie, Freddie Hubbard, Benny Carter and so many others plus pop groups like Azteca, Tower of power and Cold Blood. Mel picked some of the very best players in the Bay Area like the great John Handy on alto saxophone. John had worked with Charles Mingus and Randy Weston and led his own groups and was an icon in San Francisco by the time this record was made in February 1984. Warren Gale is on trumpet and Gale should be more widely recognized as he is a great player with a healthy brassy sound. George Cables is on piano and there isn't much more to say about a guy who is one of the world's greatest piano players. Frank Tusa from the east coast had played with Dave Liebman's Lookout Farm and the late Eddie Marshall on drums had worked with just about everyone in the Bay Area. Two of the tunes are by Mel Martin (the opener and the closer) one is a wonderful arrangement of Tadd Dameron's &quot;On a Misty Night&quot;. Frank Tusa wrote one. Eddie Marshall also wrote one and Mel Martin arranged two great tunes by Thelonious Monk called &quot;Evidence&quot; and &quot;Monk's Mood&quot;. Bebop and Beyond is a great band and deserves to be heard so here it is!</description><itunes:subtitle>Mel Martin and Company: &quot;Bebop And Beyond&quot; with John Handy Plus.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130408-210300-to-20130409-002900.mp3" length="196883759" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130408-210300-to-20130409-002900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 01-Apr-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A startling debut recording by a musician whose short life was musically very well documented. Born in Los Angeles but upon moving to New York in mid-1959 and leaving his employer, drummer Chico Hamilton, Eric joined Charles Mingus' bubbling cauldron of musical creativity, The Jazz Workshop. Through his membership in the Mingus organization, Eric was signed by Prestige (New Jazz) Records and made his debut record on April 1, 1960. To celebrate it's 53 anniversary, we hear it tonight. Eric is heard on alto saxophone, bass clarinet and flute and composed 4 of the 7 tunes on the set. His cohorts are the up and coming young trumpet player and Eric's roommate Freddie Hubbard. Boston's Jaki Byard is on piano and George Tucker (who studied with Mingus) on bass and the redoubtable Roy Haynes (&quot;Mr. Snap-Crackle) on drums. Eric's debut is a fine document and signaled the beginning of a great career. Dolphy only lived until age 36, he died of undetected diabetes in Berlin on June 29, 1964.&quot;Outward Bound&quot; was his real beginning.</description><itunes:subtitle>Multi-instrumentalist/composer Eric Dolphy: &quot;Outward Bound&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130401-210200-to-20130402-002700.mp3" length="202642946" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130401-210200-to-20130402-002700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 25-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This oft recorded band was one of the best in Modern Jazz history. Led by the great alto saxophonist Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley, it featured his brother Nat on cornet plus the wonderfully versatile Yusef Lateef on tenor saxophone, flute and oboe on the front line plus the stellar rhythm section of Joe Zawinul on piano, Sam Jones on bass and Louis Hayes on drums. This band, even on an &quot;off&quot; night could sound so good that no one would ever know it but when inspiration struck this band was &quot;out of sight&quot;!. This set was recorded before a huge audience of 35 to 40 thousand people and the band was on fire! I think you'll agree when you hear this set recorded at The International Jazz Festival at Comblain-La-Tour , Belgium on August 5, 1962. A set to remember!</description><itunes:subtitle>The Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley Sextet: &quot;Cannonball in Europe&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130325-210200-to-20130326-002400.mp3" length="193052780" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130325-210200-to-20130326-002400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 18-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Composer,theorist, pianist, arranger George Russell occupies an important place in Jazz history. He wrote the influential theory book called &quot;The Lydian Concept of Tonal Organization&quot; and many influential musicians studied the ideas in that book. George Russell had a working band from the years 1960-64 and all of the players that passed through his band learned his theories. This rare date was only issued on LP and had no domestic issue on CD (it was issued in Europe). It's called &quot;The George Russell Sextet in Kansas City&quot; which is a bit of a misnomer as it was actually recorded in New York on February 23,1961 after a two week gig in Kansas City. There are no Russell compositions on this date but his sound is all over this set. The personnel is George Russell on piano, Don Ellis on trumpet, Dave Young on tenor saxophone, Dave Baker on trombone, Chuck Israels on bass, and Joe Hunt on drums. Baker has one tune and a young Carla Bley has two (she was a student of Russell's), Clifford Brown's blues called &quot;Sandu&quot; is here as is Eddie &quot;Cleanhead&quot; Vinson's &quot;Tune Up&quot; and finally a collective improvisation called &quot;Theme&quot; leads to a fade out ending. The band sounds as modern as tomorrow and reflects the concepts of the one and only George Russell. I'm sure Kansas City was never the same after Russell's visit!</description><itunes:subtitle>Composer/ pianist George Russell: &quot;The George Russell Sextet in Kansas City&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130318-210200-to-20130319-002200.mp3" length="191135414" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130318-210200-to-20130319-002200.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 11-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>In 1962 Lee Morgan was sick, drug addicted and destitute and without a trumpet yet at the beginning of the year he made this extraordinary recording by picking a great band, borrowing a horn and contributing 4 of the 6 tunes heard here. Morgan's story is well known and can be found in his harrowing, and candid biography called &quot;Delightfulee&quot; published by The University of Michigan Press. Despite his chaotic life Lee Morgan never lost his talent nor his playing ability. This album was his only recording in 1962 and it has been critically acclaimed. Morgan picked tenor saxophonist Clifford Jordan on the front line plus the great Barry Harris on piano and firebrand Louis Hayes on drums. Four of the six tunes are by Morgan and one by Jordan and one by the legendary pianist/composer Elmo Hope complete the date. The playing is inspired all around and don't forget that Morgan was all of 23!! 1963 proved a better year for Morgan as he met a lady who helped him rebuild his life and career and he recorded &quot;The Sidewinder&quot; for Blue Note...the rest is history until his untimely and tragic death by a shooting in February of 1972. He was only 33 but he had earned his place in Jazz History. Tonight's Feature is an important milestone in Lee's history. &quot;Take Twelve&quot; is a super recording!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trumpeter extraordinaire Lee Morgan: &quot;Take Twelve&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130311-210200-to-20130312-002100.mp3" length="190223018" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130311-210200-to-20130312-002100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 04-Mar-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Tonight is a special Jazz Show as CITR is in the middle of it's annual Fun Drive to raise money for new equipment and keep the station happening. The Jazz Feature tonight is selections from pianist/composer Horace Silver and his Quintet. The personnel of this band (with the exception of the drum chair) was stable from 1959 through 1964.Richard &quot;Blue&quot; Mitchell was on trumpet, Junior Cook on tenor saxophone, Gene Taylor on bass,first drummer was Louis Hayes who was replaced by Roy Brooks and one fine album had John Harris Jr. replacing Brooks.We will be featuring one or two selections from a variety of recordings that Silver and Co. did for Blue Note Records. Some selections were done in the studio and others done live. Sit back and enjoy one of the finest bands in Jazz history.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Horace Silver:: Selections from various albums.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130304-210200-to-20130305-002000.mp3" length="189233477" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130304-210200-to-20130305-002000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 25-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This album is one of alto saxophonist Jackie McLean's masterpieces. It is his first full-blown venture into some unknown territory. When McLean signed with Blue Note in 1959, he was basically a &quot;straight-ahead&quot; bebopper of the 2nd generation but the winds of change in Jazz were blowing in the early 60's with the arrival of Ornette Coleman, Cecil Taylor, Eric Dolphy et al. Mclean was hearing this and his playing began to open up and move away from the strict rigors of bop. This album called &quot;Let Freedom Ring!&quot; was the real beginning of that search. The ideal and open rhythm section consisted of the wonderful Walter Davis jr. at the piano who anchors McLean with his beautiful chording and sensitivity. Bassist Herbie Lewis and drummer Billy Higgins were both from Los Angeles and were boyhood friends. Higgins had just left Ornette Coleman's band and was the perfect drummer of this set. Jackie McLean with his distinctive sound (&quot;no sugar added&quot;) and his hard driving approach and his &quot;take no prisoners&quot; attitude makes the four pieces really happen. Three of McLean's tunes are dedicated to members of his family. This first is the Mingus-like &quot;Melody For Melonae&quot; for his then young daughter. The second is called &quot;Rene&quot; for his son. The third and most interesting is the modal &quot;Omega&quot; for his mother. The ballad of the set is by one of McLean's mentors, pianist Bud Powell and it's called &quot;I'll Keep Loving You&quot;. This classic album captures everyone in full flight and was the first of many groundbreaking dates from Mclean and company. &quot;Let Freedom Ring!&quot;</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophonist/composer Jackie McLean: &quot;Let Freedom Ring!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130225-210200-to-20130226-002000.mp3" length="189224720" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130225-210200-to-20130226-002000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 18-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2013 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This was the third recording of this famous suite called &quot;Black,Brown and Beige&quot; which had it's genesis at Carnegie Hall in 1943. Ellington wrote this as a &quot;tone parallel to the history of the American Negro&quot;(sic).Ellington pared the suite down from it's original hour form to this 35 minute version by focusing on two main themes that recur throughout the suite. The marvel of this version is the appearance of the foremost Gospel singer of any era....Ms. Mahalia Jackson. The surprise is that she agreed to sing with Ellington as she had always refused for religious reasons to sing with a Jazz orchestra but she was so moved by the music and it's intention that she agreed. Her voice is heard on the beautiful &quot;Come Sunday&quot; and the 23rd Psalm that ends the suite.So here then is the Ellington masterpiece full of fine solos by members of his stellar organization plus ms. Jackson. &quot;Black,Brown and Beige!&quot;</description><itunes:subtitle>Maestro Duke Ellington and his Orchestra with Mahalia Jackson:&quot;Black,Brown and Beige&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130218-210200-to-20130219-001600.mp3" length="185411255" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130218-210200-to-20130219-001600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 11-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This album was recorded in October of 1962 at the legendary Jazz Workshop in San Francisco as part of a two week engagement. Mr. Roach usually traveled with his girlfriend (who became his wife), singer Abby Lincoln but not this time. This writer was there for two nights but not on the evening of the recording. The same two pieces were played every night, among many others. By this time Max Roach was playing music that had sociological and political overtones in keeping with his African-American heritage and the turbulent times in the USA. The title piece is called &quot;Speak brother Speak&quot; and it instrumentally depicts people standing on a soapbox in any ghetto in the USA and speaking their piece. It is in a series of movements that feature everyone in the band. The second long piece is Max Roach's arrangement of a Heitor Villa-Lobos theme called &quot;Prelude&quot; that displays the talents and soloing of all four band members. The tenor saxophone is played by the great Clifford Jordan and his high keening sound and melodic concept displays his deep emotional commitment to the music. On piano is Mal Waldron who reflects the influence of Bud Powell and Monk but with his penchant for hypnotic repetition. The strong bass of the lesser known Eddie Kahn is a great asset to this band as well as his soloing ability and Mr.Roach is a picture of intense fire and creativity. This recording captures one of the great moments in Jazz and furthers our tribute to Black History Month.</description><itunes:subtitle>Drummer/composer Max Roach:&quot;Speak Brother Speak!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130211-210100-to-20130212-002100.mp3" length="191135831" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130211-210100-to-20130212-002100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 04-Feb-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This album was recorded during a very turbulent time in American History.....assassinations, the Viet Nam War, youthful rebellion all rolled into one. For black Americans the assassinations of Malcolm X (1965) and Martin Luther King (1968) were uppermost in people's minds. Herbie Hancock was no different and for his final album for Blue Note records, Mr. Hancock had to make a sociological and political statement. The album was the first by his own group that he formed after leaving Miles Davis' band and it featured his Sextet with a few extra horns to expand the ensembles. The compositions are complicated, difficult to play and yet very lyrical and listenable. It is not &quot;protest music&quot; that is loud and strident. The people involved are Johnny Coles on flugelhorn, Garnett Brown on trombone,Joe Henderson on tenor saxophone, Buster Williams on bass and Albert &quot;Tootie&quot; heath on drums and Mr. Hancock on piano. There are five compositions, four by Hancock and one by Buster Williams all arranged by Hancock. There are some extra horns to enrich the ensembles as well...a bass trombone, flute and alto flute and bass clarinet.This is a unique album in Hancock's long history and this music has never been revisited since it was recorded in April 1969. It remains one of Mr. Hancock's masterpieces and is our first Black History Month tribute feature. The Prisoner stands alone in Hancock's recorded legacy.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Herbie Hancock: &quot;The Prisoner&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130204-210300-to-20130205-002000.mp3" length="188265620" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130204-210300-to-20130205-002000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 28-Jan-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>On May 1,1962, Duke Ellington had booked his Orchestra into A&amp;R Recording Studio in New York but had no idea what to record. He had written no new music for the date and was at a loss until his tenor saxophonist, Paul Gonsalves walked in, the first to arrive, looking fresh, energetic and happy. Gonsalves so many times was tardy and hung over but not today. This gave Duke his bright idea. He would do a bunch of tunes that the band knew but feature Gonsalves on every song. It was an overdue tribute to Paul, one of the great underrated tenor saxophonists of his time. Every major saxophonist from Rollins, Getz, Stitt, Coltrane, Griffin et al respected Gonsalves for his creativity and his range of emotions on the horn. Nothing stumps Mr. Gonsalves in this feature date for him. There is a great variety of moods and feels and he nails them all. You, the listener can't go wrong with the Ellington Orchestra and Paul Gonsalves! Enjoy!</description><itunes:subtitle>The Duke Ellington orchestra Featuring Tenor Saxophonist Paul Gonsalves.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130128-210300-to-20130129-001300.mp3" length="181581110" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130128-210300-to-20130129-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 21-Jan-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 21:04:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Boniface Ferdinand Leonard &quot;Buddy&quot; DeFranco was the man who brought the clarinet into the Modern jazz era. DeFranco began and can be heard on very early recordings in the mid-forties sounding like a combination of Benny Goodman and Artie Shaw but he soon was absorbing the musical language of Charlie Parker and his disciples and &quot;modernized&quot; his style and became the leading voice of the clarinet in the 40's.50's,60's and beyond. There were a few others who played modern clarinet but none could match Mr. DeFranco. This album isn't called &quot;Mr.Clarinet!&quot; for nothing! It features Buddy DeFranco's working band with Kenny Drew on piano, Milt Hinton on bass and the dynamic Art Blakey on drums. The repertoire is a well chosen mix of standards plus originals by DeFranco and Drew. This is Jazz at it's best!</description><itunes:subtitle>Buddy DeFranco:&quot;Mr.Clarinet!&quot; with Kenny Drew,Milt Hinton and Art Blakey.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130121-210400-to-20130122-002800.mp3" length="194968895" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130121-210400-to-20130122-002800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 14-Jan-2013</title><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 21:04:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This great album and concept comes from the ever changing musical mind of Miles Davis, a man who not only was one of the most individual stylists of the trumpet but a man who constantly altered his music to make it fresh and new not only for him but his followers. Sometimes he lost his followers as they could not adapt to his changes but he always gained new ones. This album is from his early 70's period and he was using electric instruments like electric piano and electric guitar and also utilizing some of the concepts of funk and rock. He was playing his trumpet acoustically on this date and was in good form and healthy. The people involved in this tribute are Davis on trumpet, Steve Grossman and soprano saxophone,Herbie Hancock on keyboards, John McLaughlin on guitar, Michael Henderson on electric bass, Billy Cobham on drums.Two lengthy compositions are heard and all of this music was heard on the documentary film on the life of one of Miles Davis' heros, the first African-American Heavyweight Champion of the World,Jack Johnson. The music was conceived and recorded in 1970 and as Davis stated, the music should have gotten more acclaim than it did at the time. Tonight we relive that musical experience.</description><itunes:subtitle>Miles Davis and Co.: &quot;A Tribute to Jack Johnson&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130114-210400-to-20130115-002900.mp3" length="195924659" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20130114-210400-to-20130115-002900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 17-Dec-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2012 21:05:00 -0800</pubDate><description>There is really no need to describe this classic date. I consider this date an essential listening experience. This date defines Modern Jazz in a way that no other does. It is also a tradition on The Jazz Show as this is the last show of 2012 and the show closest to Christmas. This date was recorded on Christmas Eve 1954 and although it's not stated in the music the SPIRIT of Christmas is here. The players are the nominal leader, trumpeter and Jazz icon Miles Davis. In 1954 he was emerging from a dark period in his life and beginning to really assert his importance as a major Jazz figure. Milt Jackson is so consistent in his solos on vibes and the spice of the session is the piano of Thelonious Monk. Monk was not Davis' choice but the choice of the record label owner Bob Weinstock......and it was a great move as it's Monk's solos that put the edge on the music. Percy Heath on bass and Kenny Clarke were the rhythm section for the Modern Jazz Quartet and Miles Davis' first choice. This date is Jazz history and will be heard as long as Jazz is alive in this world. Some of the book on jazz was written here. Merry Christmas and Happy New Year and I look forward to presenting music for you in 2013.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Miles Davis All-Stars with Thelonious Monk and Milt Jackson:&quot;The Bags' Groove Session&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121217-210500-to-20121218-001500.mp3" length="181579859" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121217-210500-to-20121218-001500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 10-Dec-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This famous recording put alto saxophonist/composer John Handy back on the Jazz map.After a great beginning in New York as part of The Charles Mingus Jazz Workshop and pianist Randy Weston's band and his own group, John moved back to the Bay Area to complete his music degree at San Francisco State. His career was a bit in limbo after leaving New York but this Quintet came together with the addition of two great musicians from Vancouver B.C. They were bassist Don Thompson and drummer Terry Clarke. Handy's unique instrumentation on the front line was himself on alto saxophone and Michael White on violin and Jerry Hahn on guitar. Handy built the band in Vancouver and further developed it at a famous club in San Francisco called &quot;The Both/And&quot;. They became THE leading group in San Francisco and were invited to play at the Monterey Jazz Festival in 1965. They played only two long Handy compositions but stole the show and were the talk of the festival. The set was recorded on Columbia Records and became a best-seller.We feature it tonight.....a classic!</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophonist/composer John Handy:&quot;The John Handy Quintet at the 1965 Monterey Jazz Festival&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121210-210300-to-20121211-002100.mp3" length="189221801" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121210-210300-to-20121211-002100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 03-Dec-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This obscure artist who rarely if ever played his music in public (he made his living playing in Dixieland and show bands) was able through the graces of Blue Note Records' Alfred Lion to record a series of dates with hand-picked sidemen playing his own compositions. Lion released Herbies first two albums on two 10&quot; LPs called &quot;The Prophetic Herbie Nichols&quot; Volumes 1 &amp; 2. Tonight we hear his first 12 pieces that made up these records. Nichols is on piano with Al McKibbon on bass and Art Blakey on drums. The dates were done in May of 1955 and presents the evocative compositions of Mr. Nichols with his marvelous piano playing. The prophetic Herbie Nichols indeed!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Herbie Nichols:&quot;The Prophetic Herbie Nichols&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121203-210300-to-20121204-002500.mp3" length="193051529" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121203-210300-to-20121204-002500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 19-Nov-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This great edition of the Kenton band performs one of composer/arranger Johnny Richards' masterpieces. It's a seven part suite called &quot;Cuban Fire&quot;. Richards was born in Mexico of Spanish and Mexican parentage and this suite reflects not only his influences from the great modern classical composers like, Bartok, Stravinsky, Hindemith etc but also his Latino background. This edition of the Kenton band was fill of great soloists and they add to the expansive drama of this suite. Players like saxophonists, Lucky Thompson, Bill Perkins and Lennie Niehaus all solo here as do trombonists Carl Fontana, Bob Fitzpatrick and Kent Larsen. Trumpeters, Vinnie Tano and Sam Noto are heard as well . The Kenton band is driven by guitarist Ralph Blaze, bassist Curtis Counce and drum great Mel Lewis and is also driven by a Latin percussion ensemble and two tympani players. &quot;Cuban Fire&quot; is one of Kenton's best recordings and a favorite of people who don't really like the Kenton band! &quot;Fuego Cubano!&quot; on tap tonight!</description><itunes:subtitle>The Stan Kenton Orchestra plays Johnny Richards' &quot;Cuban Fire!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121119-210200-to-20121120-001400.mp3" length="183495974" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121119-210200-to-20121120-001400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 12-Nov-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>One of the most unique and interesting musicians to ever visit our humble planet.Kirk began perfecting his mastery over three saxophones played at once, a concept that came to him in a dream. Kirk was sightless from a very young age so he lived in a world of sound.He played the tenor saxophone (his main horn) and the manzello (a soprano saxophone) and the stritch (an elongated alto saxophone) plus the flute and other instruments attached to his upper body. He was amazing sight to watch. At first he was dismissed as a gimmick but fans and critics soon found out that he was a major player.After moving to New York he was immediately signed to Mercury Records and recorded prolifically.He finished his career for Atlantic Records. He died at 42 of a stroke in 1977. Of all the albums that he made, this one called &quot;Rip,Rig and Panic&quot; stands as his masterpiece and we present it tonight as the Jazz Feature.Kirk performs with an all-star band that included the great Elvin Jones on drums, the wonderful Jaki Byard on piano and virtuoso Richard Davis on bass. Five originals by Kirk plus a great old standard called &quot;Once In A While&quot; and an original by Montreal pianist Milton Sealy called &quot;Black Diamond&quot; Kirk said this album is his concept of &quot;expressing freedom&quot; and it does.</description><itunes:subtitle>Multi-instrumentalist Rahsaan Roland Kirk:&quot;Rip,Rig and Panic!</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121112-210300-to-20121113-001800.mp3" length="186371606" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121112-210300-to-20121113-001800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 05-Nov-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 21:04:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This is an unusual recording by these two major Jazz voices. Their association went back to the days when they were both in Miles Davis' sextet. By the time of this recording they were both leaders and poll winners. This date done in early 1961 brings out different characteristics of both musician. Adderley is more lyrical and gentle than his usually hard-driving self. Contrast this with the usually muted and introspective Mr. Evans who here plays with more abandon and is more outgoing than usual. The rhythm section is bassist Percy Heath and drummer Connie Kay and of course they while having all the swing and drive necessary also understand understatement and subtlety. The tunes chosen are also quite unusual as well and not your run-of-the mill standards. This album is unique in both the careers of Cannonball Adderley and Bill Evans.....&quot;Know What I Mean?&quot;</description><itunes:subtitle>Julian &quot;Cannononball&quot; Adderley and Bill Evans:&quot;Know What I Mean?&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121105-210400-to-20121106-001600.mp3" length="183495140" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121105-210400-to-20121106-001600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 29-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Today would have been the 87th Birthday of John Haley Sims better known as &quot;Zoot&quot;, a nickname that he acquired when he was a teenager and he kept for the rest of his life. Zoot Sims was one of the finest exponents of the tenor saxophone. he played and recorded on the alto and soprano horns but it's his tenor that stands out. He was one of the original &quot;four brothers&quot; in Woody Herman's legendary Second Herd and after that,Zoot struck out on his own. He usually worked with a quartet or in tandem with his other &quot;brother&quot;, Al Cohn. Tonight's feature is one of Zoot's finest albums recorded in 1960 and called &quot;Down Home&quot;. As this album has no ballads I'll include a couple from a session recorded around the same time with the same instrumentation. Zoot appears here with the great Dave McKenna on piano, George Tucker on bass and Dannie Richmond on drums. The rhythm section on the ballads is Henri Renaud on piano, Bob Whitlock on bass and Jean-Louis Viale on drums.There is nothing quite like the warmth and swing of Zoot's tenor. Happy Birthday Mr. Sims.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophonist Zoot Sims:&quot;Down Home&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121029-210200-to-20121030-001300.mp3" length="182526032" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121029-210200-to-20121030-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 22-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Two of the finest and most innovative trumpeters in Jazz are on tap here. Roy &quot;Little Jazz&quot; Eldridge and John Birks &quot;Dizzy&quot; Gillespie. Roy was the elder of the two and came up in the 30's during the &quot;swing era&quot;. It had been said and it is a generalization with some merit that Roy is the link between Louis Armstrong and Dizzy Gillespie. Dizzy Gillespie needs no introduction as he is one of the pioneers of Modern Jazz and one of the most brilliant and innovative trumpeters of any era. These two Jazz Masters are accompanied with skill and inspiration by Oscar Peterson on piano, Herb Ellis on guitar, Ray Brown on bass and Louis Bellson on drums so it doesn't get much better than that! The date was simply called &quot;Roy and Diz&quot; and was done in Los Angeles on October 29, 1954 and supervised and produced by the great Norman Granz. Blues, good standards and a great ballad make up the tunes you'll hear. Trumpets all out!!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>&quot;Roy And Diz&quot;:Roy Eldridge and Dizzy Gillespie with Oscar Peterson and Co.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121022-210300-to-20121023-001900.mp3" length="187328204" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121022-210300-to-20121023-001900.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 15-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight's Feature is a true Jazz summit meeting. It took place in a New York studio for United Artists Records on September 17,1962. The people involved are Duke Ellington on piano, Charles Mingus on bass and Max Roach on drums. All the compositions are by Duke Ellington and they are all newly created for this date with two exceptions: Juan Tizol's and Ellington's &quot;Caravan&quot; and Ellington's and Eddie DeLange's &quot;Solitude&quot;. This amazing meeting is now considered a truly classic encounter and I think you, the listener will agree!</description><itunes:subtitle>Ellington/Mingus/Roach:&quot;Money Jungle&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121015-210300-to-20121016-001700.mp3" length="185323685" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121015-210300-to-20121016-001700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 08-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 21:09:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Today, October 8 is the birthday of one of the great masters of the big baritone saxophone, Park Frederick Adams 111 better known as Pepper. He was born in Highland Park, Michigan (near Detroit) and began playing in Detroit. He emigrated to New York in the mid-50's along with many players from Detroit. This Feature is about a very short-lived band co-led by Adams and trombonist Jimmy Knepper. It's their only recording done in March of 1958 but it is of very high quality. Backing Pepper and Knepper is pianist Wynton Kelly, and two colleagues from Detroit, bassist Doug Watkins and soon to be great, drummer Elvin Jones. Two Ellington tunes are played and two by Knepper, one by album producer and critic Leonard Feather, one by vocalist Jon Hendricks and one by Pepper Adams. This was a fine little band and this one album should have kept it going but this is all we have so enjoy it. It's worth it! Pepper Adams was taken from us in 1986, a victim of lung cancer but we have his many albums to appreciate his major talent.</description><itunes:subtitle>Baritone saxohpne master Pepper Adams:&quot;The Pepper/Knepper Quintet&quot; with trombonist Jimmy Knepper.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121008-210900-to-20121009-001700.mp3" length="179757152" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121008-210900-to-20121009-001700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 01-Oct-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Baritone saxophonist Gerry Mulligan in his day was the most identifiable voice on the big horn. Mulligan was also an accomplished writer, pianist and leader. Although he was originally from New York and developed his reputation there, he moved for a variety of reasons, to Los Angeles in 1952. He worked as a writer for the Stan Kenton Orchestra and started playing on Mondays at a small club called &quot;The Haig&quot;. The club had no piano and Mulligan performed with just bass and drums and other visiting horn players in a semi-jam session setting. One of the frequent horn player guests was a young, handsome surfer guy named Chet Baker who played trumpet. Their rapport was instant and the Mulligan Quartet was started. Gerry's arrangements and the chemistry between them was heard by many people and the band was booked for weeks on end. Line-ups were common and recordings were made for two West Coast labels: Pacific Jazz and Fantasy. The band was written up in Time Magazine and Gerry Mulligan and Chet Baker were on the map.Tonight's feature is the first famous recordings by this group which consisted of:Gerry Mulligan on baritone saxophone, Chet Baker on trumpet,Bob Whitlock on bass and Chico Hamilton on drums.This group didn't last long but made a great impression and over the years, Mulligan and Baker re-united over the years. This was the beginning and we'll hear a wide selection of these early great recordings.</description><itunes:subtitle>First Recordings:The Gerry Mulligan Quartet with Chet Baker.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121001-210300-to-20121002-002500.mp3" length="193108658" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20121001-210300-to-20121002-002500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 24-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Arranger and sometime composer Gil Evans really came to prominence as the orchestrator for the great Miles Davis classics: Miles Ahead, Porgy and Bess, Sketches of Spain and Quiet Nights. Evans had always been around but in the background and his association with Davis brought him to the attention of recording companies and led to his own recordings with his own bands. This one was the second under his name and features a hand-picked band with the great alto saxophonist Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley as chief soloist. The premise is old classic tunes done up with Gil's unique arrangements hence the title &quot;New Bottle, Old Wine&quot;. The band is full of great Jazz stars like trumpeter Johnny Coles, guitarist Chuck Wayne,bassist Paul Chambers and drum master Art Blakey and many others.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Gil Evans Orchestra with Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley: &quot;New Bottle,Old Wine&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120924-210400-to-20120925-001800.mp3" length="185369555" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120924-210400-to-20120925-001800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 17-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is Part 2 of The Jazz Show's &quot;back to school&quot; concept and tonight we present a brief history of Jazz narrated by the eminent alto saxophonist/bandleader/Jazz icon, Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley. Adderley narrates with recorded examples a history of Jazz music up until the time this was done in 1960. It's too bad that he wasn't contracted to do this type of thing every five years or so but this is all we have. It is still relevant as it is a good introduction to the music's early history. As Adderley states it is a short history that touches on many aspects of the music in a non-academic way and is primarily directed at the younger less experienced listener. Everyone can derive something from this recording so enjoy Julian 'Cannonball' Adderley's &quot;Introduction To Jazz&quot;.</description><itunes:subtitle>Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley Narrates &quot;An Introduction To Jazz&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120917-210500-to-20120918-001500.mp3" length="181540244" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120917-210500-to-20120918-001500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 10-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is part 1 of The Jazz Show's &quot;back to school&quot; idea. We do this and one other recording(which will be heard next show)every year at this time in September after Labour Day. This is Maestro Leonard Bernstein's recording of &quot;What Is Jazz&quot;. Bernstein loved and respected Jazz music and the musicians who play it and understood what the music was all about. This is an educational recording designed to explain some of the mysteries of the music to the lay listener and make it entertaining as well. Bernstein uses his piano playing and enlists the help of some major Jazz artists like, Coleman Hawkins, Bessie Smith, Louis Armstrong, Miles Davis, John Coltrane and others to demonstrate what Jazz is and what it isn't.He also takes apart a popular song that is used for the basis of improvisation by different musicians in different styles to show the creativity of the Jazz artist. It's like a mini-history of the music. It's fun and educational and even some of the unintentional humour can be appreciated as this was recorded in the mid-1950's. It is still a relevant document and another moment in the extraordinary legacy of Leonard Bernstein.</description><itunes:subtitle>Maestro Leonard Bernstein Narrates:&quot;What Is Jazz&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120910-210500-to-20120911-001800.mp3" length="184407119" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120910-210500-to-20120911-001800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 03-Sep-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Nick Brignola was truly one of the masters of the baritone saxophone and although he recorded prolifically and with great consistency he is usually not mentioned with the pantheon of great voices of the baritone saxophone. This is unjust because Nick was one of the true greats on the big horn. Tonight's Feature puts Nick with an ideal rhythm section and brings out some of his finest playing. Kenny Barron is on piano, Dave Holland is on bass and the always dynamic Jack DeJohnette is on drums. The set consists of some fine Jazz standards writeen by Ornette Coleman, Tadd Dameron and Charles Mingus and Duke Ellington and Dave Holland. There are a couple of tried and true standards done in Nick Brignola fashion.....Kern's &quot;All The Things You Are&quot; and Romberg's &quot;Softly As In A Morning Sunrise&quot;. The album is called appropriately enough &quot;On A Different Level&quot;....and it is!</description><itunes:subtitle>Underrated Baritone Saxophone Great Nick Brignola: &quot;On A Different Level&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120903-210500-to-20120904-001300.mp3" length="179724209" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120903-210500-to-20120904-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 27-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Lester Young was The President. His friend Billie Holiday gave him that name as he was Jazz royalty. Pres (or Prez)had a long career in Jazz and was really &quot;the second messiah&quot; of this music as Louis Armstrong was the first.Lester burst onto the scene seemingly from out of nowhere with a brand new style on the tenor saxophone and a new way of playing chord changes. Coleman Hawkins was known as &quot;the father of the tenor saxophone&quot; and his way was the accepted way to play the horn, until Lester pointed it in a new direction. Lester's influence took place a decade after he had came onto the scene in the mid-30's. Young's influence is evident in the playing of Stan Getz, Dexter Gordon, Zoot Sims, Al Cohn, Sonny Rollins,and countless others. Tonight's Feature presents Young in his latter years, still in great form with one of his favourite pianists, Oscar Peterson. The session took place in New York in November of 1952 and issued on a number of albums. The official title is &quot;Lester Young with The Oscar Peterson Trio&quot;. Along with Lester and Oscar are Barney Kessel on guitar, Ray Brown on bass and J.C.Heard on drums, The tunes are all tried and true standards and fine vehicles for blowing on. Pres is in great form and is inspired by his company. Happy Birthday Lester Young. August 27, 2012 would mark what would be Lester's 103rd Birthday. Today is The President's Day!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor Saxophone Master Lester Young with The Oscar Peterson Trio</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120827-210500-to-20120828-001700.mp3" length="183495974" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120827-210500-to-20120828-001700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 20-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Grant Green was one of the major guitar discoveries of the early 60's. Wes Montgomery was the other and although Mr. Montgomery got more immediate recognition from the critics, Green got more recognition from musicians. Today they are both idolized by fans and players and their influence on today's Jazz guitarists is formidable. Montgomery recorded for Riverside Records and Green was signed by Blue Note and recorded prolifically for that label in basically three settings. One with just bass and drums and the other with piano added. The third setting was with various different players of the Hammond organ. Tonight it's a great session with &quot;Brother&quot; Jack McDuff on the organ, the tasty drumming of Al Harewood and the added voice of the great Yusef Lateef on tenor saxophone and on one tune, the flute. This is possibly the only recording with Yusef in an organ context. The tunes include 3 blues by Mr.Green plus two standards. One is &quot;Old Folks&quot; without the horn and the other features Mr. Lateef's flute in an interpretation of the Rodgers and Hart classic, &quot;My Funny Valentine&quot;. All in all a fine album by one of the greats of Jazz guitar.....Grant Green. It's &quot;Grantstand&quot;!</description><itunes:subtitle>Guitarist Grant Green: &quot;Grantstand&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120820-210400-to-20120821-002500.mp3" length="192094514" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120820-210400-to-20120821-002500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 13-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Guitarist Rodney Jones whose main influences have been Grant Green and Wes Montgomery is a very accomplished and polished musician. On this album on tonight's Jazz Feature, Mr. Jones goes back to the roots of funk and soul music without losing the essence of Jazz. The influence of James Brown's music is very evident on this set.Jones picked a great band to accomplish this. Two great alto saxophonists are on board either separately or on some tracks, together. Maceo Parker,who was James Brown's musical director for many years delivers his funky full-toned style along side the great Arthur Blythe. Blythe is soulful in a different way with his ripe tone and blazing ideas.They work well together. On organ is the redoubtable Dr. Lonnie Smith who works alone on some tracks and on others is supported by bassist Lonnie Plaxico. The drummer is the great New Orleans-born master of the groove, Idris Muhammad. Most of the compositions are by Rodney Jones but there are a couple of others too. One by the African saxophonist Manu Dibango called &quot;Soul Makossa&quot; with both the altoists and the other, a ballad by Mal Waldron called &quot;Soul Eyes&quot; that features Arthur Blythe. Also on tap is the Bill Withers classic &quot;Ain't No Sunshine&quot;. This is an album that gets down and funky and is danceable but doesn't lose it's Jazz essence. &quot;Soul Manifesto&quot; is your answer on tonight's show.</description><itunes:subtitle>Guitarist/composer Rodney Jones:&quot;Soul Manifesto&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120813-210400-to-20120814-001800.mp3" length="185412506" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120813-210400-to-20120814-001800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 06-Aug-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>&quot;The Hawk Flies High&quot; is tonight's Jazz Feature and of course the artist involved is a man who is considered to be &quot;the father of the tenor saxophone&quot;....the one and only Coleman Randolph Hawkins. This is his only date for Riverside Records under his name and through a great coincidence he was able to make it with a band of his choosing. One day in the office of Riverside's head honcho Orrin Keepnews, Hawkins was asked who he would pick IF he were offered a date at Riverside. He picked the men you will hear here. Keepnews offered and Hawkins accepted the date. We should be glad because it's a five-star session. Coleman Hawkins picked the underrated powerhouse trumpet star Idrees Sulieman and trombone pioneer J.J. Johnson and guitarist Barry Galbraith, Hank Jones is on piano, the great Oscar Pettiford on bass and (Papa) Jo Jones on drums.&quot;The Hawk Flies High&quot; indeed!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone titan Coleman Hawkins: &quot;The Hawk Flies High&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120806-210300-to-20120807-001300.mp3" length="181569851" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120806-210300-to-20120807-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 30-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tenor saxophonist Eric Alexander is one of the foremost voices on that most popular variety of the saxophone today. Eric is one of those musicians we call &quot;keepers of the flame&quot;...meaning that they play within the Jazz tradition and establish their personalities within that tradition. Eric has absorbed his main influences so completely and is so adept at building a solo and getting around chord changes that he is head and shoulders above most players as he is capable of great profundity. This album finds him in the company of one of his mentors, pianist Harold Mabern. He has on board his frequent cohorts, bassist John Webber and drummer Joe Farnsworth. A bonus on many tunes is Eric's front line partner the incredible New Orleans born trumpeter Nicholas Payton. Th tunes are a mixture of contemporary standards and originals. They sound like a working band as they are at one with their concept and with the leader, Eric Alexander. Eric will be just 44 years old on August 4...he is the future of this music.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophonist Eric Alexander: &quot;Summit Meeting&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120730-210300-to-20120731-001400.mp3" length="182541044" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120730-210300-to-20120731-001400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 23-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>One of the most powerful and distinctive tenor saxophonists was Booker Telleferro Ervin. Booker was Charles Mingus' favorite tenor player and this album on tonight's Jazz Feature was his last in his contract with Prestige Records. Some of Ervin's greatest albums were done for Prestige.This album features the powerhouse tenorist with a sextet with Jimmy Owens on trumpet and flugelhorn and the amazing Garnett Brown on trombone plus Ervin's best rhythm section with Jaki Byard on piano, Richard Davis on bass and Alan Dawson on drums. The album is called &quot;Heavy!&quot; and was done in September of 1966. The tunes are all arranged by Jaki Byard and cover a variety of moods. Two Byard compositions are heard and two by Garnett Brown. Ervin is featured on his favorite ballad, &quot;You Don't Know What Love Is&quot; and the capper is an extended version of the old Yiddish pop hit from the 30's called &quot;Bei Mir Bist Du Schon&quot;. &quot;Heavy!&quot; is an excellent title for this formidable date.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophonist Booker Ervin: &quot;Heavy!!!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120723-210400-to-20120724-002000.mp3" length="187304435" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120723-210400-to-20120724-002000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 16-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This wonderful album was the brainchild of the leader of this great band, Art Farmer who is one of the major voices of the trumpet and in this case, the larger more mellow cousin, the flugelhorn. Farmer is too often forgotten in the legacy of Jazz trumpet but he shouldn't be as he had his own approach and was always a thoughtful, cliche-free player. In the 1960's,Farmer led this wonderful quartet with himself on flugelhorn, Jim Hall on guitar, Steve Swallow on acoustic bass and Pete LaRoca (aka Peter Sims) on drums. The album is a group of Swedish folk melodies arranged for the quartet by Farmer. This is his present to the Swedish people who have always been open to great Jazz sounds and treated the musicians who play this music with great respect.The album title sums it up....&quot;To Sweden With Love&quot;.</description><itunes:subtitle>Flugelhorn Master Art Farmer: &quot;To Sweden With Love&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120716-210400-to-20120717-000700.mp3" length="174890762" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120716-210400-to-20120717-000700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 09-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This date remained undiscovered until 2011., 52 years after it was taped in 1959 at a famous club in Stockholm called &quot;Nalen&quot;, by the great Stan Getz and company. Getz had moved to Europe to begin a new life and as he was a great favourite with European Jazz fans, he was welcomed with open arms and given the respect that a superb artist should receive. Getz performs her with his favourite European pianist the Swede, Jan Johanssen. The bassist is the competent but obscure Daniel Jordan and the fine Danish drummer, William Shiopffe. Getz himself is in magnificent form with his tone so pure that it seems that no air is passing through the horn. His ideas are so fresh and he is so relaxed in his playing here before an attentive audience. The tunes are mostly standards mixed in with some hip Jazz originals by Ahmad Jamal, Gerry Mulligan and Al Cohn. Getz at his very best!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone master &quot;Stan Getz at Nalen&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120709-210300-to-20120710-001500.mp3" length="183455942" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120709-210300-to-20120710-001500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 02-Jul-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is a true classic recording by one of the groups that defined the piano trio concept. Ahmad Jamal, who celebrates his 82nd Birthday today (July 2,2012)is still performing and recording. This recording put Jamal on the map. It was recorded with his then newly formed trio with the great unheralded Israel Crosby on bass and New Orleans-born Vernell Fournier on drums. Jamal comes into his own here with his use of time and space and at the time was a huge influence on Miles Davis because of his touch and the other qualities I mentioned. The tunes are Jamal interpretations of standards rather then the originals he uses today. However one tune is forever and we hear his original interpretation of &quot;Poinciana&quot;. This was the &quot;hit&quot; of the original album of eight tunes. Jamal plays &quot;Poinciana&quot; to this day as he must as no Jamal performance would be complete without it. Ahmad Jamal at The Pershing is his first classic and it's forever. Happy Birthday Mr. Jamal!</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist Ahmad Jamal: &quot;Live At The Pershing Lounge&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120702-210300-to-20120703-001300.mp3" length="181579859" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120702-210300-to-20120703-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 25-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Guitarist Johnny Smith is 90 today(June 25) and even though he dropped from the national scene in 1958, his recordings for Roost Records in the early 50's were his lasting Jazz legacy. He loved the sound of light-toned tenor saxophonists and he chose three of the best for these sessions done between 1952 and 1953: Stan Getz on 2 of them and Zoot Sims and the underrated Paul Quinichette on one each. The tunes were mostly standards and a couple of these, especially &quot;Moonlight in Vermont&quot; with Getz actually made the Hit Parade. Many of these interpretations converted people to Jazz lovers from Jazz haters. Classic Jazz by guitar master Johnny Smith. Happy 90th.</description><itunes:subtitle>Guitar virtuoso Johnny Smith with Stan Getz,Zoot Sims,Paul Quinichette:&quot;Moonlight in Vermont&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120625-210300-to-20120626-001300.mp3" length="181148681" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120625-210300-to-20120626-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 18-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This album by the great late voice of modern Jazz trumpet, Woody Shaw was done in a live performance at the famed and legendary Village Vanguard in New York. Although Shaw had a rather up and down life, he was very healthy and at the peak of his musicality when this album was recorded in 1978. Shaw had assembled his best band with the late Carter Jefferson on tenor and soprano saxophones, Onaje Alan Gumbs on piano, Clint Houston on bass and Victor Lewis on drums. This band follows Woody Shaw's vision to be true to the pure Jazz dictum. The recording is creative, fiery and swings like mad. &quot;Stepping Stones&quot; is one of Woody Shaw's masterpieces.</description><itunes:subtitle>Trumpeter Woody Shaw:&quot;Stepping Stones&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120618-210300-to-20120619-000800.mp3" length="176812298" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120618-210300-to-20120619-000800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 11-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>A special show tonight with 3 hours of musicians and artists who are playing at the 2012 Vancouver International Jazz Festival. Gavin will take a backseat and be the co-host while John Orysik who is the Media Director of the Coastal Jazz and Blues Society will pick the music and talk about it. The Coastal Jazz and Blues Society produces the Jazz Festival. Tonight's show is special so please check this one out!</description><itunes:subtitle>The Jazz Show presents The Jazz festival Primer with Gavin Walker and Coastal Jazz Media Director John Orysik.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120611-210400-to-20120612-000500.mp3" length="172982570" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120611-210400-to-20120612-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 04-Jun-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Today (June 4,2012) would have been the 80th birthday of the great saxophonist/composer Oliver Edward Nelson. Sadly Mr.Nelson left us at a very early age. He was only 43 when he suffered a fatal heart attack. He left a long legacy of superb recordings and great compositions. Tonight's feature is his most famous date and one that's on many people's &quot;desert island&quot; discs. It's called &quot;The Blues and The Abstract Truth&quot; and featured six of his compositions including one of his most famous pieces that became a &quot;Jazz standard&quot;, one called &quot;Stolen Moments&quot;. The people that Mr. Nelson picked for the date are the then up-and-coming trumpeter Freddie Hubbard, the versatile and adventurous Eric Dolphy on flute and alto saxophone, George Barrow on baritone saxophone fulfills and important non-soloing section role anchoring the horns. Bill Evans is on piano, Paul Chambers is on bass and the great &quot;Mr. Snap-Crackle&quot; Roy Haynes is on drums. Oliver Nelson is heard on both alto (his favorite) and tenor saxophones. This recording is one of the best loved Modern Jazz classics!</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto/tenor saxophonist/composer Oliver Nelson: &quot;The Blues And The Abstract Truth&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120604-210500-to-20120605-001100.mp3" length="177748463" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120604-210500-to-20120605-001100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 28-May-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Neil Swainson was born in Victoria B.C. on November 15,1955 and lived his first 20 years in that city taking up the piano and the bass. He moved to Vancouver for a couple of years and then moved in 1977 to Toronto and from there became recognized as &quot;world-class&quot;. Neil played with so many people such as George Coleman, Woody Shaw, Sonny Stitt and especially pianist George Shearing. In fact Neil was Shearing's favourite bassist. Neil in May of 1987 had an opportunity of a lifetime. He was asked to present his own compositions and make a recording with whomever he chose. Neil picked Gary Williamson on piano and Jerry Fuller on drums both of whom were first-call players in Toronto and both had worked with Neil extensively. Neil chose two great Jazz stars for the front line. Trumpeter Woody Shaw was simply one of the greatest in the long legacy of great trumpeters. Joe Henderson was and still is one of the most influential tenor saxophonists of all time. This incredible combination made this recording called 49th Parallel an artistic success and a fine musical statement. Five of the six compositions are by Neil and the album ends with Henderson's well-titled &quot;Homestretch&quot;. Enjoy this rare date on tonight's Jazz Feature.</description><itunes:subtitle>Canadian-born bassist Neil Swainson: &quot;49th Parallel&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120528-210400-to-20120529-001300.mp3" length="180621593" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120528-210400-to-20120529-001300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 21-May-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 21:04:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This Feature is a great edition of the Stan Kenton Orchestra of early 1959 recorded during a performance at Las Vegas' Tropicana, one of the many casinos that featured wonderful Jazz in those days. This Kenton edition swung hard and boasted many super arrangements by the unheralded Gene Roland. The band had many wonderful soloists like trumpeters Jack Sheldon and Bud Brisbois, trombonists Archie LeCoque and Kent Larsen and a great saxophone section led by altoist Lennie Niehaus and containing tenorists Richie Kamuca and Bill Trujillo and baritone man, Billy Root. The great rhythm section of bassist Red Kelly and drummer Jerry McKenzie booted everything along. Kenton plays piano and sets the tempos and brings out this great sound to an appreciative audience at The Tropicana. A good night was had by all!</description><itunes:subtitle>&quot;The Stan Kenton Orchestra Live At The Tropicana&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120521-210400-to-20120522-001500.mp3" length="182538125" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120521-210400-to-20120522-001500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 14-May-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 21:06:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This is the only recorded meeting between these two major voices on their instruments. Vibist, Milt Jackson was the leading voice on his instrument since 1946. He can be considered a pioneer of Modern Jazz as he is to his instrument what Charlie Parker and Dizzy Gillespie were to theirs. Wes Montgomery was the same age as Jackson (born in 1923) but because he developed locally, he was not heard in the national scene until 1959 when he signed with Riverside Records. Jackson and Montgomery had never played or met together before this session and as Jackson was signing a contract with Riverside himself, he asked as a condition that he make a recording with Wes Montgomery. This date was done in late 1961 and came off beautifully and it was like these gentlemen had played together all their lives. Jackson and Montgomery are backed by a &quot;Cadillac&quot; New York rhythm section made up of Wynton Kelly on piano, Sam Jones on bass and Philly Joe Jones on drums.Seven wonderful selections made up of blues, originals and a great ballad performance of Mitchell Parish's &quot;Stairway to the Stars&quot;. &quot;Bags Meets Wes&quot; is an inspired historical document of two giants of Jazz.</description><itunes:subtitle>&quot;Bags Meets Wes&quot; : Vibist Milt Jackson and guitarist Wes Montgomery.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120514-210600-to-20120515-002100.mp3" length="186347420" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120514-210600-to-20120515-002100.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 07-May-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This delightful album was the last appearance of Thelonious Monk on record as a sideman. He did very few dates as a sideman because of his unique style and approach. Monk loved and respected trumpeter and on this date flugelhornist Clark Terry and was only too happy to make this session. Monk could be notoriously difficult in the studio but Orrin Keepnews, the owner of Riverside Records and producer of this recording has stated that this was one of the easiest dates he ever produced. &quot;Everything went down in one or two takes excepting a few of the inevitable false starts....Monk was the consummate sideman and delivered on every tune&quot;. The rhythm section was superb with Sam Jones on bass and the incomparable Philly Joe Jones on drums. &quot;In Orbit&quot; was the title and ten tunes were done, 6 by Clark, one by Monk (&quot;Let's Cool One&quot;) two old obscure standards: &quot;Trust in Me&quot; and Juan Tizol's &quot;Moonlight Fiesta&quot; plus a new original by the then young composer Sara Cassey called &quot;Very Near Blue&quot;. As this album was done in May of 1958 and was Monk's last appearance as a sideman,it has historical significance.</description><itunes:subtitle>&quot;In Orbit&quot;: Clark Terry with Thelonious Monk.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120507-210500-to-20120508-001700.mp3" length="183300401" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120507-210500-to-20120508-001700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 30-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 21:07:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley is arguably the most important post-Parker voice of the alto saxophone. Adderley was a gifted man with a high I.Q. and perfect pitch and came to music naturally. He had graduated from college and was teaching high school while still in his late teens! He and his cornet playing younger brother came to new York while on summer leave from teaching and sit-in at some of the great Jazz spots and had all the tongues wagging. This led to tonight's Feature called &quot;Presenting Cannonball&quot;. Cannonball wrote four of the tunes and is the sole horn on his ballad outing on &quot;Flamingo&quot; Along with his brother Nat, the Adderley's are backed by a &quot;Cadillac&quot; New York rhythm section with Hank Jones on piano, Paul Chambers on bass and Kenny Clarke on drums. This was the debut that helped the general Jazz listening hear how amazing the young Cannonball  was and the beginning of a great career as one of Jazz music's leading voices.</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master Julian &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley his debut recording:&quot;Presenting Cannonball&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120430-210700-to-20120501-000700.mp3" length="172023470" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120430-210700-to-20120501-000700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 23-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 21:02:00 -0700</pubDate><description>This album has got to be one of the most impressive debut recordings in recent Jazz history. It is full of originality in the playing and the compositions and it features an actual working band rather than a pick-up group. It may have been a group of unknown musicians but the sounds had swing and substance. The leader and composer of all the tunes is someone who deserves a lot more recognition for forging an individual style on the vibes that is truly his own and has no indebtedness to Milt Jackson. Walt Dickerson is a true master of the vibes. His band is tight and disciplined and includes Austin Crowe on piano and Bob Lewis on bass and someone who went on to a become one of the great Modern jazz drummers...Andrew Cyrille. &quot;This Is Walt Dickerson!&quot; is a most impressive start of a long, creative career. Walt was born in Philadelphia on April 16,1931 and passed away in May of 2008. Enjoy some truly original music by one of it's masters!</description><itunes:subtitle>Vibraphone master Walt Dickerson:&quot;This Is Walt Dickerson!&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120423-210200-to-20120424-000800.mp3" length="177721358" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120423-210200-to-20120424-000800.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 16-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 21:07:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Oliver Nelson only lived until age 43 but his influence on Jazz as an instrumentalist on alto, tenor and soprano saxophones is strong and his composing and arranging leaves a long legacy. Tonight's Feature is Oliver Nelson's debut recording called appropriately enough &quot;Meet Oliver Nelson&quot;. This St. Louis born musician seemed to come out of nowhere but he had gained much experience with &quot;territory bands&quot; in the US Midwest. He had spent 3 years as a saxophonist/arranger for the great Jazz playing entertainer Louis Jordan, who was no slouch himself on alto and tenor saxophones and was a great dancer and singer. His association with Jordan brought Nelson to New York. This recording has a stellar cast. Nelson wrote 4 of the 6 selections and plays exclusively tenor saxophone here along with the great &quot;uncrowned king of the trumpet&quot;, Kenny Dorham. Ray Bryant plays piano and Wendell Marshall is on bass as well as the always swinging Arthur Taylor on drums. Two other tunes are played...one by Billy Strayhorn called &quot;Passion Flower&quot; and Bob Haggart's immortal tune &quot;What's New?&quot; &quot;Meet Oliver Nelson&quot; is an auspicious debut and a great career starter.</description><itunes:subtitle>&quot;Meet Oliver Nelson&quot;: Tenor saxophonist/composer Nelson's debut recording.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120416-210700-to-20120417-001500.mp3" length="179663744" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120416-210700-to-20120417-001500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 09-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight's feature album represents a debut (under the artist's own name) and unfortunately the only album he recorded under his leadership. The musician in question is the unheralded tenor saxophonist Walter Benton, who was lost in the shuffle of great players who never received their due. This album was recorded when Benton ventured to New York City to join Max Roach's ensemble. Benton was heard on several Roach albums but most prominently on the famous &quot;Freedom Now Suite&quot; recording. During this time he recorded the feature album called &quot;Out of This World&quot; (the Arlen tune is the title track). This very well organized date has 5 Benton compositions and two standards, one the title track and the other the ballad of the set, the beautiful &quot;Lover Man&quot;. Benton chose his sidemen wisely in the persons of the young up-and-coming trumpeter Freddie Hubbard and this stellar rhythm section with Wynton Kelly (piano), Paul Chambers(bass) and Jimmy Cobb on drums. That of course was Miles Davis' rhythm section. Cobb was replaced for the final 4 tunes by Albert &quot;Tootie&quot; Heath. Walter Benton died in 2000 in total obscurity and deserved much more as a musician of great substance but this is often the way with great artists. We have this treasured recording so sit back and enjoy the stylings and compositions of Mr. Benton.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophonist/composer Walter Benton:&quot;Out of This World&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120409-210300-to-20120410-000600.mp3" length="174756488" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120409-210300-to-20120410-000600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 02-Apr-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Tonight's Jazz Feature is the only quartet album by the ill-fated trumpet virtuoso Booker Little. Little's life was cut down at age 23 from uremia. He was born in Memphis on this day, April 2,1938 and died in New York on October 5,1961. Little was like Clifford Brown, well educated, articulate and a clean liver and a dedicated musician. He was discovered by drummer Max Roach in Chicago. Little had just graduated from the Chicago Conservatory of Music and was sessioning around town. He joined the Roach organization and recorded with Max. This album is Booker Little's real recorded debut and it features a hand picked band including pianist Tommy Flanagan on four of the six tunes and Wynton Kelly on two. The bassist is the legendary Scott LaFaro who plays very differently here than on his recordings with Bill Evans. The drummer is the ageless Roy Haynes.Five tunes are by Booker and the ballad standard is the beautiful &quot;Who Can I Turn To?&quot; This album was recorded in 1960 and Booker Little had just turned 22! It was issued on Time Records and called simply &quot;Booker Little&quot;. Happy Birthday Mr. Little.</description><itunes:subtitle>Trumpeter/composer/legend Booker Little.&quot;The Legendary Quartet Session&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120402-210500-to-20120403-000400.mp3" length="171067289" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120402-210500-to-20120403-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 26-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>James Moody would have celebrated his 87th birthday today (March 26). Moody was 85 when he passed away in December of 2010. His career spanned many eras of Jazz music and Moody was one of the best loved figures in the music always remain positive and giving in nature and was a living example of how to not only achieve musical greatness but to maintain it. Moody had a fine little band that was together for about 10 years between 1952 and 1962 and this Jazz Feature presents Moody on alto and tenor saxophones and flute backed by his band. The focus is on Moody and the band although it contains some all-star players is background. The rhythm section is heard throughout and comprises Sonny Donaldson on piano, Steve Davis on bass and Arnold &quot;Buddy&quot; Enlow on drums. It was recorded at the legendary San Francisco club called 'The Jazz Workshop' sometime in 1961 and released on Argo Records and called &quot;Cookin' The Blues&quot;. Happy Birthday James Moody....you are missed by everyone in the Jazz Community and throughout the world.</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor/alto saxophonist and flutist James Moody:&quot;Cookin' The Blues&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120326-210300-to-20120327-000500.mp3" length="173940419" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120326-210300-to-20120327-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 19-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 21:05:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Pianist/composer/innovator Lennie Tristano was born on March 19. 1919 and he passed away on November 18, 1978 at the age of 59. Tristano is a somewhat forgotten major and influential figure in Jazz in that he literally created a whole school of thinking and playing called &quot;The Tristano School&quot;. Tristano emerged on the New York scene in 1947 and began performing and teaching. He, through a series of recordings for Prestige and Capital records created a whole new sound based on the principles of Modern Jazz set down by Charlie Parker and Dizzy Gillespie and others and took that in a whole new direction. His music was unfairly branded as &quot;intellectual&quot; but it is anything but that. Yes, it is complex and has a lighter sound than Parker and Gillespie but it swings and has much emotion but is less &quot;in your face&quot;. Tristano's disciples are saxophonists Lee Konitz and Warne Marsh, guitarist Billy Bauer and many many others. Tristano is a formidable pianist and that's what is featured tonight. Four cuts from his 1955 Atlantic album will be first heard then all of the tunes from his last official album, again for Atlantic called &quot;The new Tristano&quot;. This will allow you to enter the incredible musical mind of the one and only Lennie Tristano.</description><itunes:subtitle>Pianist/composer Lennie Tristano: &quot;The New Tristano&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120319-210500-to-20120320-000700.mp3" length="173506739" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120319-210500-to-20120320-000700.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 12-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 21:03:00 -0700</pubDate><description>Trumpeter Carmell Jones is a forgotten but important trumpeter who should be recognized as a great voice on that instrument.Jones was born in Kansas City, Kansas in 1936 and died there in 1996. He moved to Los Angeles in 1960 and became an integral part of that scene and recorded under his name and with such people as Harold Land, Bud Shank and Gerald Wilson's Big Band. New York was next in 1964 and he took Blue Mitchell's place in pianist Horace Silver's Quintet. He recorded Silver's best seller for Blue Note Records, the album &quot;Song For My Father&quot;. He didn't like New York for a variety of reasons and headed for Europe where he found success in many bands and played with lots of ex-pats like altoists Leo Wright and Herb Geller. He also enjoyed being treated as an artist and was freed from the racism of the USA. He returned to the US, first to Florida then to his hometown and lived out his life playing local gigs and teaching. Sadly he was a forgotten man. Tonight's Feature is a great album recorded after he left Silver and before his departure for Europe. Jones picked an all-star cast including the fiery Jimmy Heath on tenor saxophone, Barry Harris on piano, George Tucker on bass and Roger Humphries on drums. There are three Jones originals on this date including the title track and three good standards. It's a solid and inspired album and should help those who have never heard Carmell realize what a great musician he was.</description><itunes:subtitle>Trumpeter Carmell Jones:&quot;Jay Hawk Talk&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120312-210300-to-20120313-000500.mp3" length="174448325" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120312-210300-to-20120313-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 05-Mar-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 21:01:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Eric Allen Dolphy was like a comet that streaked across the Jazz horizon then quickly disappeared. Eric's life was short and he died from diabetes at age 36. He was born in Los Angeles on June 20,1928 to hard working West Indian immigrants who saw great musical talent in their only son. Eric began on clarinet and progressed to all the saxophones but specializing on the alto. Later he added flute and bass clarinet to his arsenal. He was said to have been proficient on the oboe and bassoon but there is no recorded evidence of those on his many recordings. Tonight's Feature is his second recording for Prestige/New Jazz done in August 1960 when he was still part of the Charles Mingus Jazz Workshop. Eric gained national prominence with drummer Chico Hamilton who brought Dolphy to New York then he joined Mingus and later went on to work with Coltrane, Max Roach, John Lewis and George Russell. He returned to Mingus for a final tour of Europe and passed away in Berlin. This album entitled &quot;Out There&quot; hearkens back to Eric's time with Chico Hamilton but it takes that sound much further afield. The Hamilton band included cello, guitar, bass, drums and Dolphy and this recording eliminates the guitar leaving us with Dolphy on alto saxophone, bass clarinet and flute along with the cello of Ron Carter. The great George Duvivier plays bass and the redoubtable Roy Haynes is on drums.The compositions are mostly Eric's with the exception of &quot;Eclipse&quot; by Mingus, and &quot;Sketch of Melba&quot; by Randy Weston and finally the beautiful &quot;Feathers&quot; by classical composer Hale Smith. &quot;Out There&quot; is a worthy document and was way ahead of it's time.</description><itunes:subtitle>Multi-instrumentalist Eric Dolphy: &quot;Out There&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120305-210100-to-20120306-000600.mp3" length="176813132" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120305-210100-to-20120306-000600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 20-Feb-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>To say that Joe Henderson was a major voice of the tenor saxophone would be understating the case. Joe seemed to burst on the scene from out of nowhere in 1963 after his first album called &quot;Page One&quot; for Blue Note Records.However there was a long preparation period and years of study and lessons with the great teacher Larry Teal. Joe made many albums and played with a slew of significant bands including that of pianist Horace Silver. Henderson freelanced and performed with his own bands and toured as a single with backing by local rhythm sections. That holds true for this album recorded during a one night stand at the ironically named &quot;Junk Club&quot; in Tokyo in August of 1971. Henderson was at the top of his game backed up quite energetically by three Japanese players. Henderson gives one of his most inspired performances on record on the four long tracks here. Two are familiar Jazz standards: Monk's &quot;Round Midnight&quot;, and Kenny Dorham's &quot;Blue Bossa&quot; and two Henderson originals. Here's Joe Henderson and his best so listen up!!!</description><itunes:subtitle>Tenor saxophone master &quot;Joe Henderson in Japan&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120220-210300-to-20120221-000600.mp3" length="41001653" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120220-210300-to-20120221-000600.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 13-Feb-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This rather rare item from Blue Note Records documents a regular working band that vibraphonist/marimbaist Bobby Hutcherson had together from 1974 until 1979. The core members are here and include Manny (Emmanuel) Boyd on flute, soprano and tenor saxophones,James Leary 111 on bass. Leary composed a lot for this band and it's his compositions that give the group it's distinctive sound. George Cables is on electric and acoustic piano and the late great Eddie Marshall ins on drums. For this recording percussionist Kenneth Nash is added. Bobby Hutcherson switches between vibes and marimba. The sound is interesting and the vibes have metal bars and the marimba's are wooden. The music sounds totally contemporary, despite being recorded in 1976. The album is called &quot;Waiting&quot; but there is no waiting here...the music is alive and vital!</description><itunes:subtitle>Vibraphone master Bobby Hutcherson: &quot;Waiting&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120213-210300-to-20120214-000400.mp3" length="172367495" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120213-210300-to-20120214-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 06-Feb-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Alto saxophonist John Handy is one of the most prominent musicians living in the Bay Area of San Francisco. He has been a prominent force on the Jazz scene, an educator,band leader and an institution. He just celebrated his 79th Birthday on February 3,2012 and is in good health and spirits and still plays selected gigs. 
Tonight's Feature is a rare recording which was his last for Roulette Records. Handy signed with the label and recorded two critically acclaimed albums but ran into legal problems with the label over royalties and this album in this writer's view is the best of the three but was never issued until about 15 years later. Handy is exclusively on alto saxophone and he's accompanied by a stellar rhythm section including the legendary Walter Bishop Jr. on piano, Julian Euell on bass and the equally legendary Edgar Bateman Jr. on drums. Five of the six tunes are Handy originals with the one standard, a great version of &quot;East of the Sun and West of the Moon&quot;. The album was recorded in New York in the summer of 1962 and soon after John Handy returned to San Francisco to begin to travel some new road in his career. This date presents John in his early prime.</description><itunes:subtitle>Alto saxophone master John Handy: &quot;Jazz With John Handy 111&quot;.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120206-210200-to-20120207-000500.mp3" length="174857402" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120206-210200-to-20120207-000500.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 30-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This Feature pays a birthday tribute to the great British Jazz giant, Tubby Hayes. He was born in London on January 30, 1935 and died at age 38 on June 8,1973 of a heart attack. Tubby was mainly a tenor saxophonist although he played all the saxes. He was accomplished on vibes and flute and played excellent piano, composed and arranged.
Tonight's Feature is his first great recording called &quot;Tubby's Groove&quot;, It was done in London when he was 24 and he is backed by the finest rhythm section in London at the time. Terry Shannon on piano, Jeff Clyne on bass and the incredible Phil Seaman on drums. The repertoire is fairly straight forward. Good standards and a few good Jazz tunes like Johnny Hines &quot;Sunny Monday&quot;, Chano Pozo's &quot;Tin Tin Deo&quot; and Hayes' own &quot;Blue Hayes&quot; etc. Happy Birthday Tubbs, your great legacy lives on throughout the world.</description><itunes:subtitle>England's Finest: Edward Brian &quot;Tubby&quot; Hayes:&quot;Tubby's Groove&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120130-210200-to-20120131-000400.mp3" length="173742761" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120130-210200-to-20120131-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 23-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 21:03:00 -0800</pubDate><description>J.J.Johnson was the premier trombonist in Modern Jazz and is to the trombone what Charlie Parker was to the alto saxophone and Dizzy Gillespie was to the trumpet and Bud Powell and Thelonious Monk were to the piano. I'm sure you now get the point that Mr. Johnson was one of the pioneers of Modern Jazz. J.J. was also a composer and arranger of major proportions and did everything from writing for large ensembles to scoring T.V. shows and movies. This Feature tonight celebrates what would have been his 88th birthday (Johnson died in 2001) and focuses on his magnificent trombone artistry. At this time (1964) he was occasionally gigging with Miles Davis, playing solo gigs, writing and as he does here, lead his own group. Johnson is backed by Harold Mabern on piano, Arthur Harper on bass and Frank Gant on drums. The tunes are all &quot;blowing&quot; vehicles such as Miles Davis' &quot;Neo&quot;(aka &quot;Teo&quot;), Max Roach's &quot;Blues Waltz&quot;, Johnson's &quot;Minor Blues&quot; and three standards,&quot;My Funny Valentine&quot;,&quot;Stella By Starlight&quot; and the less familiar &quot;Gloria&quot; by Bronislaw Kaper. Johnson is in full flight and in top form and this is one of his definitive recordings.....Proof Positive indeed!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trombone master J.J.Johnson: &quot;Proof Positive&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120123-210300-to-20120124-000400.mp3" length="172556813" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120123-210300-to-20120124-000400.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 16-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This is the 74th anniversary of this most famous Jazz concert by 'The King of Swing&quot;: Benny Goodman. This concert was the first time real Jazz music was presented on the formal concert stage. Yes, it had been heard in nightclubs, after-hour joints and ballrooms but until this momentous event, never in concert halls. Mr. Goodman's full band, his Trio and Quartet are heard plus a short &quot;History of Jazz&quot; with some guests from the Duke Ellington Band and cornet virtuoso, Bobby Hackett. Also on tap was the staged jam session where guests from Ellington's band and Count Basie's band including the Count himself jammed on Fats Waller's &quot;Honeysuckle Rose&quot;. The Trio with Goodman on clarinet, Gene Krupa on drums and Teddy Wilson on piano is heard and so is the Quartet with the addition of Lionel Hampton on vibraphone. Some of the most exciting performances by the Quartet are captured here making the studio recordings sound like rehearsals. It's all here and to this day one of the prime moments in Jazz music has been captured on recordings. We take you back tonight to enjoy the whole concert.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Famous Benny Goodman Carnegie Hall Concert of January 16,1938.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120116-210200-to-20120117-000300.mp3" length="173035946" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120116-210200-to-20120117-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 09-Jan-2012</title><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>In many ways this is an indirect tribute to the passing of the innovative drummer/composer Paul Motian. Motian had played with Jarrett from 1967 to 1976 but on this recording they had not played or seen one another in 16 years. &quot;At The Deer Head Inn&quot; is in fact a reunion of sorts and the trio is comprised of piano genius Keith Jarrett, bassist Gary Peacock and Motian. Most of us are aware of &quot;The Standards Trio&quot; with Jarrett, Peacock and Jack DeJohnette who have recorded many many discs but with Motian on board for this date the music takes a subtle turn and has, because of Motian's genius, some new and different properties. The selections are mostly standards from the &quot;Great American Songbook&quot; plus a couple of Jazz originals like Jaki Byard's &quot;Chandra&quot; and Miles Davis' &quot;Solar&quot;. The Deer Head Inn holds a special place in Jarrett's heart as it is close to his hometown of Allentown, Pennsylvania and it's where he played some of his first professional gigs as a very young man before he became known world-wide. Motian's work here is wonderful and he'll be missed by all.</description><itunes:subtitle>Keith Jarrett, Gary Peacock, and Paul Motian: &quot;At The Deer Head Inn&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120109-210200-to-20120110-000300.mp3" length="173117261" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20120109-210200-to-20120110-000300.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 19-Dec-2011</title><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>This is one of the most famous recordings in Modern Jazz history. As always on the last Jazz Show before Christmas, we play this historic date recorded on December 24,1954. The Miles Davis All-Stars gathered to lay down these tracks. Miles did not want to record with Monk as he respected him as a pianist and composer and friend but did not enjoy playing with him preferring John Lewis or Horace Silver as pianists but Bob Weinstock, the owner of Prestige Records insisted that Davis use Monk as he wanted Monk to record with some of his label's best sellers. Miles finally agreed to the date with Monk and even though they had their differences, it's Monk that provides the positive creative tension which makes this music so great. This session is a Jazz milestone. The people involved are Milt Jackson on vibes, Percy heath on bass, Kenny Clarke on drums and Monk and Miles. The tunes are Jackson's famous blues, &quot;Bags' Groove&quot;. Monk's &quot;Bemsha Swing&quot; the Gershwin's &quot;The Man I Love&quot; and Davis' opus, &quot;Swing Spring&quot;. The feel of Christmas is in the air on these recordings and Jazz history was made here. Merry Christmas from The Jazz Show and myself, Gavin Walker.See you in 2012 on January 9.</description><itunes:subtitle>The Miles Davis All-Stars with Milt Jackson and Thelonious Monk Plus.</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111219-210200-to-20111220-001000.mp3" length="179664578" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111219-210200-to-20111220-001000.mp3</guid></item><item><title>Broadcast on 12-Dec-2011</title><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 21:02:00 -0800</pubDate><description>Julian Priester is one of the major voices of Jazz trombone but is underrecognised. He was born in Chicago and like many great musicians was educated by the legendary Captain Walter Dyett at DuSable High School in Chicago. His playing credits include Sun Ra, Lionel Hampton, Max Roach, Art Blakey, Freddie Hubbard, Duke Ellington, Herbie Hancock and Dave Holland. He was also for many years a music professor at The Cornish Institute in Seattle. Tonight's Feature is his debut recording under his name called &quot;Keep Swingin'&quot; and released on Riverside Records in 1960. This is a well-organized and thoughtful date and Julian picked his sidemen well. Jimmy Heath appears on tenor saxophone on 5 of the 8 tunes. Tommy Flanagan is on piano and the great Sam Jones is on bass, plus the dynamic Elvin Jones on drums.Priester wrote 4 originals for the date and Jimmy Heath penned the great opening track called &quot;24 Hour Leave&quot; This album is an auspicious debut for a wonderful musician who deserves more recognition.....Julian Priester!</description><itunes:subtitle>Trombonist/composer Julian Priester:&quot;Keep Swingin'&quot;</itunes:subtitle><enclosure url="http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111212-210200-to-20111213-000400.mp3" length="173940419" type="audio/mpeg"/><guid isPermaLink="true">http://playlist.citr.ca/podcasting/audio/20111212-210200-to-20111213-000400.mp3</guid></item></channel></rss>